[
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 19m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$17250 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{121}=$",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $19m$ is",
    "solution": "$6859 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -9x - 9$ and $y = 8$",
    "solution": "$(-17/9, 8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $29^{8^{5}}$",
    "solution": "$29^{40}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$18^2=$",
    "solution": "$324$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $669 = $",
    "solution": "$0x29d$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $62, 32, 19 = $",
    "solution": "$189.97984084880636$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 23m$ and radius $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$1180 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $19$ and $9 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 10m$, base width $= 8m$, and height $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$160 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{2}{10}\\div\\frac{1}{6}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{6}{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $218$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$3.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[780.6012783612763, 168.26758012987796, 803.312057256546, 785.1208093487721, 425.5277480633535, 25.538217743933387, 695.9116543974388, 736.7632682082619, 311.02281309034083, 841.5343891203713, 870.32311095027, 458.2881935146301, 9.35583348934854, 180.36124639875916, 31.158997287116797, 286.097150292938, 709.0727175117664, 87.71705859026623, 170.33640353881285]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2352.78$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $-21$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$-5.800000000000004$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $637$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$10$ hours and $37$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{314}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$6.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$18^2=$",
    "solution": "$324$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $49 = $",
    "solution": "$307.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $43$ and angle $191$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$3081.89$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(561775785,516083647)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-18--54|=$",
    "solution": "$36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[10, 60, 360, 2160, 12960, 77760]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 10th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $10$, common ratio is $6$ , 10th term is $100776960$, sum upto 10th term is $120932350.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[6, 42, 294, 2058, 14406, 100842]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 10th term value, sum upto 11th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $6$, common ratio is $7$ , 10th term is $242121642$, sum upto 11th term is $1977326742.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10^2=$",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $5.59 \\times 10^{-14}$ and $6.03 \\times 10^{38} = $",
    "solution": "$3.37 \\times 10^{25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $35^{8}$ and $35^{1} = $35^{8-1} = 35^{7}$",
    "solution": "$64339296875$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $8 = $",
    "solution": "$50.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $9.79 \\times 10^{100}$ and $9.16 \\times 10^{-59} = $",
    "solution": "$8.97 \\times 10^{42}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $20$ and angle, $278$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 97.04031$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $9$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1260$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 18m$ is",
    "solution": "$4071.5040790523717 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $11$ and $16 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{1}{9}$ and $\\frac{7}{1}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 97 =",
    "solution": 83
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{6} + 4x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{6}x^{7} + \\frac{4}{4}x^{5} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 48m$, base width $= 48m$, and height $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$4704 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(64)=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $921 = $",
    "solution": "$0x399$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $51 = $",
    "solution": "$0x33$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $9x - 8y = -72$ and $4x - 3y = -27$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 0$, $y = 9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1000 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$804.247719318987 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $8$ and $9$?",
    "solution": "$12.04$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-17,-1)$ and $(15,-4)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$32y = -3x -83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $49^{10}$ and $49^{5} = $49^{10-5} = 49^{5}$",
    "solution": "$282475249$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $10$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1\\cdot4$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 16 m$, base width $= 5 m$ and height $= 19 m$ is",
    "solution": "$506.6666666666667 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{8} + 2x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$72x^{7} + 6x^{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $41 = $",
    "solution": "$257.61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5.83(-5.0\\theta + i-3.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $6x^2 + 7x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.5, -0.667)) = (\\frac{-7 + 1}{2*6}, \\frac{-7 - 1}{2*6})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[284, 267, 243, 206, 205, 257, 201, 216, 295, 275, 249, 279, 221, 263, 287, 289, 242, 236, 286, 210, 246, 291, 293, 215, 264, 248, 256]$ with $95$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(264.08312953452025, 241.39835194696118)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o432$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $42$ terms of the AP series: $41, 73, 105 ... $",
    "solution": "$29274.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $35$ and $4$?",
    "solution": "$158.97$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -3/4x + 1$ and $y = -x - 7$",
    "solution": "$(-32, 25)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-8x + 17y = 205$ and $15x + 7y = 121$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 2$, $y = 13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $84 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$1241356.355 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1941 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1941 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 23 =",
    "solution": 67
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $73$ and $14 = $",
    "solution": "$93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $34 = $",
    "solution": "$213.63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^3 + 9*x^2 + 4*x + 7$",
    "solution": "${-3 - \\frac{\\sqrt{69}}{3}, -3 + \\frac{\\sqrt{69}}{3}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $2$ numbers $[64, 59] = $",
    "solution": "$61.45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(2187)=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[18, 19, 42, 59, 60, 72, 74, 81, 89, 94]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $60.8$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $66.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $27^{5}$ and $27^{6} = $27^{5-6} = 27^{-1}$",
    "solution": "$0.037037037037037035$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $6, 16 21 = $",
    "solution": "$30.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13 * \\begin{bmatrix} 2 & 4 \\\\ 0 & 7 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 26 & 52 \\\\ 0 & 91 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -3/6x - 7$ and $y = 1/4x - 4$",
    "solution": "$(-4, -5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[1, 3, 6, 12, 26, 28, 37, 73, 90, 91]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $36.7$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $27.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[12, -6, 9] \\times [-2, -20, 20] = $",
    "solution": "$[60, -258, -252]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $37, 24, 15, 21, 8, 42, 23, 32, 29, 8, 21, 46, 43, 44, 40$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $28.866666666666667$, Standard Deviation is $155.98222222222222$, Variance is $12.48928429583626$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $14$ objects picked $8$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$3003$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$26\\div23=$",
    "solution": "$1.13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 570$ and $SP = 595$ is: ",
    "solution": "$4.39$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $3$ sides?",
    "solution": "$180$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[254, 269, 212, 223, 232, 261, 230, 211, 291, 201, 216, 268, 235, 208, 224, 259, 236, 275, 206, 233]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(246.57548985786875, 227.82451014213123)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $238$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$4.15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $2.75$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$157.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$000010 = $",
    "solution": "$111101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x + 5 = 8$",
    "solution": "$1/2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(410226425,261112953)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2027 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2027 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $9 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$1526.814 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1993 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1993 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $9$ sided polygon with lengths of $99, 42, 53, 3, 71, 45, 9, 24, 45$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$391$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $52x^2+190x+71=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.42, -3.23}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 91 & 53 \\\\ 11 & 83 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$6970$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 6/5x + 10$ and $y = 2x - 10$",
    "solution": "$(25, 40)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $96^{\\frac{1}{6}}$ _ $57^{\\frac{1}{2}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cos)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\sin$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $96$% of $60$?",
    "solution": "$57.60$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $75 = $",
    "solution": "$471.24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{576}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$8.32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5\\div52=$",
    "solution": "$0.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $67$ and $30 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $26x^2+97x+65=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.88, -2.86}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1000 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $9x - 7y = -61$ and $-3x + 7y = 25$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -6$, $y = 1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{7} + 9x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{10}{7}x^{8} + \\frac{9}{9}x^{10} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $19m, 12m, 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$912 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 40m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$3141 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $8$ and $2 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $9609$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $1$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$672.63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $4402$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$3521.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $7$ sides",
    "solution": "$128.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-87-33|=$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 16m$, base width $= 12m$, and height $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$384 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $91=$",
    "solution": "$26015.53$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $118 , 25, 183 =$",
    "solution": "$34$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 36 & -92 & 13 & 53 & 94 & 29 & -73 & -10 \\\\ -4 & 60 & 9 & -14 & -38 & -25 & -73 & -28 \\\\ 91 & 31 & -19 & 77 & 62 & -37 & 87 & 25 \\\\ -93 & -90 & -26 & 77 & 44 & 81 & -4 & 17 \\\\ -89 & 0 & 0 & 87 & -61 & -76 & -60 & 87 \\\\ -45 & 77 & -21 & 32 & -88 & -62 & -3 & -50 \\\\ -45 & 37 & -91 & 37 & 15 & 7 & 21 & -38 \\\\ 21 & 23 & -98 & -10 & -21 & -66 & -86 & 70 \\\\ 68 & -69 & 81 & -77 & 81 & 80 & -8 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -64 & 19 & 1 & 41 & -94 \\\\ -45 & -30 & -28 & 56 & 60 \\\\ -39 & 46 & 87 & -8 & 61 \\\\ 79 & 77 & -44 & 72 & 30 \\\\ -51 & -74 & -57 & -93 & -50 \\\\ 74 & 100 & -94 & 11 & -49 \\\\ -48 & 53 & -15 & 90 & -27 \\\\ -41 & 1 & -43 & -72 & -24 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6782 & 188 & -5148 & -14237 & -10431 \\\\ 839 & -6125 & 6530 & 821 & 9873 \\\\ -11496 & 2202 & -8254 & 11020 & -9779 \\\\ 20344 & 10315 & -14016 & -7886 & -2403 \\\\ 9369 & -1171 & 3863 & -4212 & 17282 \\\\ 4856 & -1564 & 7603 & 15771 & 17248 \\\\ 7990 & -2637 & -10820 & 6927 & 1261 \\\\ -1902 & -15103 & -3028 & -9340 & -1946 \\\\ -8480 & 2745 & 246 & -14929 & -15751 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(3)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $11$ sides",
    "solution": "$147.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-2,5)$ and $(16,-19) = $",
    "solution": "$(7.0,-7.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $9$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1260$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[7, 14, 28, 56, 112, 224]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 6th term value, sum upto 9th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $7$, common ratio is $2$ , 6th term is $224$, sum upto 9th term is $3577.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $23, 16, 37, 37, 28, 40, 31, 13, 39, 20, 13, 48, 13, 7, 32$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $26.466666666666665$, Standard Deviation is $144.38222222222223$, Variance is $12.015915371798448$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $23$ and height, $50$?",
    "solution": "$7225.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $176$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$3.07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12\\cdot0$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $8$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1080$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $16$ and angle, $238$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 66.46214$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(17, 10)$ and $(4, 12)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{173}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-7x-30$",
    "solution": "$(x-10)(x+3)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $67x^2 + 71x + 31 = $",
    "solution": "$88.8333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $8x^2 + 7x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.18, -0.695)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{17}}{2*8}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{17}}{2*8})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 20m$, base width $= 50m$, and height $= 24m$ is",
    "solution": "$1870 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3! =$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(90) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 7 & 3 \\\\ 1 & 4 & 2 \\\\ 1 & 2 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -1 & 2 \\\\ 1 & 0 & -3 \\\\ -2 & 1 & 5 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0100010$",
    "solution": "$0x22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$600 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 11m$ and radius $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$2690 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 20m$, base width $= 16m$, and height $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$640 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(0) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{3}{9}$ and $\\frac{10}{9}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $3$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$12389$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$00110111$",
    "solution": "$0x37$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$17 * \\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 1 \\\\ 4 & 0 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 17 & 17 \\\\ 68 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $15$ of the AP series: $-67, -18, 31 ... $",
    "solution": "$619$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $89$% of $83$?",
    "solution": "$73.87$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $41$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$0.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$89$ % $21 = $",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $93$",
    "solution": "$3, 31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $28, 34$ and $1$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 * \\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 4 \\\\ 4 & 7 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(17-3j) * (-2-7j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-55-113j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3522$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$3957.32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $4, 50, 86 = $",
    "solution": "$305.36746490503714$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11 * \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 7 \\\\ 2 & 8 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 77 & 77 \\\\ 22 & 88 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1908$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$477.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 38m$ and radius $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$3386 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $20$ objects picked $0$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $9$ and $20$?",
    "solution": "$21.93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1682$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$168.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-2x - 2y = 12$ and $8x + 4y = -28$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -1$, $y = -5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[250.0, 319.88]$ and $[427.85, 710.65]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.12$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $35 = $",
    "solution": "$100011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{42}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$3.48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(809092112,572093199)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $137$",
    "solution": "$137$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $15$ and $6 = $",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $8$ and $9 =$",
    "solution": "$72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13^5 =$",
    "solution": "$371293$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(846781641,396164102)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $37 = $",
    "solution": "$232.48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(7, -18)$ and $(17, 21)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{1621}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $48$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$118.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 7/3x + 2$ and $y = -2/5x - 6$",
    "solution": "$(-120/41, -198/41)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$3x^{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-7,-5)$ and $(-12,-19) = $",
    "solution": "$(-9.5,-12.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 24m$, base width $= 30m$, and height $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$1854 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$15.3(15.0\\theta + i-3.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-0.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $10$ and height, $63$?",
    "solution": "$3958.41$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{10}{8}\\div\\frac{7}{1}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{28}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-77-45|=$",
    "solution": "$122$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$DCCCLXXXII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $6 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$452.389 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & -18 & -30 & 34 & -74 \\\\ 10 & 93 & -81 & 64 & 74 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -71 & 0 & -44 & 19 & 38 & 94 \\\\ -24 & -84 & 40 & 97 & -43 & 98 \\\\ -29 & -73 & 95 & 11 & 64 & 85 \\\\ 84 & 24 & 1 & 33 & -52 & 31 \\\\ 19 & -84 & 98 & -44 & -22 & -34 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 2397 & 10734 & -11008 & 2397 & -1096 & -274 \\\\ 6189 & -6579 & 2901 & 7176 & -13759 & 2637 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $602$ from base $16$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$1538$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x + 5 = 5$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(60) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$87$ % $14 = $",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(2-16j) * (4+6j) = $",
    "solution": "$(104-52j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 34m$ and radius $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$1744 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 9 m$, base width $= 10 m$ and height $= 16 m$ is",
    "solution": "$480.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{144}=$",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{8}\\cdot\\frac{5}{7}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $92 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$1630880.333 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cot)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $7531$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$8718.07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $36$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$0.63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $11$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1620$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $68=$",
    "solution": "$14526.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10010 = $",
    "solution": "$01101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $26$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 35th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$9227465$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$4536.459791783661 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $20$ objects picked $0$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2043 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2043 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{945}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $61=$",
    "solution": "$11689.87$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$19.24(-17.0\\theta + i-9.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.65$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMCMXC$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = x + 7$ and $y = 5/3x + 4$",
    "solution": "$(9/2, 23/2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $54x^2+132x+66=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.7, -1.74}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(2187)=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11110 = $",
    "solution": "$00001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $82$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x + 10 = 10$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $9$ sides",
    "solution": "$140.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 5th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $24 , 107, 103 =$",
    "solution": "$126$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $28$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $782 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 17, 23, 34, 46, 391, 782]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\tan)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $39$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 110 =",
    "solution": 70
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $24$ of the AP series: $-59, -103, -147 ... $",
    "solution": "$-1071$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cot)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $13, 23$ and $3$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $55 m = $",
    "solution": "$696909.9703213357 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $38.29$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $16$ pistons will contain no more than $7$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$76.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $13$ and $1 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 954$ and $SP = 878$ is: ",
    "solution": "$7.97$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 8/3x - 6$ and $y = -10/4x$",
    "solution": "$(36/31, -90/31)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-17-13j) * (5+17j) = $",
    "solution": "$(136-354j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $9.75 \\times 10^{47}$ and $4.41 \\times 10^{-57} = $",
    "solution": "$4.3 \\times 10^{-9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$00001$",
    "solution": "$0x1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(7,-3)$ and passing through $(-1.0, -3.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$201.06$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $8273 = $",
    "solution": "$2051$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 16 & 21 & 53 & -66 & 44 & -33 \\\\ -99 & -62 & 99 & 42 & -94 & 50 \\\\ -90 & -56 & -53 & -23 & 71 & 28 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 31 & -34 & -12 & 23 & 100 & -14 \\\\ 21 & 39 & 7 & 54 & -55 & -46 \\\\ 5 & 64 & 50 & 80 & -54 & 16 \\\\ 66 & 97 & -5 & 21 & 19 & -43 \\\\ -87 & 0 & 82 & 19 & 75 & -3 \\\\ 92 & -43 & 96 & 10 & 7 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -10018 & -1316 & 3375 & 4862 & -602 & 2232 \\\\ 11674 & 9208 & 2586 & 1891 & -17738 & 4498 \\\\ -9350 & -5951 & 6663 & -8188 & 2026 & 3876 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $4$ and $7$?",
    "solution": "$8.06$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $1.29$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$73.91$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o5227$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(1,1)$ and $(8,-15) = $",
    "solution": "$(4.5,-7.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(16,-13)$ and $(-18,16) = $",
    "solution": "$(-1.0,1.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$15.03(1.0\\theta + i15.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$1.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $21 = $",
    "solution": "$10101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $41x^2+180x+46=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.27, -4.12}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $58=$",
    "solution": "$10568.32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MDCCCXIV$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[16, 18, 30, 46, 47, 52, 55, 68, 81, 84]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $49.7$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $49.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $8.43 \\times 10^{-29}$ and $4.44 \\times 10^{-51} = $",
    "solution": "$3.74 \\times 10^{-79}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$216 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-16,-6)$ and $(16,16)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$16y = 11x + 80$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $16$ objects picked $6$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$8008$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $44^{\\frac{1}{6}}$ _ $90^{\\frac{1}{8}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$22.83(-11.0\\theta + i20.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$2.07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 22 & 46 \\\\ 38 & 18 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-1352$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $4m, 10m, 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$388 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $8$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1080$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 31m$ and radius $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$3593 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 6 m$, base width $= 10 m$ and height $= 48 m$ is",
    "solution": "$960.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $15^{4}$ and $41^{4} = (15/41)^4 = 0.36585365853658536^{4}$",
    "solution": "$0.017915527887885776$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $55, 96, 5 = $",
    "solution": "$21.87241093620547$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$314.1592653589793 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $21^{7}$ and $21^{4} = $21^{7-4} = 21^{3}$",
    "solution": "$9261$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 47m$ and $r1 = 11m$ is and $r2 = 11m$ is ",
    "solution": "$8022.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 8m$ and radius $= 1m$ is",
    "solution": "$56 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(30) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $3$ numbers $[55, 91, 38] = $",
    "solution": "$57.51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $5$ sided polygon with lengths of $90, 92, 24, 62, 80$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$348$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $86x^2+175x+85=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.8, -1.23}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 4m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$1840 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $2.64$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$151.26$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $151$ and $190$?",
    "solution": "$22.87$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 952$ and $SP = 949$ is: ",
    "solution": "$0.32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$47+31=$",
    "solution": "$78$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $8.89 \\times 10^{69}$ and $7.89 \\times 10^{70} = $",
    "solution": "$7.01 \\times 10^{140}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $18$ and $66 = $",
    "solution": "$96$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[4, 15, 3] \\times [-15, 10, -15] = $",
    "solution": "$[-255, 15, 265]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[8, 72, 648, 5832, 52488, 472392]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 10th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $8$, common ratio is $9$ , 10th term is $3099363912$, sum upto 10th term is $3486784400.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = x - 5$ and $y = 2/5x - 9$",
    "solution": "$(-20/3, -35/3)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o6674$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{1}{8}\\div\\frac{9}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2031 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2031 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $20m$ is",
    "solution": "$8000 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $12$ and $25 = $",
    "solution": "$143$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-1x-90$",
    "solution": "$(x-10)(x+9)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $6$ and $4 =$",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[941.4178260640086, 780.3001793214911, 325.03387260640994, 763.0130146285705, 304.09354715001, 638.5031349427936, 588.2191753238188, 301.9543856666338, 843.9761777430176, 946.727235879521, 118.61371728837489, 601.8476257014464, 790.9549701549354, 315.75605818323936, 338.26643550604206]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2438.22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $54 , 61, 32 =$",
    "solution": "$213$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10\\cdot5$",
    "solution": "$50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 13 =",
    "solution": 77
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$CLXXXIX$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$20.62(-5.0\\theta + i20.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$1.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0100111$",
    "solution": "$39$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1912 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1912 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+5x+6$",
    "solution": "$(x+3)(x+2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $30, 19, 17, 35, 25, 36, 15, 33, 45, 46, 50, 10, 34, 16, 22$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $28.866666666666667$, Standard Deviation is $143.1822222222222$, Variance is $11.965877411298438$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $0.87$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$49.85$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233, 377$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$17.0(-15.0\\theta + i-8.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.65$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $31^{9^{2}}$",
    "solution": "$31^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{5}\\cdot\\frac{1}{9}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{7}{45}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $19$% of $25$?",
    "solution": "$4.75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 30m$ and $r1 = 13m$ is and $r2 = 13m$ is ",
    "solution": "$24410.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[52.49, 614.96, 968.59, 922.0, 406.6, 651.44, 765.39, 45.22, 309.3, 41.98, 575.54, 667.06, 23.24]$ and $[701.22, 691.95, 552.88, 516.47, 333.7, 628.89, 60.14, 887.72, 765.86, 955.92, 273.52, 949.08, 580.73]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.86$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $24$ and height, $67$?",
    "solution": "$10103.36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $122$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 54th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$86267571272$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1967 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1967 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $63 = $",
    "solution": "$111111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=10*x^2 + 6*x + 4$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{3}{10}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $24 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$28952.918 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[203, 207, 297, 212, 277, 259, 282, 239, 209, 271, 213, 243, 253, 217, 285, 200, 245, 286, 296, 214, 272, 276, 216, 248, 273, 279, 231, 262, 274, 289, 251, 227, 237, 204, 211, 232, 291]$ with $80$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(254.64191927915488, 241.62835099111538)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $12$ and $26 = $",
    "solution": "$142$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$000$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $702$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$11$ hours and $42$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $14$ and height, $25$?",
    "solution": "$2199.11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $72$% of $66$?",
    "solution": "$47.52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $129$",
    "solution": "$3, 43$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $44^{8}$ and $41^{8} = (44/41)^8 = 1.0731707317073171^{8}$",
    "solution": "$1.7593431650408164$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $19$ and $8 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $126$",
    "solution": "$2, 3, 3, 7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $5$ sides?",
    "solution": "$540$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=3*x^2 + 9*x + 10$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{3}{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 14m$ and $r1 = 5m$ is and $r2 = 5m$ is ",
    "solution": "$2946.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $20$ and $2 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $67 m = $",
    "solution": "$1259833.1083621692 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $53x^2 + 92x + 15 = $",
    "solution": "$78.6667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-5, 1, -11] \\times [-4, 17, 16] = $",
    "solution": "$[203, 124, -81]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(12+12j) * (5+8j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-36+156j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$47$ % $14 = $",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $79$",
    "solution": "$79$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1100 = $",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $4=$",
    "solution": "$50.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $31$ and angle $179$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$1501.15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(316792683,237770438)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $6 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{5}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $40^{6}$ and $40^{10} = $40^{6-10} = 40^{-4}$",
    "solution": "$3.90625e-07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(16, 1)$ and $(21, -14)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{250}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $56 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$367809.29 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $86$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$186.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(17,3)$ and $(20,9) = $",
    "solution": "$(18.5,6.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$14-7=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $8$ sided polygon with lengths of $105, 106, 7, 36, 64, 103, 102, 101$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$624$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -104 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cos)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\sin$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $111$ and $187$?",
    "solution": "$51.01$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $3072$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1843.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-14x+48$",
    "solution": "$(x-6)(x-8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $3x^2 + 9x + 5 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.736, -2.264)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{21}}{2*3}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{21}}{2*3})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $2.05 \\times 10^{-54}$ and $8.5 \\times 10^{-69} = $",
    "solution": "$1.74 \\times 10^{-122}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $4.57$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$261.84$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{2}{10}\\div\\frac{7}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{35}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $84x^2 + 65x + 3 = $",
    "solution": "$63.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{9}{4}\\div\\frac{10}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{10}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[246, 203, 242, 288, 299, 277, 258, 236, 226, 211, 268, 273, 216, 218, 229, 224, 223, 262, 255, 289, 261, 213, 294, 254, 230, 291, 295, 274, 227, 243, 219, 238, 225, 263, 250, 249]$ with $80$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(254.92109665399065, 243.35668112378713)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 4/6x - 2$ and $y = -4/3x - 9$",
    "solution": "$(-7/2, -13/3)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 49th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$7778742049$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $347 = $",
    "solution": "$0x15b$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $51 = $",
    "solution": "$110011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.84\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=91.23$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=98.42\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$51.98$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $2x^2+177x+45=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.25, -88.25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1001 = $",
    "solution": "$111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$238\\div14=$",
    "solution": "$17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $18m$ is",
    "solution": "$5832 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{6} + 1x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$18x^{5} + 10x^{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $28$% of $38$?",
    "solution": "$10.64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $8.74 \\times 10^{-20}$ and $2.99 \\times 10^{12} = $",
    "solution": "$2.61 \\times 10^{-7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $-26$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$-14.800000000000004$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(64)=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 27 =",
    "solution": 153
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $20$ objects picked $0$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$00100110$",
    "solution": "$38$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 112 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$37-9=$",
    "solution": "$28$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $29^{6}$ and $29^{3} = $29^{6-3} = 29^{3}$",
    "solution": "$24389$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$113.09733552923255 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $10 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{3}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $43$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$109.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 35m$ and radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$13231 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $20$ sides",
    "solution": "$162.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 43m$ and radius $= 1m$ is",
    "solution": "$276 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $1215 = $",
    "solution": "$41115$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $28 m = $",
    "solution": "$91952.32257547084 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$150 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-15-3j) * (10-13j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-189+165j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -224 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $76$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$22$ % $72 = $",
    "solution": "$22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $16 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{6}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={9, 10, 5, 1}$, $b={8, 3, 6}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 3, 5, 6, 8, 9, 10}$. Intersection is $set()$, a-b is ${9, 10, 5, 1}$, b-a is ${8, 3, 6}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 3, 5, 6, 8, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-17-8j) * (16+13j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-168-349j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $47^{1^{10}}$",
    "solution": "$47^{10}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-21--93|=$",
    "solution": "$72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-5,-2)$ and passing through $(-0.13999999999999968, 5.57)$ is",
    "solution": "$254.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x + 5 = 7$",
    "solution": "$1/4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13^8 =$",
    "solution": "$815730721$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{7}\\cdot\\frac{1}{2}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $20$",
    "solution": "$2, 2, 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$71\\div88=$",
    "solution": "$0.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $858$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$14$ hours and $18$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $17$ and height, $29$?",
    "solution": "$3097.61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(45) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $8, 9$ and $29$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $1AA13$ from base $13$ to base $8$.",
    "solution": "$146015$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-18, -19, -18]\\cdot[-14, 19, -13]=$",
    "solution": "$125$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $92x^2 + 16x + 75 = $",
    "solution": "$113.6667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[12, 36, 108, 324, 972, 2916]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 6th term value, sum upto 7th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $12$, common ratio is $3$ , 6th term is $2916$, sum upto 7th term is $13116.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1100110 = $",
    "solution": "$11010$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $6458$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $6$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$387.48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $7x^2 + 7x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.173, -0.827)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{21}}{2*7}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{21}}{2*7})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 4 m$, base width $= 3 m$ and height $= 39 m$ is",
    "solution": "$156.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $645 = $",
    "solution": "$0x285$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $37$ and angle, $122$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 78.78416$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $256625$ from base $7$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$47990$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$72$ % $29 = $",
    "solution": "$14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $4x^2 + 8x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.293, -1.707)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{32}}{2*4}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{32}}{2*4})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$20^2=$",
    "solution": "$400$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $13$ sides",
    "solution": "$152.31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $60$% of $80$?",
    "solution": "$48.00$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $8667$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $6$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$15354.12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $27$ terms of the AP series: $-91, 2, 95 ... $",
    "solution": "$30186.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $17, 39, 12, 8, 35, 20, 11, 44, 11, 29, 45, 49, 35, 35, 27$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $27.8$, Standard Deviation is $178.29333333333338$, Variance is $13.352652670287405$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o161$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x + 7 = 7$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $59$ and exact value equals $37$.",
    "solution": "$59.46\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$17^2=$",
    "solution": "$289$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $4m, 10m, 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$640 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 85th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$259695496911123328$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=7*x^3 + 10*x^2 + 2*x + 7$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{10}{21} - \\frac{\\sqrt{58}}{21}, - \\frac{10}{21} + \\frac{\\sqrt{58}}{21}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $6$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $70$ and $76 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $50x^2+159x+60=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.44, -2.74}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$16.12(2.0\\theta + i-16.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-1.45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $35.7$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $15$ pistons will contain no more than $5$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$54.14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-10,-11)$ and $(-2,-10)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$8y = x -78$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $9$ sided polygon with lengths of $37, 64, 6, 81, 30, 27, 35, 13, 1$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$294$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $100$ and $45 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 5]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $68$ terms of the AP series: $7, 51, 95 ... $",
    "solution": "$100708.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[10, 23, 48, 52, 54, 58, 59, 63, 66, 97]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $53.0$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $56.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $8046$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$7241.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $165$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$2.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MCLXVI$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 7}$, $b={9, 2, 3, 5}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 9}$. Intersection is $set()$, a-b is ${1, 7}$, b-a is ${9, 2, 3, 5}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 9}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(x-4)(4x+5)$",
    "solution": "$4x^2-11x-20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $27^{7}$ and $26^{7} = (27/26)^7 = 1.0384615384615385^{7}$",
    "solution": "$1.302365590543559$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $29, 30$ and $2$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233, 377, 610, 987, 1597, 2584, 4181$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $3$ and height, $36$?",
    "solution": "$678.58$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $10$ and $20 =$",
    "solution": "$20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233, 377, 610, 987, 1597, 2584, 4181$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$2123.7166338267 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $377$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$6$ hours and $17$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|15-21|=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[375.80736570475557, 251.48902976356814, 877.5096081659558, 114.71214662593643, 309.9383038684569, 651.9104451357158, 25.889101817327955, 991.5268277491808, 191.56234141443906, 792.9593688703021, 865.8420689818568, 823.0980983959948, 736.5681845805548, 655.6066960054006, 741.2932821989127, 74.46251982916951]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2472.36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $17$ sides",
    "solution": "$158.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 * \\begin{bmatrix} 10 & 9 \\\\ 8 & 9 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -99 & 8 & 19 & -96 & 23 & -96 & -40 \\\\ 89 & 20 & -61 & -54 & 10 & 29 & 90 \\\\ 77 & -1 & 60 & -100 & -67 & 26 & 12 \\\\ -54 & 12 & -38 & -72 & -75 & -44 & 29 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -78 & 45 & 6 \\\\ -18 & 41 & -37 \\\\ -55 & 65 & 15 \\\\ -31 & -26 & 81 \\\\ -21 & 40 & -35 \\\\ 57 & 95 & -15 \\\\ 38 & -81 & -69 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 2034 & -5356 & -4986 \\\\ 2590 & -1871 & -12490 \\\\ -2843 & 8742 & -5574 \\\\ 8487 & -12065 & -5886 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{9}{8}\\div\\frac{8}{9}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{81}{64}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $6$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$24841$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $42, 48$ and $18$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 6m$, base width $= 24m$, and height $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$480 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $5m, 14m, 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$482 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{4}=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$89-19=$",
    "solution": "$70$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\tan(45) = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $209$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $20$ and $19 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $20$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$68.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $32$ and angle $45$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$402.12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(1,-5)$ and passing through $(-0.96, -7.27)$ is",
    "solution": "$28.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[1, 4, 11, 22, 38, 44, 66, 69, 81, 97]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $43.3$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $41.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$201.06192982974676 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{7} + 4x^{9} + 1x^{1} + 4x^{10} + 4x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{6} + 36x^{8} + 1x^{0} + 40x^{9} + 16x^{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^3 + 5*x^2 + 10$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{10}{3}, 0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10100100 = $",
    "solution": "$01011011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $49$ and height, $24$?",
    "solution": "$7389.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $4$ and height, $68$?",
    "solution": "$1709.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $307$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$5.36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $34$% of $86$?",
    "solution": "$29.24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $3^{7}$ and $23^{7} = (3/23)^7 = 0.13043478260869565^{7}$",
    "solution": "$6.42323676806096e-07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $913$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$15$ hours and $13$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.16\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=91.48$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=92.84\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$13.04$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 761 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $7, 19 23 = $",
    "solution": "$59.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[13, 7, -17] \\times [-4, 20, 2] = $",
    "solution": "$[354, 42, 288]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $18m, 18m, 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$2088 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $6$ and $9$?",
    "solution": "$10.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $20$ sides",
    "solution": "$162.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-9,8)$ and passing through $(-2.0, 8.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$153.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 65 & 28 \\\\ 92 & 28 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-756$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 9m$ and radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$503 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-3,-2)$ and passing through $(-7.58, -7.3)$ is",
    "solution": "$153.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{36}=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o6271$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$102\\div17=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[294.14, 709.53, 55.48, 135.92, 748.75, 555.01, 652.4]$ and $[146.31, 72.55, 825.03, 584.1, 586.58, 944.27, 969.81]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.75$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $38$ and height, $90$?",
    "solution": "$21488.49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $7$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$44.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[3, 4, 28, 47, 48, 52, 60, 70, 96, 98]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $50.6$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $50.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.67\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=92.81$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=90.33\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$14.02$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(20,15)$ and $(-6,-5) = $",
    "solution": "$(7.0,5.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 134$ and $SP = 230$ is: ",
    "solution": "$71.64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{222}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$6.06$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $28$ and exact value equals $94$.",
    "solution": "$70.21\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{9}{3}\\cdot\\frac{7}{10}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{21}{10}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $8145$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$488.7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x + 2 = 10$",
    "solution": "$4/5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5! =$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-8,18)$ and $(-15,-2) = $",
    "solution": "$(-11.5,8.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-13, 8)$ and $(-7, 0)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{100}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(599275247,706118164)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1111000000$",
    "solution": "$960$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[9, -19, -7]\\cdot[-3, -1, 9]=$",
    "solution": "$-71$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -634 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-5,-10)$ and passing through $(-9.58, -15.3)$ is",
    "solution": "$153.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $906$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$15$ hours and $6$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{340}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$6.98$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{358}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$7.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 3m$ and radius $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$774 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 16m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1675 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $881 = $",
    "solution": "$0x371$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $96$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $28^{\\frac{1}{1}}$ _ $94^{\\frac{1}{5}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-13,-9)$ and $(-5,4) = $",
    "solution": "$(-9.0,-2.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $19, 32, 22, 9, 42, 34, 27, 40, 33, 26, 42, 49, 5, 41, 36$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $30.466666666666665$, Standard Deviation is $147.18222222222224$, Variance is $12.131868043389783$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $19^{\\frac{1}{1}}$ _ $72^{\\frac{1}{7}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13^6 =$",
    "solution": "$4826809$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(128)=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $95 = $",
    "solution": "$1011111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x + 8 = 8$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=7*x^2 + 7*x + 1$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{1}{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $37$ terms of the AP series: $-74, -56, -38 ... $",
    "solution": "$9250.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $88$% of $92$?",
    "solution": "$80.96$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $93$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 3]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.44\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=90.04$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=98.54\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$21.42$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$14^7 =$",
    "solution": "$105413504$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 158 =",
    "solution": 22
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $17^{9}$ and $35^{9} = (17/35)^9 = 0.4857142857142857^{9}$",
    "solution": "$0.0015046236824991627$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $2m, 11m, 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$220 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $35 = $",
    "solution": "$100011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$001$",
    "solution": "$0x1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8^2=$",
    "solution": "$64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{5}{4}$ and $\\frac{3}{2}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-5x + 15y = 295$ and $6x + 19y = 201$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -14$, $y = 15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x + 9 = 10$",
    "solution": "$1/10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $13$ and $13 = $",
    "solution": "$13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $0$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$32.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $40.69$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $14$ pistons will contain no more than $3$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$11.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $48 m = $",
    "solution": "$463246.6863277365 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[767.4454351920903, 30.05413829189807, 144.89894839797267, 253.8699525364001, 17.394401837785512, 861.0797381588782, 689.5886715267604]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1375.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-57--69|=$",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $712 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4, 8, 89, 178, 356, 712]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMXXXII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1\\div12=$",
    "solution": "$0.08$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x + 2 = 2$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $19, 13 23 = $",
    "solution": "$123.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $1$ and height, $55$?",
    "solution": "$345.58$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$18.03(-18.0\\theta + i-1.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-3.09$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 6m$ and radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$25 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3! =$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$110100 = $",
    "solution": "$001011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[2, 24, 288, 3456, 41472, 497664]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 6th term value, sum upto 7th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $2$, common ratio is $12$ , 6th term is $497664$, sum upto 7th term is $6514874.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(30) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 29m$ and radius $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$11023 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$20.59(-10.0\\theta + i-18.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.08$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -27 & -18 & -31 & 72 & -48 & 84 & -88 & -38 & 66 \\\\ -83 & 21 & 88 & -62 & -20 & 51 & -81 & 65 & 85 \\\\ -30 & 79 & 99 & -7 & 55 & 8 & -49 & -36 & -77 \\\\ -14 & 34 & 86 & -53 & -79 & -82 & 13 & 4 & -69 \\\\ 72 & 46 & -92 & 97 & -67 & -34 & -52 & -55 & 56 \\\\ -18 & -73 & 13 & 1 & -13 & 4 & -39 & 15 & 67 \\\\ -10 & 64 & 7 & -97 & -28 & 58 & 62 & -45 & -40 \\\\ 21 & -81 & 16 & -95 & 2 & 27 & -65 & 1 & 98 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -94 & -76 & -72 & 63 \\\\ -68 & -5 & -97 & 36 \\\\ 21 & -94 & -25 & 93 \\\\ 44 & 5 & 21 & 52 \\\\ -8 & -64 & -71 & 91 \\\\ -59 & 13 & -15 & -22 \\\\ 90 & -72 & 71 & 74 \\\\ 11 & 92 & -32 & 10 \\\\ 44 & -90 & 7 & -21 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -3727 & 6480 & 3555 & -15982 \\\\ -190 & 3726 & -6144 & -9584 \\\\ -9887 & -3726 & -15016 & 12257 \\\\ 2126 & 2177 & 1598 & 2650 \\\\ -7839 & 921 & -1582 & -8243 \\\\ 6444 & -442 & 6156 & -7915 \\\\ -7406 & -3161 & -1020 & -1565 \\\\ -3446 & -6995 & -558 & -12315 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $83$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$1.45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$5026.548245743669 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $19, 11 26 = $",
    "solution": "$92.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-10x + 7y = -223$ and $18x + 9y = -9$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 9$, $y = -19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\tan(0) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $46^{2}$ and $26^{2} = (46/26)^2 = 1.7692307692307692^{2}$",
    "solution": "$3.130177514792899$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $10$ objects picked $3$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $41$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$105.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $56=$",
    "solution": "$9852.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(20,-1)$ and $(6,6) = $",
    "solution": "$(13.0,2.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[9, 15, 21, 36, 65, 70, 73, 77, 86, 95]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $54.7$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $67.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$79-69=$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{4}{10}$ and $\\frac{7}{2}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $7$ sided polygon with lengths of $54, 20, 34, 71, 113, 36, 36$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$364$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $1804$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$2065.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $902 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 11, 22, 41, 82, 451, 902]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $4207$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$6181.46$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $76$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$168.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x + 7 = 7$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 13m$ and radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$95 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 40m$, base width $= 32m$, and height $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$2560 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $2$ numbers $[1, 8] = $",
    "solution": "$2.83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9336$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$18602.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $9x + 8y = -116$ and $3x + 2y = -32$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -4$, $y = -10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 52 =",
    "solution": 128
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[1, 19, -2] \\times [-20, -20, -13] = $",
    "solution": "$[-287, 53, 360]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13^3 =$",
    "solution": "$2197$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-11, 7, -10]\\cdot[9, 11, -7]=$",
    "solution": "$48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$19^2=$",
    "solution": "$361$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $96x^2 + 91x + 47 = $",
    "solution": "$124.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(14,-20)$ and $(10,-18)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$2y = -x -26$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $173$ composite?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(0, -7)$ and $(7, 20)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{778}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(0) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 11m$ and radius $= 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$933 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$14x^{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $88^{\\frac{1}{1}}$ _ $33^{\\frac{1}{5}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5! =$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $71$ and $85 = $",
    "solution": "$24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $741 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 3, 13, 19, 39, 57, 247, 741]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-9x-6)(-2x+8)$",
    "solution": "$18x^2-60x-48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{6} + 6x^{4} + 7x^{17}$",
    "solution": "$6x^{4} + 8x^{6} + 7x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[200, 268, 243, 263, 239, 260, 252, 269, 213, 265, 271, 266, 280, 248, 249, 289, 228, 234, 299, 211, 262, 291, 214, 218, 251, 282, 273, 210, 258, 287, 222, 294, 233]$ with $95$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(262.08289085934416, 243.49286671641337)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $96 = $",
    "solution": "$1100000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-1$",
    "solution": "$(x+1)(x-1)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $2.13 \\times 10^{-57}$ and $1.43 \\times 10^{30} = $",
    "solution": "$3.05 \\times 10^{-27}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $5576 = $",
    "solution": "$15128$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 48th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$4807526976$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMLXXVIII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 48m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$5026 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $6=$",
    "solution": "$113.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 35th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$9227465$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{282}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$6.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $22$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $72$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(6561)=$",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1 * \\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 0 \\\\ 9 & 1 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 0 \\\\ 9 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-36$",
    "solution": "$(x-6)(x+6)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -505 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{5} + 8x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$35x^{4} + 72x^{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1\\cdot11$",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 15m$ and radius $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1176 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 1 & 0 \\\\ 5 & 1 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -1 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 0 \\\\ 4 & 1 & -5 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $4848$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$2181.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=9*x^3 + 8*x^2 + x + 5$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{8}{27} - \\frac{\\sqrt{37}}{27}, - \\frac{8}{27} + \\frac{\\sqrt{37}}{27}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{6}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{7}{6}x^{7} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $30=$",
    "solution": "$2827.43$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 734$ and $SP = 590$ is: ",
    "solution": "$19.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $11x + 3y = -140$ and $4x + 10y = 56$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -16$, $y = 12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $94 = $",
    "solution": "$1011110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $48 = $",
    "solution": "$301.59$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.95\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=96.95$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=92.86\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$11.52$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $44$ and $73 = $",
    "solution": "$63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $86$ terms of the AP series: $80, 134, 188 ... $",
    "solution": "$204250.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1360$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1224.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$24.08(18.0\\theta + i-16.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-0.73$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $100100001011101$ from base $2$ to base $16$.",
    "solution": "$485D$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $4$ sided polygon with lengths of $49, 52, 120, 38$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$259$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{7}$",
    "solution": "$2x^{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(4)=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 257 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-6, -19)$ and $(17, 1)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{929}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $56 = $",
    "solution": "$351.86$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1987 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1987 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $4$ sides",
    "solution": "$90.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$60\\div99=$",
    "solution": "$0.61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 19th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$4181$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0\\div87=$",
    "solution": "$0.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 39m$ and $r1 = 13m$ is and $r2 = 13m$ is ",
    "solution": "$12619.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $5m$ is",
    "solution": "$125 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[4, 14, 17, 28, 43, 56, 59, 66, 79, 95]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $46.1$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $49.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $8.55 \\times 10^{-86}$ and $2.81 \\times 10^{-13} = $",
    "solution": "$2.4 \\times 10^{-98}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 781 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $51$ of the AP series: $-95, -57, -19 ... $",
    "solution": "$1805$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$306\\div17=$",
    "solution": "$18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $19^{\\frac{1}{8}}$ _ $31^{\\frac{1}{5}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $716 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4, 179, 358, 716]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $23^{5}$ and $23^{3} = $23^{5-3} = 23^{2}$",
    "solution": "$529$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $7$ sided polygon with lengths of $87, 84, 69, 11, 17, 73, 57$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$398$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $9m, 8m, 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$144 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-3, -20)$ and $(0, -12)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{73}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -67 & 42 \\\\ 20 & -81 \\\\ 93 & 97 \\\\ 46 & -81 \\\\ 92 & 60 \\\\ 51 & 83 \\\\ 94 & -57 \\\\ 4 & -88 \\\\ -87 & 51 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -88 & 80 & 7 \\\\ 59 & 43 & -51 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 8374 & -3554 & -2611 \\\\ -6539 & -1883 & 4271 \\\\ -2461 & 11611 & -4296 \\\\ -8827 & 197 & 4453 \\\\ -4556 & 9940 & -2416 \\\\ 409 & 7649 & -3876 \\\\ -11635 & 5069 & 3565 \\\\ -5544 & -3464 & 4516 \\\\ 10665 & -4767 & -3210 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-16,6)$ and $(20,19)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$36y = 13x + 424$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $57$ of the AP series: $100, 164, 228 ... $",
    "solution": "$3684$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-12, -6)$ and $(-16, -10)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{32}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $28x^2+128x+39=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.33, -4.24}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11^6 =$",
    "solution": "$1771561$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={2, 10, 3}$, $b={9, 2, 5}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${2, 3, 5, 9, 10}$. Intersection is ${2}$, a-b is ${10, 3}$, b-a is ${9, 5}$. Symmetric difference is ${9, 10, 3, 5}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 6m$, base width $= 8m$, and height $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$96 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8 * \\begin{bmatrix} 9 & 0 \\\\ 2 & 10 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 72 & 0 \\\\ 16 & 80 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $98$ and $137$?",
    "solution": "$33.19$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $36$ and $30 = $",
    "solution": "$114$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $15m, 12m, 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$2700 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-10+17j) * (7-2j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-36+139j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0110110$",
    "solution": "$0x36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $33, 10$ and $4$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $69$% of $25$?",
    "solution": "$17.25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMCCCXXXIII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $77x^2+171x+84=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.73, -1.49}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$01011111$",
    "solution": "$95$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $77$ of the AP series: $-72, -33, 6 ... $",
    "solution": "$2892$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13^2=$",
    "solution": "$169$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{7}\\div\\frac{6}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{32}{21}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $11$ and $15 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1989 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1989 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $28$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $6, 20 18 = $",
    "solution": "$53.07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $22^{7}$ and $12^{7} = (22/12)^7 = 1.8333333333333333^{7}$",
    "solution": "$69.61295081732966$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $129$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$2.25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$150 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $13m$ is",
    "solution": "$2197 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $54x^2+158x+17=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.11, -2.81}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[8, 5, 6]\\cdot[-20, 18, -20]=$",
    "solution": "$-190$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $53 m = $",
    "solution": "$623614.5193179834 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $12^{8}$ and $37^{8} = (12/37)^8 = 0.32432432432432434^{8}$",
    "solution": "$0.0001224154337814017$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $2.15$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$123.19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5! =$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $15m, 10m, 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$2550 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $8$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$33922$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-5,-6)$ and passing through $(-14.0, -6.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$254.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o477$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2^2=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{6} + 5x^{7}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{6}x^{7} + \\frac{5}{7}x^{8} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $3693 = $",
    "solution": "$14613$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $76$ of the AP series: $-93, -157, -221 ... $",
    "solution": "$-4893$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $1.62$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$92.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$28\\div4=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$31+44=$",
    "solution": "$75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x + 7 = 9$",
    "solution": "$1/3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $881 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 881]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $6.17 \\times 10^{-87}$ and $5.69 \\times 10^{-27} = $",
    "solution": "$3.51 \\times 10^{-113}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9936$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$12088.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[920.0578561648016, 882.1022026144483, 640.5032921847791, 128.88395685001163, 121.82098418496446, 683.0880370791091, 997.6572949546592, 257.9225082160097, 49.85230731098434]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1896.64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $82 = $",
    "solution": "$1010010$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $42$ and height, $51$?",
    "solution": "$13458.58$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $18$ sides",
    "solution": "$160.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $56$ and $56 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4, 7, 8, 14, 28, 56]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 42m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$1156 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $59x^2 + 25x + 50 = $",
    "solution": "$82.1667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[521.53, 874.93, 12.16, 326.92, 741.51, 330.91, 901.51, 917.02, 274.31, 477.96, 244.29, 238.76, 681.24, 406.97, 610.52, 698.28, 281.09, 7.53]$ and $[9.74, 564.55, 831.01, 661.53, 47.07, 535.29, 872.31, 79.13, 452.37, 823.18, 71.27, 23.85, 760.06, 563.59, 981.76, 355.48, 350.6, 380.65]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.76$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{64}=$",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $5$ sided polygon with lengths of $42, 45, 104, 17, 116$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$324$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $15$ and $88 = $",
    "solution": "$77$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $4.0 \\times 10^{-83}$ and $3.71 \\times 10^{93} = $",
    "solution": "$1.48 \\times 10^{11}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $10$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 44m$ and radius $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$18430 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[19, 17, 5] \\times [-11, -14, -8] = $",
    "solution": "$[-66, 97, -79]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(3-6j) * (9+12j) = $",
    "solution": "$(99-18j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -2/4x$ and $y = 5/4x - 5$",
    "solution": "$(20/7, -10/7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $7706$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$9979.49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $15 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{10}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2040 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2040 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$000$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1+2=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $10x + -1y = 60$ and $1x + 14y = -135$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 5$, $y = -10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $8$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$32769$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{18} + 3x^{10} + 5x^{6} + 2x^{5} + 8x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$8x^{1} + 2x^{5} + 5x^{6} + 3x^{10} + 3x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $2.28 \\times 10^{-41}$ and $5.77 \\times 10^{-69} = $",
    "solution": "$1.32 \\times 10^{-109}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={8, 10, 5, 6}$, $b={1, 4, 5, 6}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 4, 5, 6, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${5, 6}$, a-b is ${8, 10}$, b-a is ${1, 4}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 4, 8, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 2, 3, 4, 5}$, $b={1, 5, 6, 9}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 9}$. Intersection is ${1, 5}$, a-b is ${2, 3, 4}$, b-a is ${9, 6}$. Symmetric difference is ${2, 3, 4, 6, 9}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 58th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$591286729879$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $26 m = $",
    "solution": "$73622.1766393256 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 60 =",
    "solution": 30
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $21, 75, 80 = $",
    "solution": "$1089.1410048622367$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 1 & 0 \\\\ 3 & 1 & 0 \\\\ 3 & 1 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & -1 & 0 \\\\ -3 & 4 & 0 \\\\ 0 & -1 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $4$ sides?",
    "solution": "$360$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[190.74, 708.69, 498.02, 166.28, 965.56, 214.67, 463.82, 246.75, 570.47, 62.1, 516.41, 988.04, 981.39, 39.91, 472.94, 364.35, 672.99]$ and $[117.68, 775.99, 217.76, 325.98, 81.4, 593.05, 934.8, 131.12, 641.26, 50.57, 195.14, 258.62, 923.82, 445.69, 816.19, 954.7, 440.12]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.71$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $11^{8}$ and $13^{8} = (11/13)^8 = 0.8461538461538461^{8}$",
    "solution": "$0.2627814246559435$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $10$ objects picked $4$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$210$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0010111 = $",
    "solution": "$1101000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $73=$",
    "solution": "$16741.55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $39, 31$ and $26$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $5$ sided polygon with lengths of $79, 90, 117, 30, 8$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$324$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $22$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$71.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 30 =",
    "solution": 60
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x + 2 = 5$",
    "solution": "$3/7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $33 = $",
    "solution": "$207.35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{411}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$7.43$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $18$ and angle, $75$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 23.56194$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $42^{3}$ and $42^{5} = $42^{3-5} = 42^{-2}$",
    "solution": "$0.0005668934240362812$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-87--100|=$",
    "solution": "$13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $76$% of $66$?",
    "solution": "$50.16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $8$ and $11 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $19 = $",
    "solution": "$119.38$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $4$ and $10 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $75$% of $98$?",
    "solution": "$73.50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 13 m$, base width $= 8 m$ and height $= 42 m$ is",
    "solution": "$1456.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[642.48, 575.0, 922.99, 354.84, 475.34, 489.42, 440.95, 894.25, 810.92, 938.36, 367.28, 152.5, 889.31, 721.55, 787.66]$ and $[6.18, 636.24, 224.51, 196.78, 643.38, 808.19, 51.17, 208.53, 460.97, 326.18, 151.87, 444.81, 249.89, 561.84, 949.07]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.69$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $227 = $",
    "solution": "$0xe3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$47+28=$",
    "solution": "$75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(858705353,943276250)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(9x-4)(9x+6)$",
    "solution": "$81x^2+18x-24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$35$ % $16 = $",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $49^{5}$ and $49^{6} = $49^{5-6} = 49^{-1}$",
    "solution": "$0.02040816326530612$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $-44$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$-47.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[5, 14, -18]\\cdot[-18, 14, -12]=$",
    "solution": "$322$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $67$ and $25 = $",
    "solution": "$88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-19+9j) * (4+15j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-211-249j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x + 5 = 8$",
    "solution": "$3/10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $5x - 7y = -24$ and $4x - 9y = -43$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 5$, $y = 7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $2$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$10120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $23, 15, 28, 22, 39, 17, 48, 7, 45, 29, 26, 45, 35, 41, 38$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $30.533333333333335$, Standard Deviation is $141.18222222222224$, Variance is $11.882012549321022$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $2$ composite?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $16 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{6}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $66 m = $",
    "solution": "$1204260.4287152681 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{1}=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{9}{10}\\div\\frac{3}{6}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5736$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$7026.85$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 7 m$, base width $= 15 m$ and height $= 15 m$ is",
    "solution": "$525.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[246, 220, 247, 278, 281, 203, 270, 226, 290, 299, 284, 279, 227, 273, 241, 293, 248, 277, 294, 257, 225, 258, 261, 229, 234, 205, 215, 207, 214, 280, 292, 295]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(263.44914897396603, 245.80085102603394)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $4$ sides?",
    "solution": "$360$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{9}=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $26$ and angle, $112$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 50.82399$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $897 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 3, 13, 23, 39, 69, 299, 897]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o1276$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $5 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $6765$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$8320.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $27^{5}$ and $7^{5} = (27/7)^5 = 3.857142857142857^{5}$",
    "solution": "$853.7458796929851$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4! =$",
    "solution": "$24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1100$",
    "solution": "$0xc$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[10, 120, 1440, 17280, 207360, 2488320]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 6th term value, sum upto 7th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $10$, common ratio is $12$ , 6th term is $2488320$, sum upto 7th term is $32574370.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $10 = $",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $634 = $",
    "solution": "$0x27a$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[206, 239, 267, 261, 248, 217, 236, 234, 272, 226, 229, 249, 289, 203, 282, 259, 277, 262, 297, 275, 228, 241, 238, 265, 237, 266, 201, 246, 292, 214, 295, 284, 268, 242, 281, 290]$ with $80$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(259.03548085315816, 247.40896359128632)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7.21(-6.0\\theta + i-4.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $20 = $",
    "solution": "$10100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(3+12j) * (12-4j) = $",
    "solution": "$(84+132j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $54$ of the AP series: $-30, 49, 128 ... $",
    "solution": "$4157$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x + 7 = 9$",
    "solution": "$1/2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $54 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$329791.83 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 93 & 90 & 88 & 41 & -12 \\\\ 98 & 89 & -78 & 25 & 8 \\\\ 2 & 17 & 2 & 34 & 22 \\\\ -64 & 73 & 63 & -85 & -69 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 86 & -61 & -40 & 64 & 3 & -79 \\\\ -14 & 4 & 62 & -86 & -29 & 44 \\\\ -45 & -58 & 90 & 92 & -53 & 91 \\\\ 65 & 55 & -47 & -16 & 26 & -30 \\\\ 79 & -68 & -83 & 56 & 63 & 72 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4495 & -7346 & 8849 & 4980 & -6685 & 2527 \\\\ 12949 & -267 & -7261 & -8510 & 3001 & -11098 \\\\ 3792 & 204 & -2270 & -462 & 1677 & 1336 \\\\ -20337 & 559 & 22478 & -7082 & -12205 & 11583 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 24m$ and radius $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$19301 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-6x - 10y = 74$ and $7x - 2y = -59$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -9$, $y = -2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $2$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$9776$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{2} + 9x^{8} + 1x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$12x^{1} + 72x^{7} + 3x^{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[4, 12, 36, 108, 324, 972]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 8th term value, sum upto 7th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $4$, common ratio is $3$ , 8th term is $8748$, sum upto 7th term is $4372.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{787}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.23$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 31m$ and radius $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$4335 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1907 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1907 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-8x+5)(-10x-9)$",
    "solution": "$80x^2+22x-45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $33$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1996 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1996 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $156 , 51, 43 =$",
    "solution": "$110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $75x^2 + 56x + 92 = $",
    "solution": "$145.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{64}=$",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{2} + 3x^{5} + 2x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{2}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{3}{5}x^{6} + \\frac{2}{3}x^{4} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $38$ and angle, $43$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 28.51868$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $28 = $",
    "solution": "$175.93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $178$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$2$ hours and $58$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $60$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$140.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $77$ and $149$?",
    "solution": "$63.72$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $26^{4^{5}}$",
    "solution": "$26^{20}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $4991 = $",
    "solution": "$13715$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(10x-8)(-9x)$",
    "solution": "$-90x^2+72x$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 77 \\\\ 75 & 68 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-5775$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $54 , 116, 38 =$",
    "solution": "$152$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $133$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(1,-1)$ and $(-18,-15)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$19y = 14x -33$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$01$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -68 & 22 & 96 & -86 & 97 & 33 & -66 & -29 & 30 & 22 \\\\ 58 & -59 & 18 & -60 & 90 & -42 & -49 & 27 & -77 & -81 \\\\ 76 & -54 & 10 & -22 & 58 & 37 & 76 & 42 & 81 & -9 \\\\ 43 & 63 & -6 & 30 & 77 & 34 & -36 & -14 & 42 & -81 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 93 & -52 & 26 & -38 & -35 \\\\ -88 & -77 & -10 & 23 & 62 \\\\ 43 & 21 & -77 & 38 & -48 \\\\ -47 & 78 & -41 & -58 & 22 \\\\ -49 & 45 & -31 & -2 & 15 \\\\ -84 & -67 & 60 & -90 & -48 \\\\ 100 & 29 & 19 & -98 & -39 \\\\ 78 & -39 & 58 & 96 & -47 \\\\ 4 & -75 & -84 & 62 & -29 \\\\ 6 & -52 & 89 & 50 & 32 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -16225 & -4873 & -10379 & 15206 & 886 \\\\ 9710 & 11602 & -2244 & 2773 & -4223 \\\\ 18480 & -6210 & -655 & -4764 & -15453 \\\\ -14852 & -3122 & -12860 & -4629 & 1124 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9\\cdot9$",
    "solution": "$81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 10m$ and radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$904 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $10, 98 = $",
    "solution": "$889.2592592592592$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 61 =",
    "solution": 29
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 82 & 12 \\\\ 68 & 7 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-242$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(81)=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $97 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$1911497.861 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $91$ terms of the AP series: $-87, -21, 45 ... $",
    "solution": "$262353.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cos)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\sin$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[129.85, 776.26, 53.28, 286.11]$ and $[232.37, 496.61, 903.97, 450.8]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.91$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $13$ and $14 =$",
    "solution": "$182$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $21$ and height, $27$?",
    "solution": "$3562.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x + 5 = 9$",
    "solution": "$1/2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$33+19=$",
    "solution": "$52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $9.6 \\times 10^{47}$ and $4.18 \\times 10^{-55} = $",
    "solution": "$4.01 \\times 10^{-7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $15m$ is",
    "solution": "$3375 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $40.87$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $18$ pistons will contain no more than $9$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$84.79$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $11m, 4m, 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$298 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-7, -7)$ and $(13, -12)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{425}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $14m, 16m, 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$568 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $28B4$ from base $12$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$4744$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $3$ numbers $[5, 1, 9] = $",
    "solution": "$3.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $21973$ from base $11$ to base $16$.",
    "solution": "$7C26$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $79$",
    "solution": "$79$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $11001000 = $",
    "solution": "$111000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $9 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{4}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$20^2=$",
    "solution": "$400$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o1745$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-29$ and exact value equals $-91$.",
    "solution": "$68.13\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12$ % $72 = $",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $59$ and $7 = $",
    "solution": "$114$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $33x^2+173x+54=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.33, -4.91}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$80$ % $22 = $",
    "solution": "$14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $92$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $441 = $",
    "solution": "$0x1b9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[12, 23, 33, 34, 36, 37, 56, 59, 63, 89]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $44.2$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $36.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{6} + 1x^{9} + 4x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$48x^{5} + 9x^{8} + 4x^{0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 26m$ and radius $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$2338 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $6m, 11m, 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$132 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 136 =",
    "solution": 44
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $31$ and height, $11$?",
    "solution": "$2142.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 122 =",
    "solution": 58
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $11001010 = $",
    "solution": "$110110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$110$",
    "solution": "$0x6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$39$ % $94 = $",
    "solution": "$39$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0011100100$",
    "solution": "$0xe4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $80$% of $40$?",
    "solution": "$32.00$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $33x^2 + 50x + 69 = $",
    "solution": "$105.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $85 = $",
    "solution": "$1010101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12 * \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 6 \\\\ 3 & 0 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 84 & 72 \\\\ 36 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-2x - 7y = 17$ and $x - 6y = 39$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 9$, $y = -5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[18, 36, 48, 49, 57, 62, 63, 78, 88, 94]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $59.3$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $59.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 41m$ and radius $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$4410 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $45$ and angle $320$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$5654.87$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $61A7$ from base $16$ to base $15$.",
    "solution": "$7619$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $114$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$1.99$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $14m, 11m, 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$508 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $47$ and angle, $9$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 7.38274$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMDLXXX$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(0,10)$ and passing through $(8.0, 10.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$201.06$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $37$ of the AP series: $62, 106, 150 ... $",
    "solution": "$1646$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{424}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$7.51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{6} + 3x^{1} + 9x^{2} + 9x^{2} + 8x^{6}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{6}x^{7} + \\frac{3}{1}x^{2} + \\frac{9}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{9}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{8}{6}x^{7} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $3$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$804.247719318987 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $18 = $",
    "solution": "$113.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{9}\\div\\frac{3}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{28}{27}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $39$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$102.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(243)=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[851.6797765625743, 714.38135680334, 220.2734352125345, 561.1100693148375, 240.5328753022188, 241.122444860288, 992.2781363612712, 559.2860143853208, 744.9082040188638, 757.140786891207, 749.9160309318362, 210.58712209303064, 243.95104941921107, 321.457294671907, 145.84269229082025, 986.4329330405695, 860.5641377351604]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2577.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $13$ objects picked $1$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $8$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1080$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $79$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$81$ % $45 = $",
    "solution": "$36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6 * \\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 8 \\\\ 1 & 7 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 48 \\\\ 6 & 42 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $31^{3}$ and $22^{3} = (31/22)^3 = 1.4090909090909092^{3}$",
    "solution": "$2.7978024042073635$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $75$% of $74$?",
    "solution": "$55.50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 481$ and $SP = 968$ is: ",
    "solution": "$101.25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{290}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$6.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $169 , 67, 58 =$",
    "solution": "$66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{7} + 8x^{4} + 2x^{7} + 5x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$56x^{6} + 32x^{3} + 14x^{6} + 40x^{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2\\cdot9$",
    "solution": "$18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $39$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$0$ hours and $39$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $11$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $10x + 9y = -77$ and $-9x - 3y = 54$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -5$, $y = -3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5^2=$",
    "solution": "$25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $5^{8}$ and $16^{8} = (5/16)^8 = 0.3125^{8}$",
    "solution": "$9.094947017729282e-05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $16$ sides",
    "solution": "$157.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1728 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[236, 206, 242, 205, 209, 238, 264, 241, 217, 262, 256, 269, 249, 210, 267, 223, 248, 274, 290, 271, 202, 203, 224, 222, 234, 275, 235, 226, 272, 257, 244, 298]$ with $80$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(248.73069564561374, 236.83180435438626)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $29$ and angle, $224$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 113.37659$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{2} + 1x^{7} + 1x^{9} + 1x^{6}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{10}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{1}{7}x^{8} + \\frac{1}{9}x^{10} + \\frac{1}{6}x^{7} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $7$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$30083$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $38^{5^{4}}$",
    "solution": "$38^{20}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 20m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$2309 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 33 & 5 \\\\ 40 & 33 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$889$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $8m, 15m, 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$1080 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $49, 36$ and $40$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $4$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$18067$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10 * \\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 8 \\\\ 9 & 6 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 10 & 80 \\\\ 90 & 60 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[247, 255, 232, 291, 259, 208, 275, 299, 288, 230, 252, 205, 218, 248, 216, 223, 270, 264, 260, 298, 285]$ with $80$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(261.5905278646966, 245.36185308768438)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-8x-7)(-4x+5)$",
    "solution": "$32x^2-12x-35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1010010000$",
    "solution": "$656$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 4 m$, base width $= 13 m$ and height $= 3 m$ is",
    "solution": "$52.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 58 & 1 \\\\ 15 & 30 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$1725$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $12$ and $3 =$",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-14, 5, 12] \\times [-16, -10, -9] = $",
    "solution": "$[75, -318, 220]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8-7=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 140 =",
    "solution": 40
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $2$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$10615$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[7, 17, 21, 24, 35, 42, 70, 81, 85, 98]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $48.0$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $38.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $31.32$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $18$ pistons will contain no more than $6$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$67.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 800$ and $SP = 619$ is: ",
    "solution": "$22.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $16m, 17m, 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1336 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $16$ objects picked $0$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $7$ sides?",
    "solution": "$900$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1936 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1936 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(20-20j) * (-14-8j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-440+120j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-14,7)$ and $(12,-12) = $",
    "solution": "$(-1.0,-2.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $4$ and $6 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $11 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{2}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $36$ and angle, $358$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 224.93803$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $53$ of the AP series: $15, 67, 119 ... $",
    "solution": "$2719$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $4=$",
    "solution": "$50.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[255, 228, 278, 243, 234, 283, 223, 236, 212, 297, 294, 227, 204, 225, 296, 285, 279, 244, 293, 241, 277, 286, 229, 258, 275, 208, 217, 201, 249, 265, 230, 238, 235, 264, 231, 214, 250, 289, 226, 216]$ with $80$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(254.1992332850288, 242.5507667149712)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2\\cdot2$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$39-32=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $940 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4, 5, 10, 20, 47, 94, 188, 235, 470, 940]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $34x^2+110x+21=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.2, -3.03}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6^2=$",
    "solution": "$36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 959$ and $SP = 691$ is: ",
    "solution": "$27.95$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{1}{7}$ and $\\frac{1}{9}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $78 m = $",
    "solution": "$1987798.7692617911 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 20m$, base width $= 20m$, and height $= 26m$ is",
    "solution": "$1360 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[7, 42, 252, 1512, 9072, 54432]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 6th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $7$, common ratio is $6$ , 6th term is $54432$, sum upto 10th term is $84652645.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $54, 4 = $",
    "solution": "$14.896551724137932$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $97 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$1911497.861 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $16m, 4m, 18m$ is",
    "solution": "$1152 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -784 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $1^{2}$ and $42^{2} = (1/42)^2 = 0.023809523809523808^{2}$",
    "solution": "$0.0005668934240362811$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $1 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$2.094 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $317 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 317]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{4} + 2x^{4} + 1x^{8} + 1x^{9} + 7x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{10}{4}x^{5} + \\frac{2}{4}x^{5} + \\frac{1}{8}x^{9} + \\frac{1}{9}x^{10} + \\frac{7}{8}x^{9} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $73$ terms of the AP series: $-89, -117, -145 ... $",
    "solution": "$-80081.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $71x^2 + 85x + 77 = $",
    "solution": "$143.1667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-11, -6)$ and $(-5, 12)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{360}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$30-24=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $9124 = $",
    "solution": "$23104$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-16, -5, -14]\\cdot[12, 9, 0]=$",
    "solution": "$-237$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $0.23$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$13.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 44m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$1206 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4^2=$",
    "solution": "$16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $29$ and height, $14$?",
    "solution": "$2550.97$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $76$ and exact value equals $67$.",
    "solution": "$13.43\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$16^3 =$",
    "solution": "$4096$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $135$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$2$ hours and $15$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $953 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 953]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o5177$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=3*x^2 + 2*x + 10$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{1}{3}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $96$ and exact value equals $1$.",
    "solution": "$9500.0\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-19, -3, 15] \\times [-13, -16, -7] = $",
    "solution": "$[261, -328, 265]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $22$ of the AP series: $-10, -25, -40 ... $",
    "solution": "$-325$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 31m$ and $r1 = 8m$ is and $r2 = 8m$ is ",
    "solution": "$4804.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(9,19)$ and $(15,-18)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$6y = -37x + 447$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $18, 32, 47, 44, 48, 46, 38, 22, 43, 30, 7, 31, 17, 35, 15$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $31.533333333333335$, Standard Deviation is $161.5822222222222$, Variance is $12.71149960556276$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $885 = $",
    "solution": "$0x375$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$9x^{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o1244$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $37 m = $",
    "solution": "$212174.79024304505 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $62x^2+200x+71=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.41, -2.82}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-9x - 7y = 119$ and $2x - 5y = 26$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -7$, $y = -8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(19,-14)$ and $(15,-10) = $",
    "solution": "$(17.0,-12.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $8$ sides",
    "solution": "$135.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 178 =",
    "solution": 2
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $45$ and exact value equals $6$.",
    "solution": "$650.0\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-80--36|=$",
    "solution": "$44$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[77, 34, 13, 73] = $",
    "solution": "$39.7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $7$ and $2 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[238, 251, 216, 203, 239, 295, 270, 293, 268, 226, 237, 241, 201, 244, 204, 264, 230, 229, 232, 245, 214, 260, 202]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(248.26988317462286, 230.16489943407277)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[35, 40, 66, 22] = $",
    "solution": "$37.76$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $43$ and $4 = $",
    "solution": "$133$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $2 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$16.28(11.0\\theta + i12.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$0.83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $9$ sided polygon with lengths of $71, 120, 58, 40, 81, 92, 63, 92, 107$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$724$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $7$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 383$ and $SP = 16$ is: ",
    "solution": "$95.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $15^{2}$ and $15^{5} = $15^{2-5} = 15^{-3}$",
    "solution": "$0.0002962962962962963$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -1 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8 * \\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 5 \\\\ 2 & 10 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 24 & 40 \\\\ 16 & 80 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{18} + 3x^{15} + 7x^{7} + 7x^{6} + 8x^{5} + 10x^{19}$",
    "solution": "$8x^{5} + 7x^{6} + 7x^{7} + 3x^{15} + 10x^{18} + 10x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$19\\div67=$",
    "solution": "$0.28$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 1m$ is",
    "solution": "$6 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[4, 20, 100, 500, 2500, 12500]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 8th term value, sum upto 9th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $4$, common ratio is $5$ , 8th term is $312500$, sum upto 9th term is $1953124.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $18 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$12214.512 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1001$",
    "solution": "$9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $6141$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$9090.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $2$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$9240$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $46x^2 + 43x + 57 = $",
    "solution": "$93.8333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $295 = $",
    "solution": "$0x127$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $12$ and $16 =$",
    "solution": "$48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $73x^2 + 84x + 20 = $",
    "solution": "$86.3333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-5, 6)$ and $(0, -1)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{74}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[17, -6, 13]\\cdot[0, 20, 0]=$",
    "solution": "$-120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 1$ and $y = -7/6x + 10$",
    "solution": "$(54/7, 1)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x + 10 = 10$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11+46=$",
    "solution": "$57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[42, 77, 83, 35] = $",
    "solution": "$55.36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$59\\div86=$",
    "solution": "$0.69$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^2 + 4*x + 9$",
    "solution": "${-2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $15$ and height, $86$?",
    "solution": "$8105.31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13\\div67=$",
    "solution": "$0.19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(81)=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-18$ and exact value equals $-12$.",
    "solution": "$50.0\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $59 , 122, 24 =$",
    "solution": "$155$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$01 = $",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $148$",
    "solution": "$2, 2, 37$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 76 \\\\ 86 & 75 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-6011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{6} + 3x^{8} + 7x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{6}{6}x^{7} + \\frac{3}{8}x^{9} + \\frac{7}{8}x^{9} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[1, -5, 13] \\times [9, 15, -18] = $",
    "solution": "$[-105, 135, 60]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9+27=$",
    "solution": "$36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$011001100$",
    "solution": "$0xcc$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $28x^2 + 20x + 50 = $",
    "solution": "$69.3333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5\\cdot11$",
    "solution": "$55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$96 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $6.23$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$356.95$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 6m$ and $r1 = 2m$ is and $r2 = 2m$ is ",
    "solution": "$1080.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[509.4884760260674, 294.42902664598523, 18.77269134372428, 835.2703834881187, 636.9064633105706, 995.0461127924528, 471.2681383282131, 867.0194210277183]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1847.67$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $26$ and $81 = $",
    "solution": "$73$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{10} + 7x^{1} + 4x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$70x^{9} + 7x^{0} + 40x^{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $76 = $",
    "solution": "$1001100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $22x^2 + 77x + 90 = $",
    "solution": "$135.8333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $4$ and $17 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{5}{10}\\cdot\\frac{3}{10}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{20}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{3} + 4x^{6} + 9x^{7}$",
    "solution": "$27x^{2} + 24x^{5} + 63x^{6}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 16m$ and radius $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$1011 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $43$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(89423501,808117394)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+5x-24$",
    "solution": "$(x+8)(x-3)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $47^{1^{1}}$",
    "solution": "$47^{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|16--46|=$",
    "solution": "$62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$32-22=$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $191$",
    "solution": "$191$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $155 = $",
    "solution": "$0x9b$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 47 & 82 \\\\ 18 & 40 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$404$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $22$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 45 & 28 \\\\ 93 & 70 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$546$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$110 = $",
    "solution": "$001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$4536.459791783661 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{4} + 4x^{8} + 10x^{6} + 5x^{9} + 6x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$5x^{4} + 10x^{6} + 4x^{8} + 5x^{9} + 6x^{10}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $16$ of the AP series: $-30, -104, -178 ... $",
    "solution": "$-1140$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[95.64, 56.04, 814.78, 478.26, 716.06, 955.29, 549.17, 113.54, 633.11, 556.65, 198.64, 577.89, 808.25, 335.96, 940.48, 345.56, 529.96, 624.07, 794.94]$ and $[316.05, 342.2, 48.77, 294.78, 889.1, 513.94, 198.08, 816.74, 270.29, 177.93, 513.49, 767.13, 464.74, 912.24, 353.28, 205.53, 810.87, 985.19, 548.32]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.7$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 8 m$, base width $= 10 m$ and height $= 29 m$ is",
    "solution": "$773.3333333333334 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 340$ and $SP = 648$ is: ",
    "solution": "$90.59$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $51$ terms of the AP series: $-64, -32, 0 ... $",
    "solution": "$37536.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $134$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 22m$ and radius $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$8362 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & 20 & 41 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 10 \\\\ 1 & 4 & 8 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -4 & 5 \\\\ -2 & 1 & 9 \\\\ 1 & 0 & -5 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{3} + 7x^{7}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{10}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{7}{7}x^{8} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $58$ of the AP series: $-85, -184, -283 ... $",
    "solution": "$-5728$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{16}=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $4$ sided polygon with lengths of $102, 14, 102, 67$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$285$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$93$ % $94 = $",
    "solution": "$93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $74$ and $33 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2\\cdot2$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 7x + 7 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.209, -5.791)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{21}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{21}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 26m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$380 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 42 & 24 \\\\ 30 & 16 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $39.28$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $11$ pistons will contain no more than $8$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$99.49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $35.82$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $16$ pistons will contain no more than $9$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$97.3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $3$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$72-4=$",
    "solution": "$68$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $18, 35$ and $27$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $87, 32, 77, 14 = $",
    "solution": "$110.09765582009611$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$62\\div88=$",
    "solution": "$0.7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{14} + 8x^{7} + 9x^{13}$",
    "solution": "$8x^{7} + 9x^{13} + 5x^{14}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $6$ sides",
    "solution": "$120.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $48, 65, 63 = $",
    "solution": "$1209.4227951948433$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 953 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 24m$ and $r1 = 17m$ is and $r2 = 17m$ is ",
    "solution": "$14049.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(1,9)$ and passing through $(10.0, 9.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$254.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 53th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$53316291173$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=2*x^3 + 4*x^2 + 2$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{4}{3}, 0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $10100101 = $",
    "solution": "$1011011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $0$ and exact value equals $7$.",
    "solution": "$100.0\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 18 m$, base width $= 19 m$ and height $= 11 m$ is",
    "solution": "$1254.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $32.88$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $18$ pistons will contain no more than $7$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$78.92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 18m$ and radius $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$2004 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $4708$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$11101.22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $2^{10}$ and $1^{10} = (2/1)^10 = 2.0^{10}$",
    "solution": "$1024.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $5$ and $18$?",
    "solution": "$18.68$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 40m$ and $r1 = 15m$ is and $r2 = 15m$ is ",
    "solution": "$28274.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(20,-9)$ and $(12,4)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$8y = -13x + 188$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $11$ objects picked $2$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{1}=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $5$ of the AP series: $-21, 27, 75 ... $",
    "solution": "$171$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10\\cdot7$",
    "solution": "$70$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5! =$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={8, 9, 4, 7}$, $b={8, 10, 6, 7}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${4, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10}$. Intersection is ${8, 7}$, a-b is ${9, 4}$, b-a is ${10, 6}$. Symmetric difference is ${4, 6, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{9}\\div\\frac{3}{6}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{16}{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 11 m$, base width $= 5 m$ and height $= 1 m$ is",
    "solution": "$18.333333333333332 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13^2=$",
    "solution": "$169$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$2166 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-5x + 8y = -167$ and $11x + -1y = 218$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 19$, $y = -9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 21m$ and radius $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$3716 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $4m$ is",
    "solution": "$64 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -19 & 85 & -84 & 9 & -31 \\\\ -15 & -22 & -52 & 77 & 17 \\\\ 2 & -66 & -72 & 18 & -74 \\\\ -26 & -54 & -88 & 86 & -25 \\\\ -44 & -34 & 11 & 66 & 92 \\\\ -84 & 29 & -88 & -29 & -7 \\\\ -19 & 31 & -65 & 49 & 80 \\\\ -75 & 80 & 12 & 72 & -58 \\\\ -52 & 59 & 21 & -69 & -7 \\\\ -16 & 97 & 48 & -96 & -76 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -38 \\\\ 59 & 74 \\\\ -96 & 54 \\\\ -17 & -36 \\\\ -49 & 56 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 14445 & 416 \\\\ 1552 & -5686 \\\\ 6338 & -13640 \\\\ 5025 & -12256 \\\\ -8692 & 2526 \\\\ 10995 & 1238 \\\\ 3316 & 2222 \\\\ 5186 & 3578 \\\\ 2981 & 9568 \\\\ 6471 & 9578 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 76 & 61 \\\\ 63 & 5 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-3463$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$9x^{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $20$ and $15$?",
    "solution": "$25.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $22291$ from base $10$ to base $2$.",
    "solution": "$101011100010011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $4, 4 5 = $",
    "solution": "$7.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1971 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1971 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $10$% of $78$?",
    "solution": "$7.80$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$00001 = $",
    "solution": "$11110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $9$ sides",
    "solution": "$140.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1\\cdot10$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $566$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$9$ hours and $26$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $68$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$1.19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 61 & 12 \\\\ 1 & 25 & 5 \\\\ 1 & 20 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -4 & 5 \\\\ 1 & 0 & -3 \\\\ -5 & 1 & 14 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7 * \\begin{bmatrix} 9 & 7 \\\\ 4 & 0 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 63 & 49 \\\\ 28 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 31 & 92 \\\\ 23 & 38 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-938$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $3$% of $17$?",
    "solution": "$0.51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $8$ and $15 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o1325$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $10$ objects picked $0$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $47$ terms of the AP series: $8, -47, -102 ... $",
    "solution": "$-59079.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $17, 72, 15, 80 = $",
    "solution": "$526.7348036578805$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x + 5 = 6$",
    "solution": "$1/8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={3, 5, 6, 7, 8, 10}$, $b={2, 3, 7, 8, 10}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${2, 3, 5, 6, 7, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${8, 10, 3, 7}$, a-b is ${5, 6}$, b-a is ${2}$. Symmetric difference is ${2, 5, 6}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $19$ and height, $97$?",
    "solution": "$11579.91$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $7357 = $",
    "solution": "$1121113$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $134$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 30m$, base width $= 30m$, and height $= 25m$ is",
    "solution": "$2100 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 36m$ and radius $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$5541 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^3 + 3*x^2 + 3*x + 7$",
    "solution": "${-1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 3m$ and radius $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$1306 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{1} + 3x^{6} + 8x^{1} + 6x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$6x^{0} + 18x^{5} + 8x^{0} + 60x^{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $6$ sided polygon with lengths of $15, 1, 52, 112, 10, 105$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$295$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $-13$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$8.599999999999998$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 40m$ and radius $= 1m$ is",
    "solution": "$125 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $40.14$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $20$ pistons will contain no more than $5$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$12.3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 30th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$832040$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $74 m = $",
    "solution": "$1697398.3219443604 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $61$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{7} + 2x^{8} + 7x^{9} + 9x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{8}{7}x^{8} + \\frac{2}{8}x^{9} + \\frac{7}{9}x^{10} + \\frac{9}{8}x^{9} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 4/2x - 3$ and $y = -8/6x - 8$",
    "solution": "$(-3/2, -6)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $9635$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1445.25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 20m$, base width $= 20m$, and height $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$720 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[7, 28, 112, 448, 1792, 7168]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 10th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $7$, common ratio is $4$ , 10th term is $1835008$, sum upto 10th term is $2446675.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-2x - 3y = 21$ and $6x - y = 7$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 0$, $y = -7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $10$ and $7 =$",
    "solution": "$70$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $18m, 13m, 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$2106 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $1.57$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$89.95$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $33$ and $13 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-69$ and exact value equals $-54$.",
    "solution": "$27.78\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $150$",
    "solution": "$2, 3, 5, 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 1m$ is",
    "solution": "$6 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$726 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $60$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{28}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$3.04$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$23.35(-16.0\\theta + i-17.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.33$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 40m$, base width $= 10m$, and height $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1170 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{10}\\cdot\\frac{9}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{10}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1 = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $5$ and $10 =$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $8m, 6m, 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$480 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cot)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[13, -20, 17] \\times [-12, 9, 19] = $",
    "solution": "$[-533, -451, -123]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-18,9)$ and $(-14,11) = $",
    "solution": "$(-16.0,10.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $15m, 16m, 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$4560 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x + 4 = 10$",
    "solution": "$3/4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $1=$",
    "solution": "$3.14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={2, 3, 5}$, $b={10, 3, 4}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${2, 3, 4, 5, 10}$. Intersection is ${3}$, a-b is ${2, 5}$, b-a is ${10, 4}$. Symmetric difference is ${2, 4, 5, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[17, 6, 19]\\cdot[6, 15, 17]=$",
    "solution": "$515$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3^2=$",
    "solution": "$9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4^9 =$",
    "solution": "$262144$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $171 , 59, 80 =$",
    "solution": "$50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $9^{6}$ and $9^{3} = $9^{6-3} = 9^{3}$",
    "solution": "$729$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $8$ and $12 =$",
    "solution": "$24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $51$ and $177$?",
    "solution": "$110.53$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $46$ and angle $132$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$2437.46$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$97\\div6=$",
    "solution": "$16.17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $56 = $",
    "solution": "$351.86$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[6, 0, 1]\\cdot[-1, -10, 0]=$",
    "solution": "$-6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $10$ terms of the AP series: $-54, -46, -38 ... $",
    "solution": "$-180.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$5026.548245743669 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $7$ and $5 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-3, -4, 2]\\cdot[14, -2, 6]=$",
    "solution": "$-22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $75$ of the AP series: $-3, 58, 119 ... $",
    "solution": "$4511$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1101100010 = $",
    "solution": "$0010011101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 21 & 22 \\\\ 51 & 49 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $13^{5}$ and $13^{8} = $13^{5-8} = 13^{-3}$",
    "solution": "$0.0004551661356395084$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $18$ and angle, $176$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 55.29203$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $13$ objects picked $3$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1716$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[207.2946688970666, 943.7759400488574, 418.9461646989463, 322.34977069295434, 595.2764861215509, 755.8642768384575, 271.07293304043725, 439.43684437450537, 584.9174947637781, 368.6230902538751, 1.8190572140891481, 972.397530431636, 141.31106505649282, 944.6987269835344, 779.578881611336, 562.9783423738245, 967.9915542529401, 75.37225651329682, 548.4884440952824]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2628.61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{5}{1}\\cdot\\frac{1}{3}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(0) = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $6.11$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$350.08$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=6*x^3 + 7*x^2$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{7}{9}, 0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $498 = $",
    "solution": "$0x1f2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $4$ and $9 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-17, -16, 16] \\times [5, 2, 1] = $",
    "solution": "$[-48, 97, 46]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $32^{\\frac{1}{3}}$ _ $10^{\\frac{1}{8}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $14, 17 4 = $",
    "solution": "$20.33$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $1$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$0$ hours and $1$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$19\\div23=$",
    "solution": "$0.83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$15^2=$",
    "solution": "$225$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $63$ of the AP series: $-19, -19, -19 ... $",
    "solution": "$-19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $67$ composite?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $18$ and $8 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$2827.4333882308138 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[5, 16, 20, 26, 29, 42, 72, 74, 83, 85]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $45.2$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $35.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $10$ sided polygon with lengths of $50, 15, 111, 68, 11, 70, 110, 51, 23, 80$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$589$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $38, 3$ and $25$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $48^{2^{4}}$",
    "solution": "$48^{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -757 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $35$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $-35$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$-31.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{7}{10}$ and $\\frac{1}{2}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $89$ and exact value equals $7$.",
    "solution": "$1171.43\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{144}=$",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x + 6 = 6$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$CCCLIII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $17$",
    "solution": "$17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $127$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$2.22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{396}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$7.34$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $20$ objects picked $7$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$77520$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $20$ and angle $62$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$216.42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[738.04, 305.93]$ and $[985.5, 368.52]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.04$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $43 m = $",
    "solution": "$333038.1428119516 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-4, -4, -18]\\cdot[-2, -20, -2]=$",
    "solution": "$124$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $51, 78 = $",
    "solution": "$2405.3023255813955$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 934$ and $SP = 727$ is: ",
    "solution": "$22.16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6! =$",
    "solution": "$720$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$32+9=$",
    "solution": "$41$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $38^{2}$ and $38^{2} = $38^{2-2} = 38^{0}$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $76$ and $134$?",
    "solution": "$55.24$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{1}=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $1$ and $10$?",
    "solution": "$10.05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 36m$ and $r1 = 15m$ is and $r2 = 15m$ is ",
    "solution": "$27181.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$32-14=$",
    "solution": "$18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $211$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$3.68$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(4, 15)$ and $(11, 21)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{85}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $96 m = $",
    "solution": "$3705973.490621892 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $7$ sides?",
    "solution": "$900$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$22-20=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{8}\\div\\frac{1}{2}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{4}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-3, -8)$ and $(14, 21)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{1130}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $33$ and $51 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 3]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$79\\div42=$",
    "solution": "$1.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $9$ and $6 = $",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $7 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$718.378 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $1$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$5637$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{1} + 3x^{7} + 9x^{1} + 2x^{7} + 6x^{5} + 2x^{16}$",
    "solution": "$17x^{1} + 6x^{5} + 5x^{7} + 2x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{19} + 7x^{4} + 3x^{10} + 8x^{9} + 8x^{13}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{4} + 8x^{9} + 3x^{10} + 8x^{13} + 4x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{10} + 5x^{4} + 8x^{8} + 5x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$5x^{1} + 5x^{4} + 8x^{8} + 7x^{10}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 42m$ and radius $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$7791 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{3}{5}$ and $\\frac{2}{4}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $5$ and $3 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $8$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$33625$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $5$ and $3 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $11$ and height, $73$?",
    "solution": "$5045.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $19$ and $5 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $40$% of $33$?",
    "solution": "$13.20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1989 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1989 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(30) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $18$ and height, $12$?",
    "solution": "$1357.17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$90\\div15=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-6x + 9y = 75$ and $4x + 1y = -29$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -8$, $y = 3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-8,1)$ and passing through $(-10.0, 1.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$12.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$18.25(18.0\\theta + i-3.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-0.17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $5x^2 + 8x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.137, -1.463)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{44}}{2*5}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{44}}{2*5})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[206, 290, 286, 240, 293, 282, 249, 233, 253, 239, 207, 269, 287, 211, 205, 213, 229, 254, 261, 236, 294, 216, 200, 288, 231, 268, 219, 271, 277, 220, 201, 218, 235, 265, 273, 234, 281, 251, 250]$ with $80$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(253.07031301956346, 241.03225108300063)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $31.7$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $17$ pistons will contain no more than $7$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$86.36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $14, 15 8 = $",
    "solution": "$55.31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $10$ and $16 =$",
    "solution": "$80$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 7x + 4 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.719, -2.781)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{17}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{17}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $76 m = $",
    "solution": "$1838778.3689363105 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{8} + 10x^{4} + 5x^{7} + 2x^{5} + 8x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$32x^{7} + 40x^{3} + 35x^{6} + 10x^{4} + 64x^{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5^2=$",
    "solution": "$25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 75 & 43 \\\\ 21 & 42 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$2247$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 35 & 50 \\\\ 9 & 45 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$1125$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$76-72=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $92$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{4}=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5! =$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $8$ and $77$?",
    "solution": "$162.35$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 42m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$13194 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $536$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$8$ hours and $56$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$17^10 =$",
    "solution": "$2015993900449$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 576 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -5x + 8$ and $y = 4/5x$",
    "solution": "$(40/29, 32/29)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $29$ and exact value equals $69$.",
    "solution": "$57.97\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $10$ objects picked $5$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$252$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(4-3j) * (-13-3j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-61+27j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $36^{10^{1}}$",
    "solution": "$36^{10}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $4x^2 + 8x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.134, -1.866)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{48}}{2*4}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{48}}{2*4})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.56\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=92.89$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=92.35\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$16.14$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[1, 10, 17, 22, 37, 40, 46, 68, 80, 96]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $41.7$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $38.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$32\\div16=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $46^{7^{3}}$",
    "solution": "$46^{21}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $95$ of the AP series: $-41, -76, -111 ... $",
    "solution": "$-3331$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cot)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $88$ and $86 = $",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $17m$ is",
    "solution": "$4913 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $10$ sides",
    "solution": "$144.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $87 , 63, 67 =$",
    "solution": "$143$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3 * \\begin{bmatrix} 10 & 3 \\\\ 10 & 7 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 30 & 9 \\\\ 30 & 21 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $570 = $",
    "solution": "$0x23a$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $18$ and exact value equals $31$.",
    "solution": "$41.94\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$225\\div9=$",
    "solution": "$25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -59 & -78 & -51 & -24 \\\\ -10 & -23 & -50 & -83 \\\\ -45 & -42 & -85 & -88 \\\\ 64 & -88 & 22 & 82 \\\\ -92 & -29 & 15 & -22 \\\\ 69 & -88 & -79 & -76 \\\\ 40 & -55 & 42 & -44 \\\\ 40 & -66 & -93 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 28 & 92 & 66 \\\\ -79 & -74 & -83 \\\\ -9 & 41 & -12 \\\\ -71 & -3 & -44 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6673 & -1675 & 4248 \\\\ 7880 & -1019 & 5501 \\\\ 9071 & -4253 & 5408 \\\\ 2724 & 13056 & 7656 \\\\ 1142 & -5637 & -2877 \\\\ 14991 & 9849 & 16150 \\\\ 8211 & 9604 & 8637 \\\\ 6887 & 4739 & 9058 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $11$ sided polygon with lengths of $57, 23, 73, 85, 9, 112, 23, 45, 117, 109, 88$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$741$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3323$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$3670.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 2, 4, 6, 7, 10}$, $b={1, 2, 5, 7}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, 10}$. Intersection is ${1, 2, 7}$, a-b is ${10, 4, 6}$, b-a is ${5}$. Symmetric difference is ${4, 5, 6, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 2, 6, 7, 10}$, $b={9, 2, 4}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10}$. Intersection is ${2}$, a-b is ${1, 10, 6, 7}$, b-a is ${9, 4}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $77 = $",
    "solution": "$483.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $24^{4}$ and $37^{4} = (24/37)^4 = 0.6486486486486487^{4}$",
    "solution": "$0.17702641341912465$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{186}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$5.71$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $15$ objects picked $1$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 33m$ and radius $= 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$2192 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-4x - 5y = 34$ and $-10x + 7y = -32$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -1$, $y = -6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $48^{4}$ and $21^{4} = (48/21)^4 = 2.2857142857142856^{4}$",
    "solution": "$27.295293627655138$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $18$ sides",
    "solution": "$160.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $12$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1800$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{6} + 1x^{3} + 6x^{3} + 8x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$24x^{5} + 3x^{2} + 18x^{2} + 72x^{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10$",
    "solution": "$0x2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{49}=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $326$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$5.69$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $19m$ is",
    "solution": "$6859 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$39+28=$",
    "solution": "$67$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $70$ and $48 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $6x^2 + 9x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.5, -1.0)) = (\\frac{-9 + 3}{2*6}, \\frac{-9 - 3}{2*6})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $22x^2+187x+87=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.49, -8.01}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $30$ and exact value equals $18$.",
    "solution": "$66.67\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 46m$ and $r1 = 7m$ is and $r2 = 7m$ is ",
    "solution": "$24037.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $45$ and angle, $275$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 215.98449$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $43$ and height, $94$?",
    "solution": "$25396.64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $6.98 \\times 10^{25}$ and $7.64 \\times 10^{16} = $",
    "solution": "$5.33 \\times 10^{42}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $19, 8 = $",
    "solution": "$45.03703703703704$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3! =$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{18} + 9x^{12} + 2x^{17} + 4x^{1} + 5x^{11} + 2x^{1} + 5x^{1} + 8x^{12} + 10x^{17} + 8x^{6}$",
    "solution": "$11x^{1} + 8x^{6} + 5x^{11} + 17x^{12} + 12x^{17} + 9x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$17.26(3.0\\theta + i17.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$1.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-20,-19)$ and $(-4,14) = $",
    "solution": "$(-12.0,-2.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $41^{7^{9}}$",
    "solution": "$41^{63}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $547 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 547]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.54\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=98.25$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=94.77\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$9.26$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $31$ and $43 = $",
    "solution": "$106$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(3x+5)(2x+3)$",
    "solution": "$6x^2+19x+15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{5}{7}\\cdot\\frac{2}{5}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{2}{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 118 =",
    "solution": 62
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1728 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $6346 = $",
    "solution": "$181210$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{16} + 7x^{5} + 9x^{16} + 8x^{14}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{5} + 8x^{14} + 15x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(90) = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $111011010000101$ from base $2$ to base $11$.",
    "solution": "$20883$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(15,-9)$ and $(17,3) = $",
    "solution": "$(16.0,-3.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $90$ of the AP series: $57, 124, 191 ... $",
    "solution": "$6020$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[1, -11, 19]\\cdot[13, 15, -10]=$",
    "solution": "$-342$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[292, 281, 239, 284, 287, 203, 230, 280, 228, 208, 231, 285, 237, 221, 205, 232, 276, 298, 264, 213, 258, 212, 278, 225, 215, 271, 291, 248, 253, 268, 211, 266, 201, 261, 288, 289, 255, 227, 296, 240]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(259.10666553656824, 243.24333446343178)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $122$ and $151$?",
    "solution": "$21.25$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $87 m = $",
    "solution": "$2758330.9162224527 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $6$ and $15$?",
    "solution": "$16.16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-16x+60$",
    "solution": "$(x-10)(x-6)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 14 =",
    "solution": 76
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -2/6x - 8$ and $y = -4/2x + 9$",
    "solution": "$(51/5, -57/5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1 = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $808$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$13$ hours and $28$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $18x^2 + 78x + 40 = $",
    "solution": "$85.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x + 8 = 9$",
    "solution": "$1/3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $53^{\\frac{1}{6}}$ _ $46^{\\frac{1}{4}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $228$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $7$ sides",
    "solution": "$128.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-8x+15$",
    "solution": "$(x-3)(x-5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $17m, 19m, 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$1006 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $9 , 6, 245 =$",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[5, 40, 320, 2560, 20480, 163840]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 8th term value, sum upto 9th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $5$, common ratio is $8$ , 8th term is $10485760$, sum upto 9th term is $95869805.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{12} + 7x^{1} + 7x^{17} + 5x^{16} + 6x^{16} + 10x^{19} + 10x^{17} + 5x^{9} + 3x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{1} + 3x^{3} + 5x^{9} + 7x^{12} + 11x^{16} + 17x^{17} + 10x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $987$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$16$ hours and $27$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o7250$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$77\\div11=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(6, -8)$ and $(-19, -7)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{626}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 256$ and $SP = 362$ is: ",
    "solution": "$41.41$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $38$ terms of the AP series: $-40, -94, -148 ... $",
    "solution": "$-39482.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{8} + 9x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{8}x^{9} + \\frac{9}{3}x^{4} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $7x - 8y = -67$ and $2x + 2y = -2$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -5$, $y = 4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(20,-11)$ and $(-5,3)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$25y = -14x + 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 7th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^2 + 6*x + 7$",
    "solution": "${-3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(x+9)(2x-4)$",
    "solution": "$x^2+18x-36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $530 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 5, 10, 53, 106, 265, 530]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{4}{6}$ and $\\frac{6}{7}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(13+6j) * (-8+13j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-182+121j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 26m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$380 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $34, 38, 49, 18, 12, 21, 33, 18, 27, 12, 49, 9, 50, 37, 35$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $29.466666666666665$, Standard Deviation is $183.18222222222226$, Variance is $13.534482709812824$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $4x^2 + 8x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.293, -1.707)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{32}}{2*4}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{32}}{2*4})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 6x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.172, -5.828)) = (\\frac{-6 + \\sqrt{32}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-6 - \\sqrt{32}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 235$ and $SP = 569$ is: ",
    "solution": "$142.13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -7 & -95 & 1 \\\\ 14 & -89 & 70 \\\\ 23 & 23 & -31 \\\\ -100 & -97 & 19 \\\\ -24 & 65 & -53 \\\\ -89 & -83 & -53 \\\\ -40 & 45 & 8 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 42 & 26 & 75 & 40 & -99 & -90 & 58 & -77 & 65 & 35 \\\\ 39 & -49 & -9 & -51 & 31 & -93 & -6 & 51 & 85 & -55 \\\\ -38 & -17 & -34 & -42 & 15 & -68 & 51 & -34 & 82 & 52 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -4037 & 4456 & 296 & 4523 & -2237 & 9397 & 215 & -4340 & -8448 & 5032 \\\\ -5543 & 3535 & -529 & 2159 & -3095 & 2257 & 4916 & -7997 & -915 & 9025 \\\\ 3041 & -2 & 2572 & 1049 & -2029 & -2101 & -385 & 456 & 908 & -2072 \\\\ -8705 & 1830 & -7273 & 149 & 7178 & 16729 & -4249 & 2107 & -13187 & 2823 \\\\ 3541 & -2908 & -583 & -2049 & 3596 & -281 & -4485 & 6965 & -381 & -7171 \\\\ -4961 & 2654 & -4126 & 2899 & 5443 & 19333 & -7367 & 4422 & -17186 & -1306 \\\\ -229 & -3381 & -3677 & -4231 & 5475 & -1129 & -2182 & 5103 & 1881 & -3459 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $46$% of $70$?",
    "solution": "$32.20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 10 & 1 & 5 \\\\ 8 & 1 & 4 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ -4 & 5 & 0 \\\\ 1 & -1 & -2 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $79=$",
    "solution": "$19606.68$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$71\\div67=$",
    "solution": "$1.06$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8\\cdot7$",
    "solution": "$56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cot)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $3.23 \\times 10^{-47}$ and $7.62 \\times 10^{91} = $",
    "solution": "$2.46 \\times 10^{45}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $18$ and $7 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 4 & 4 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 5 \\\\ 5 & 21 & 20 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & -4 & 0 \\\\ -5 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 4 & 1 & -1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$81\\div83=$",
    "solution": "$0.98$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $401 = $",
    "solution": "$0x191$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={9, 2, 7}$, $b={1, 10, 5, 7}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 5, 7, 9, 10}$. Intersection is ${7}$, a-b is ${9, 2}$, b-a is ${1, 10, 5}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 2, 5, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 9m$ and radius $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$2261 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{7}\\cdot\\frac{3}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{6}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{6}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[24, 34, 59, 65, 69, 85, 91, 94, 95, 98]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $71.4$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $77.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$010100$",
    "solution": "$20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $26^{4}$ and $26^{10} = $26^{4-10} = 26^{-6}$",
    "solution": "$3.2371282973906776e-09$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[876.3434750612912, 329.67113973835546]$ is:",
    "solution": "$936.3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4-4=$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $522 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 3, 6, 9, 18, 29, 58, 87, 174, 261, 522]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $2m$ is",
    "solution": "$8 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $12m, 15m, 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$2160 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $4x + 7y = -52$ and $-3x + 5y = -43$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 1$, $y = -8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{210}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$5.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $1^{5}$ and $1^{4} = $1^{5-4} = 1^{1}$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-4x-10)(8x+5)$",
    "solution": "$-32x^2-100x-50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $66$ and $95 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12\\div55=$",
    "solution": "$0.22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $51$ of the AP series: $27, -6, -39 ... $",
    "solution": "$-1623$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $6m$ is",
    "solution": "$216 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{10}\\cdot\\frac{5}{1}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $7$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$29001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $31.25$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $15$ pistons will contain no more than $1$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$2.83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$010 = $",
    "solution": "$101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(5,-8)$ and passing through $(0.41999999999999993, -13.3)$ is",
    "solution": "$153.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $10$ objects picked $1$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $11$ objects picked $0$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{8}{5}$ and $\\frac{10}{4}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 3m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$816 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10\\cdot10$",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $8x - 7y = -108$ and $-x + 3y = 22$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -10$, $y = 4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0111110$",
    "solution": "$0x3e$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[297.12, 374.07, 704.42, 749.82, 775.25, 727.7, 32.86, 616.54, 27.35, 433.22, 376.33, 326.75, 66.77, 332.6, 961.66, 201.54, 40.1]$ and $[801.54, 231.99, 16.59, 558.86, 4.32, 930.8, 761.46, 243.23, 282.2, 108.16, 770.24, 556.74, 981.07, 30.64, 684.55, 405.39, 644.26]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.91$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{144}=$",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.71\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=94.65$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=98.58\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$53.7$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $38, 26, 88 = $",
    "solution": "$1155.7510574018127$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 35 =",
    "solution": 145
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 7x + 7 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.209, -5.791)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{21}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{21}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$1014 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$24-5=$",
    "solution": "$19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $33$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $28$ and $60 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{3}{1}$ and $\\frac{1}{2}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $3x^2 + 4x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.333, -1.0)) = (\\frac{-4 + 2}{2*3}, \\frac{-4 - 2}{2*3})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $20 = $",
    "solution": "$0x14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $17$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $5$ sides?",
    "solution": "$540$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $71, 29, 76, 63 = $",
    "solution": "$811.8747504905222$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$37$ % $43 = $",
    "solution": "$37$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$17\\div12=$",
    "solution": "$1.42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 2 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 1 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 3 & 3 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -3 & 1 \\\\ 1 & -1 & 0 \\\\ -1 & 2 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $11111 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(939982820,399336669)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $7$ sides",
    "solution": "$128.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $2x^2+79x+9=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.11, -39.39}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $6000$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$360.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $64$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 9$ and $SP = 581$ is: ",
    "solution": "$6355.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $B450$ from base $12$ to base $2$.",
    "solution": "$100110010111100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[279.19816525836126, 869.5275705094031, 706.6278486387475, 799.6264007927091, 679.8368288325755, 805.2968397829986, 477.8349578673087, 620.7118083107305, 293.3070582863935, 750.6725508763479, 322.6214471689728, 71.47175236484038, 828.8057713142994, 768.2553805802905, 992.5733204192899, 590.9879637277303]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2658.45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[9, 8, -11]\\cdot[16, 9, -4]=$",
    "solution": "$260$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o536$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233, 377, 610, 987, 1597, 2584$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $45, 35, 12, 36, 23, 11, 20, 25, 16, 48, 44, 44, 35, 49, 26$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $31.266666666666666$, Standard Deviation is $162.32888888888888$, Variance is $12.740835486297156$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={8, 3, 6}$, $b={8, 10, 5, 6}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${3, 5, 6, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${8, 6}$, a-b is ${3}$, b-a is ${10, 5}$. Symmetric difference is ${3, 5, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8^3 =$",
    "solution": "$512$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $342$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$5.97$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[7, 9, 5] \\times [14, 17, -9] = $",
    "solution": "$[-166, 133, -7]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 8th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={2, 3, 4, 7, 8, 10}$, $b={1, 3, 7, 8, 10}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 3, 4, 7, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${8, 10, 3, 7}$, a-b is ${2, 4}$, b-a is ${1}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 2, 4}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{6}{9}\\cdot\\frac{3}{7}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{2}{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{6}\\div\\frac{10}{2}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{7}{30}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[293, 227, 218, 240, 279, 220, 202, 221, 283, 225, 208, 207, 228, 269, 223, 200, 205, 276, 244, 233]$ with $99$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(251.51674124798225, 218.58325875201777)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $90 = $",
    "solution": "$1011010$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -877 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o3735$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $534031$ from base $6$ to base $16$.",
    "solution": "$AA83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $63 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$523697.212 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{10}{3}\\div\\frac{5}{9}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{6}{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 1 m$, base width $= 15 m$ and height $= 15 m$ is",
    "solution": "$75.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $80$% of $92$?",
    "solution": "$73.60$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(0) = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-19,3)$ and $(1,9) = $",
    "solution": "$(-9.0,6.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-3, -13, 2] \\times [3, 10, -4] = $",
    "solution": "$[32, -6, 9]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $3$ numbers $[5, 22, 69] = $",
    "solution": "$19.65$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $53, 68, 50, 81 = $",
    "solution": "$1228.7717190445803$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[367.26560089832196, 890.6100919567036, 961.6932403429031, 162.84464837133504, 477.0732080702024, 628.8411096974397, 770.7808351765303]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1759.71$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 1 & 5 \\\\ 4 & 4 & 21 \\\\ 1 & 2 & 10 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 2 & 0 & -1 \\\\ 19 & -5 & 1 \\\\ -4 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $12$ sides",
    "solution": "$150.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $46$ terms of the AP series: $58, 21, -16 ... $",
    "solution": "$-35627.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\tan(90) = $",
    "solution": "$\\infty$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $74$% of $7$?",
    "solution": "$5.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $7m, 18m, 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$882 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[667.9, 914.19, 757.44, 315.99, 361.98, 307.95]$ and $[422.99, 113.87, 283.61, 232.38, 907.16, 451.14]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.84$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $41$ and exact value equals $66$.",
    "solution": "$37.88\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 101 =",
    "solution": 79
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $2$ and angle $73$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$2.55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $38$ and angle, $105$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 69.63864$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 5$ and $SP = 614$ is: ",
    "solution": "$12180.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $66$ of the AP series: $47, 118, 189 ... $",
    "solution": "$4662$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$1176 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $96 m = $",
    "solution": "$3705973.490621892 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 311$ and $SP = 609$ is: ",
    "solution": "$95.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $28^{2}$ and $1^{2} = (28/1)^2 = 28.0^{2}$",
    "solution": "$784.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $3$ and $15$?",
    "solution": "$15.3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $4421 = $",
    "solution": "$1145$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $9$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$38009$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $10$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{8}{1}$ and $\\frac{4}{10}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$210\\div21=$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $40$ and angle, $190$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 132.64502$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 14m$ and radius $= 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$8620 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $5345 = $",
    "solution": "$14141$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11^3 =$",
    "solution": "$1331$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-2x + -16y = -194$ and $17x + -15y = -465$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -15$, $y = 14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $11101 = $",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 20m$ and radius $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$2695 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $1136 = $",
    "solution": "$470$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $6.17$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$353.51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$2400 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $46^{\\frac{1}{5}}$ _ $64^{\\frac{1}{9}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $3$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$14737$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o2146$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $16$ objects picked $8$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$518918400$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[319.11983720172253, 783.5045921540352, 32.6111466662421, 555.860310229314, 957.0636114371943, 635.2539562095197, 698.6508613800574, 250.83471294504955, 908.5898541757317, 727.4448961883938, 290.38654847617715, 215.94035447928727]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2093.32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-13,-1)$ and $(-10,-7) = $",
    "solution": "$(-11.5,-4.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $82 = $",
    "solution": "$515.22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13.15(-2.0\\theta + i13.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$1.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[220, 250, 241, 261, 205, 236, 283, 285, 298, 210, 234, 231, 221, 284, 211, 277, 228, 288, 282, 276, 280, 256, 226, 263, 229, 218, 267, 278]$ with $95$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(261.7870086280912, 240.92727708619452)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $9=$",
    "solution": "$254.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o7336$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 1m$ and $r1 = 14m$ is and $r2 = 14m$ is ",
    "solution": "$493.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $117 = $",
    "solution": "$0x75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[9, -1, 16] \\times [-15, -18, 0] = $",
    "solution": "$[288, -240, -177]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[737.81, 166.75, 173.34, 49.16, 863.0, 6.2]$ and $[799.91, 725.56, 887.4, 997.95, 220.14, 634.48]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1.03$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $50, 32, 11, 24, 38, 7, 24, 26, 46, 18, 19, 49, 35, 24, 17$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $28.0$, Standard Deviation is $166.53333333333333$, Variance is $12.904779476354229$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 17 =",
    "solution": 73
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+x-42$",
    "solution": "$(x+7)(x-6)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{6}\\cdot\\frac{4}{7}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{16}{21}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-7,-18)$ and $(18,-9)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$25y = 9x -387$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $13$ and $16$?",
    "solution": "$20.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 893$ and $SP = 308$ is: ",
    "solution": "$65.51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[19, -7, -20] \\times [-3, -12, 9] = $",
    "solution": "$[-303, -111, -249]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 15 m$, base width $= 9 m$ and height $= 48 m$ is",
    "solution": "$2160.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 12m$, base width $= 12m$, and height $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$384 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $324 = $",
    "solution": "$0x144$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $3$ sides?",
    "solution": "$180$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $56$",
    "solution": "$2, 2, 2, 7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 8x + 5 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.775, -3.225)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{24}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{24}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $39, 18$ and $26$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $14$ and $4 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.70\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=91.56$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=91.65\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$7.18$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMCCCLXXXVIII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $97$ of the AP series: $29, 26, 23 ... $",
    "solution": "$-259$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 26 & -98 & 46 & -20 \\\\ 42 & 100 & -31 & -81 \\\\ -9 & 6 & 65 & 6 \\\\ -77 & -56 & -74 & -66 \\\\ 53 & 6 & 56 & 92 \\\\ 55 & 46 & 68 & 76 \\\\ -16 & 7 & -56 & 52 \\\\ -28 & 77 & 55 & -1 \\\\ 8 & 89 & 54 & -53 \\\\ 72 & 64 & -52 & 21 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 97 & -70 & -1 & 56 & -35 & 69 & -97 & -18 & 81 \\\\ -20 & -69 & -50 & -10 & 43 & 73 & 71 & 14 & -65 \\\\ -4 & 1 & -39 & 13 & 48 & -45 & -98 & -85 & -65 \\\\ -90 & -5 & -68 & -42 & 40 & -33 & -80 & -55 & 22 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6098 & 5088 & 4440 & 3874 & -3716 & -6770 & -12388 & -4650 & 5046 \\\\ 9488 & -9466 & 1675 & 4351 & -1898 & 14266 & 12544 & 7734 & -2865 \\\\ -1793 & 251 & -3234 & 29 & 3933 & -3306 & -5551 & -5609 & -5212 \\\\ -113 & 9510 & 10251 & -1942 & -5905 & -3893 & 16025 & 10522 & 761 \\\\ -3483 & -4528 & -8793 & -228 & 4771 & -1461 & -17563 & -10690 & 2287 \\\\ -2697 & -7336 & -10175 & 312 & 6357 & 1585 & -14813 & -10306 & -1283 \\\\ -6148 & 321 & -1686 & -3878 & 253 & 211 & 3377 & 2286 & 3033 \\\\ -4386 & -3293 & -5899 & -1581 & 6891 & 1247 & 2873 & -3038 & -10870 \\\\ 3550 & -6382 & -2960 & 2486 & 4019 & 6368 & 4491 & -573 & -9813 \\\\ 4022 & -9613 & -2672 & 1834 & -1424 & 11287 & 976 & 2865 & 5514 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{25}=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $97x^2 + 91x + 90 = $",
    "solution": "$167.8333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $98x^2 + 29x + 51 = $",
    "solution": "$98.1667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[292, 216, 223, 251, 293, 239, 272, 255, 297, 234, 250, 252, 248, 286, 266, 290, 282, 227, 247, 244, 280, 265, 213, 222, 299, 273, 263, 207, 238, 274, 211, 281, 218, 295, 204, 283, 258, 254]$ with $95$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(264.25551038337375, 246.3760685639947)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $96=$",
    "solution": "$28952.92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $19^{\\frac{1}{5}}$ _ $91^{\\frac{1}{6}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $38.78$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $10$ pistons will contain no more than $2$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$18.78$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $15$ and $5 = $",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $1$ and $10 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $893$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$14$ hours and $53$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{6} + 8x^{9} + 9x^{18} + 1x^{18} + 2x^{2} + 5x^{15} + 1x^{11} + 1x^{10} + 9x^{8} + 10x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$2x^{2} + 8x^{6} + 9x^{8} + 8x^{9} + 11x^{10} + 1x^{11} + 5x^{15} + 10x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $26^{3^{3}}$",
    "solution": "$26^{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-1x + 6y = 14$ and $20x + -4y = 184$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 10$, $y = 4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $3^{\\frac{1}{3}}$ _ $38^{\\frac{1}{1}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $11$",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $14$ and $17 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 6 =",
    "solution": 174
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMCCCLXII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $85=$",
    "solution": "$22698.01$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[10, 20, 40, 80, 160, 320]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 11th term value, sum upto 6th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $10$, common ratio is $2$ , 11th term is $10240$, sum upto 6th term is $630.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11101$",
    "solution": "$29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $84$ and $62 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $62$% of $12$?",
    "solution": "$7.44$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{8}\\cdot\\frac{6}{2}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=8*x^3 + 7*x^2 + 2*x$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{1}{3}, - \\frac{1}{4}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 30m$ and radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$3253 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0110100000$",
    "solution": "$0x1a0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $11 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={8, 5, 7}$, $b={9, 2, 10, 7}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${2, 5, 7, 8, 9, 10}$. Intersection is ${7}$, a-b is ${8, 5}$, b-a is ${9, 2, 10}$. Symmetric difference is ${2, 5, 8, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{1}=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[472.3, 118.35, 306.5, 532.75, 942.08, 487.35, 294.28, 720.14, 971.32, 692.07, 675.99, 815.57, 733.09, 130.35, 575.02, 109.44, 287.32]$ and $[249.58, 645.81, 173.32, 88.99, 739.81, 30.84, 938.23, 905.36, 231.76, 816.93, 507.01, 965.07, 969.64, 152.24, 242.7, 216.55, 184.4]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.6$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 2 & 11 & 2 \\\\ 2 & 10 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -5 & 1 & 9 \\\\ 1 & 0 & -2 \\\\ 0 & -1 & 2 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-5x+1)(-7x)$",
    "solution": "$35x^2-7x$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={4, 5, 7}$, $b={8, 2, 3, 6}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8}$. Intersection is $set()$, a-b is ${4, 5, 7}$, b-a is ${8, 2, 3, 6}$. Symmetric difference is ${2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1^8 =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $18$ objects picked $5$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1028160$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $8$ and $16 = $",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-4, -6, -9] \\times [17, -4, -18] = $",
    "solution": "$[72, -225, 118]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $770 = $",
    "solution": "$0x302$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(7x-1)(x+9)$",
    "solution": "$7x^2+62x-9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-9, -3, 12]\\cdot[-20, 6, 1]=$",
    "solution": "$174$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $42 m = $",
    "solution": "$310339.0886922141 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $18$ sides",
    "solution": "$160.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{9} + 5x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$36x^{8} + 5x^{0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $79$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 94th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$19740274219868282880$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $60 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$452389.342 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $40.67$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $20$ pistons will contain no more than $3$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$1.38$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $5.92 \\times 10^{-13}$ and $2.85 \\times 10^{21} = $",
    "solution": "$1.69 \\times 10^{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 51 & 35 & 63 & -82 & -35 & -66 & 56 & -50 & -47 & -28 \\\\ -53 & 75 & -50 & 26 & -75 & 91 & -32 & -55 & 98 & 81 \\\\ -86 & -67 & 19 & -36 & 47 & -35 & -86 & -30 & 2 & 33 \\\\ -76 & -63 & 64 & -28 & 36 & -41 & -74 & 74 & -8 & 55 \\\\ 62 & -69 & 38 & -67 & 30 & -32 & -73 & -72 & -12 & 66 \\\\ -71 & 13 & 33 & 19 & -39 & 66 & 38 & 87 & 76 & -20 \\\\ 35 & 67 & -11 & -17 & -91 & 66 & 95 & -30 & 51 & 100 \\\\ -5 & -82 & 28 & 7 & 93 & 97 & -27 & -55 & 77 & -74 \\\\ 80 & 49 & -36 & -99 & -64 & -65 & -24 & -69 & 20 & -68 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 23 & -33 & 46 & -100 & 24 & -60 & -97 & -40 & -59 & -99 \\\\ 66 & -83 & -83 & 60 & -91 & -47 & 24 & 38 & -42 & -6 \\\\ -10 & 82 & 67 & 96 & 47 & 28 & 6 & -65 & 10 & -36 \\\\ 6 & 50 & -79 & -76 & -97 & -95 & 49 & -71 & 68 & -46 \\\\ -11 & -44 & 14 & 6 & 40 & -96 & 3 & 74 & 25 & -64 \\\\ 67 & 55 & 84 & -94 & -13 & 71 & 32 & -42 & -99 & 88 \\\\ 6 & -37 & 50 & 12 & 38 & 46 & 85 & -77 & -91 & -98 \\\\ -35 & 87 & -96 & -64 & 16 & -88 & -54 & 100 & 6 & 23 \\\\ -65 & -69 & -76 & -12 & 91 & -62 & 63 & 35 & 24 & 10 \\\\ -71 & 10 & -54 & 6 & 65 & 64 & 43 & 11 & 92 & -17 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 5453 & -9071 & 16790 & 19542 & 3643 & 11621 & -6669 & -10066 & -12866 & -13955 \\\\ 921 & -8524 & -15615 & -3534 & -5065 & 11922 & 20509 & -1713 & 2747 & 19683 \\\\ -11607 & 4928 & 86 & 13774 & 9332 & 5936 & -40 & 11218 & 21000 & 10997 \\\\ -16276 & 18024 & -7873 & 10964 & 12825 & -294 & -4757 & 16283 & 22871 & 8913 \\\\ -8208 & -1708 & 14760 & 5860 & 16940 & 9746 & -11894 & -524 & 10977 & -4490 \\\\ -2477 & 10985 & -9785 & -2978 & 2855 & -702 & 12783 & 2396 & -5196 & 12570 \\\\ 1863 & -9478 & -721 & -2946 & 5648 & 19728 & 16361 & -13868 & -13355 & -2247 \\\\ 1723 & 1021 & 19423 & -8996 & 10729 & -3680 & 4755 & -3965 & -5616 & 5650 \\\\ 6988 & -22543 & 6242 & 8214 & -959 & 2199 & -13901 & 925 & -13041 & -1867 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $32^{1}$ and $9^{1} = (32/9)^1 = 3.5555555555555554^{1}$",
    "solution": "$3.5555555555555554$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(841108135,653117408)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 21m$ and radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$87 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(871789099,271735465)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\tan(45) = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o4421$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 31m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1337 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $5$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$22617$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 34 & 20 \\\\ 80 & 15 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-1090$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $13$ and exact value equals $37$.",
    "solution": "$64.86\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2002 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2002 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(8,14)$ and $(-5,-20) = $",
    "solution": "$(1.5,-3.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{3} + 7x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$12x^{2} + 28x^{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$15^2=$",
    "solution": "$225$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 28m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1248 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMCMLXIX$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $6.72 \\times 10^{72}$ and $6.43 \\times 10^{79} = $",
    "solution": "$4.32 \\times 10^{152}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o317$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-5-3j) * (8+14j) = $",
    "solution": "$(2-94j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $3x^2 + 7x + 4 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.0, -1.333)) = (\\frac{-7 + 1}{2*3}, \\frac{-7 - 1}{2*3})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $71 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$749607.045 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $44^{7}$ and $43^{7} = (44/43)^7 = 1.0232558139534884^{7}$",
    "solution": "$1.1745987824885105$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $3$ numbers $[29, 89, 57] = $",
    "solution": "$52.79$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 947$ and $SP = 694$ is: ",
    "solution": "$26.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x + 6 = 6$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7^3 =$",
    "solution": "$343$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2021 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2021 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={4, 5, 7}$, $b={2, 10, 5}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${2, 4, 5, 7, 10}$. Intersection is ${5}$, a-b is ${4, 7}$, b-a is ${2, 10}$. Symmetric difference is ${2, 4, 7, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $6$ and $5 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-4, 5, 5] \\times [-12, 9, 13] = $",
    "solution": "$[20, -8, 24]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 3 =",
    "solution": 87
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $23$ and $88 = $",
    "solution": "$69$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $B84C$ from base $16$ to base $2$.",
    "solution": "$1011100001001100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{8}x^{9} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$2166 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $180$ and $47$?",
    "solution": "$117.18$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[4, 12, 36, 108, 324, 972]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 7th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $4$, common ratio is $3$ , 7th term is $2916$, sum upto 10th term is $118096.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[18, -15, -2]\\cdot[3, 18, -9]=$",
    "solution": "$-198$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $44, 45$ and $17$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $2062$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$3816.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12^8 =$",
    "solution": "$429981696$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 560 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $7666$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1839.84$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(14,16)$ and $(5,-17)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$3y = 11x -106$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $20$ objects picked $1$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{6}\\div\\frac{7}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{8}{21}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $45$ and angle, $91$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 71.47123$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $68, 87 = $",
    "solution": "$3320.5935483870967$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $39.0$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $19$ pistons will contain no more than $2$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$0.69$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $10$ and $20$?",
    "solution": "$22.36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $7$ sided polygon with lengths of $36, 18, 27, 87, 113, 53, 31$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$365$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $16$ and $7 =$",
    "solution": "$112$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 21m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$318 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 2 m$, base width $= 2 m$ and height $= 10 m$ is",
    "solution": "$13.333333333333334 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\tan)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $36^{8^{7}}$",
    "solution": "$36^{56}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $6225$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$8787.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $40^{5}$ and $40^{9} = $40^{5-9} = 40^{-4}$",
    "solution": "$3.90625e-07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 50m$, base width $= 18m$, and height $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$2116 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-6, 3)$ and $(5, 15)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{265}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$00111$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $185$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $1402 = $",
    "solution": "$5710$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-17-26|=$",
    "solution": "$43$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[544.4287232138211, 175.5792415931231, 862.1183497263855, 659.7858679893675, 685.3215343568271, 920.1863559935978, 931.0636273365077, 93.70250030283222, 423.01943325297367, 235.89278975368833, 244.30501671632865]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1998.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $67$ and $34 = $",
    "solution": "$79$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $118$",
    "solution": "$2, 59$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 32m$ and radius $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$25735 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(2,-3)$ and $(-17,10)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$19y = -13x -31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(445571084,385313423)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 2, 3, 4, 10}$, $b={1, 3, 4, 8, 9, 10}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 3, 4, 8, 9, 10}$. Intersection is ${1, 10, 3, 4}$, a-b is ${2}$, b-a is ${8, 9}$. Symmetric difference is ${2, 8, 9}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $3.88$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$222.31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[3, 10, -1]\\cdot[17, 7, 17]=$",
    "solution": "$104$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $35$ and angle $243$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$2597.7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 54 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5258$ dollars, $2$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$6283.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-1x-56$",
    "solution": "$(x-8)(x+7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $28^{3}$ and $43^{3} = (28/43)^3 = 0.6511627906976745^{3}$",
    "solution": "$0.27610147534179386$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $25$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$77.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$81-57=$",
    "solution": "$24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[3, 25, 31, 35, 49, 55, 73, 74, 77, 82]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $50.4$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $52.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1990 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1990 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 66 \\\\ 2 & 80 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-132$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(831490269,455032927)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2007 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2007 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{9}{1}$ and $\\frac{8}{10}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 4m$ and $r1 = 13m$ is and $r2 = 13m$ is ",
    "solution": "$2651.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $20$ and angle, $58$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 20.24582$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+3x-54$",
    "solution": "$(x-6)(x+9)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $4$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$16647$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 351$ and $SP = 472$ is: ",
    "solution": "$34.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[297.7342080278379, 703.1742163112151, 663.9195595919297, 744.6965330877515]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1256.37$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 82 =",
    "solution": 8
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(45) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[284, 220, 222, 215, 250, 241, 296, 285, 232, 233, 214, 289, 256, 278, 239, 204, 242, 210, 244, 252, 227, 212, 245, 238, 216, 293, 287, 207]$ with $80$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(250.91149870292978, 237.01707272564167)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $39x^2+139x+40=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.32, -3.25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.32\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=98.61$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=91.05\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$12.85$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $8657 = $",
    "solution": "$21131$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-3,11)$ and $(-16,-18) = $",
    "solution": "$(-9.5,-3.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11 = $",
    "solution": "$00$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $90=$",
    "solution": "$25446.9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $10$ objects picked $5$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$252$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $97$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $8608$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$11519.45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{17} + 10x^{4} + 7x^{10} + 9x^{5}$",
    "solution": "$10x^{4} + 9x^{5} + 7x^{10} + 1x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $13$ and $12$?",
    "solution": "$17.69$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & 1 & 10 \\\\ 4 & 1 & 8 \\\\ 20 & 5 & 41 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 9 & -2 \\\\ -4 & 5 & 0 \\\\ 0 & -5 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+2x$",
    "solution": "$(x)(x+2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(243)=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-4,9)$ and $(-6,-3) = $",
    "solution": "$(-5.0,3.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $31, 17, 37, 17, 49, 14, 21, 49, 15, 47, 23, 42, 18, 34, 36$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $30.0$, Standard Deviation is $156.66666666666666$, Variance is $12.516655570345725$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 942$ and $SP = 382$ is: ",
    "solution": "$59.45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$01010$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{6}{4}$ and $\\frac{10}{2}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{1}\\div\\frac{7}{10}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{40}{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{9}{4}\\div\\frac{9}{10}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $53$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $17$ objects picked $8$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$980179200$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $14^{\\frac{1}{5}}$ _ $28^{\\frac{1}{2}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[293, 241, 280, 253, 260, 219, 291, 207, 274, 275, 204, 285, 272, 255, 226, 273, 233, 263, 294, 203, 232, 242, 256, 276, 230, 248, 200, 298, 299, 243, 284, 251, 222, 277, 208, 220, 221, 210]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(258.53918509084104, 242.40818333021164)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $22$% of $10$?",
    "solution": "$2.20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $58$% of $73$?",
    "solution": "$42.34$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(4)=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $73$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{3}{7}$ and $\\frac{8}{7}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-80--7|=$",
    "solution": "$73$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12\\cdot6$",
    "solution": "$72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $54^{\\frac{1}{6}}$ _ $96^{\\frac{1}{9}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 26m$, base width $= 40m$, and height $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1810 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $20$ objects picked $7$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$77520$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMDCCCLXIII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1956 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1956 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $8m, 11m, 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$594 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(14, -3)$ and $(-9, 13)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{785}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{295}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$6.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $5.54$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$317.42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-18,1)$ and $(17,-14)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$7y = -3x -47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={3, 8, 10, 2}$, $b={8, 1, 5}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${8}$, a-b is ${2, 10, 3}$, b-a is ${1, 5}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 2, 3, 5, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$113.09733552923255 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $783$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$13$ hours and $3$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 95 & 51 & -58 & -100 & 19 & 12 & 70 & -91 & -10 & 18 \\\\ 73 & 38 & 93 & 23 & 27 & -39 & -78 & 59 & 86 & 13 \\\\ -23 & -81 & -33 & 31 & 91 & 24 & 94 & 68 & -3 & -15 \\\\ -8 & 4 & 77 & -93 & -99 & 15 & -28 & -32 & 78 & -91 \\\\ -94 & -23 & 84 & 65 & 27 & 14 & 2 & 60 & -80 & -37 \\\\ -73 & -40 & -89 & 31 & -34 & 16 & -87 & -53 & -91 & -66 \\\\ 53 & -66 & 75 & 38 & 93 & 24 & 56 & 17 & 99 & -62 \\\\ -42 & 27 & -64 & -53 & -66 & -20 & 42 & -6 & -61 & -53 \\\\ -50 & 26 & 100 & -15 & -23 & 7 & -98 & 59 & -54 & -28 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 63 & 58 & -84 & 22 & -57 & 2 & 58 & 77 \\\\ -13 & 57 & 64 & -76 & -39 & 17 & -81 & 97 \\\\ -37 & 84 & -21 & -46 & 49 & -48 & -77 & -77 \\\\ -3 & -100 & -42 & -64 & -16 & 75 & 3 & -50 \\\\ -52 & -46 & 75 & -85 & 73 & -71 & 9 & -56 \\\\ 19 & 22 & -49 & -31 & -100 & 47 & 4 & -92 \\\\ 27 & 81 & -100 & -5 & 47 & 84 & -87 & -92 \\\\ -22 & 41 & 37 & -17 & 77 & -45 & -73 & 37 \\\\ -68 & -47 & -54 & -49 & 4 & 49 & -94 & -12 \\\\ -38 & -10 & -18 & -38 & -28 & -11 & 76 & 86 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 10896 & 15164 & -8612 & 6298 & -12720 & 4843 & 8625 & 11421 \\\\ -11296 & 1741 & 2422 & -13439 & 5274 & -10833 & -10466 & 12517 \\\\ -1728 & -4788 & -4664 & -4204 & 16662 & 2007 & -5224 & -23327 \\\\ 409 & 14080 & -5901 & 10200 & -4086 & 1026 & -17303 & -4713 \\\\ -4484 & -389 & 10275 & -6777 & 15332 & -7040 & -9409 & -22173 \\\\ 8706 & -19457 & 13646 & 14241 & -9904 & 281 & 20686 & -2307 \\\\ -6310 & -738 & -15249 & -11413 & 13082 & 2231 & -16439 & -28455 \\\\ 10010 & 8176 & 4682 & 14485 & -1013 & 4610 & -2038 & 4587 \\\\ -5022 & 6993 & 17729 & -1781 & 5102 & -16846 & -5763 & 1805 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$72-0=$",
    "solution": "$72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $96$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5! =$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{9}=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $29, 14, 36, 22, 31, 24, 33, 33, 15, 10, 20, 47, 8, 15, 18$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $23.666666666666668$, Standard Deviation is $111.82222222222222$, Variance is $10.57460269807912$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+19x+90$",
    "solution": "$(x+10)(x+9)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $79$ terms of the AP series: $-52, -49, -46 ... $",
    "solution": "$5135.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $45$ and $78 = $",
    "solution": "$57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.53\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=94.02$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=93.45\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$18.24$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $6$ sided polygon with lengths of $21, 86, 52, 7, 39, 40$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$245$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $51=$",
    "solution": "$8171.28$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $5$ sides",
    "solution": "$108.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $59$ and $30 = $",
    "solution": "$91$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $83 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$1197547.892 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(15,10)$ and $(0,11) = $",
    "solution": "$(7.5,10.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(30) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $8$ terms of the AP series: $11, 93, 175 ... $",
    "solution": "$2384.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $2073$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$3189.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $39$ terms of the AP series: $-47, -46, -45 ... $",
    "solution": "$-1092.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o303$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-44$ and exact value equals $-19$.",
    "solution": "$131.58\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(45) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 12 & 4 \\\\ 1 & 15 & 5 \\\\ 0 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & -4 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ -1 & 1 & -3 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 58 & 19 \\\\ 75 & 44 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$1127$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $20$ and $16 = $",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 8m$, base width $= 8m$, and height $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$112 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 1 & 8 \\\\ 12 & 4 & 25 \\\\ 3 & 1 & 6 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & -2 & 7 \\\\ -3 & 0 & 4 \\\\ 0 & 1 & -4 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 9m$ and radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$1809 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $3$ and angle $321$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$25.21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $13$ and $3 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $5m, 8m, 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$120 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13\\div54=$",
    "solution": "$0.24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $7$ and $18$?",
    "solution": "$19.31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12.17(2.0\\theta + i12.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$1.41$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-10x-1)(9x-10)$",
    "solution": "$-90x^2+91x+10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-17-5j) * (8+8j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-96-176j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $65$ terms of the AP series: $-32, -55, -78 ... $",
    "solution": "$-49920.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $4m$ is",
    "solution": "$64 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 45m$ and radius $= 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$1552 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $158$ and $110$?",
    "solution": "$35.82$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $10$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{2} + 3x^{3} + 1x^{3} + 6x^{4} + 3x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{8}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{3}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{1}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{6}{4}x^{5} + \\frac{3}{3}x^{4} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-17, -1, 16]\\cdot[20, 3, -4]=$",
    "solution": "$-407$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(81)=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 4 & 8 \\\\ 4 & 12 & 25 \\\\ 1 & 3 & 6 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -3 & 0 & 4 \\\\ 1 & -2 & 7 \\\\ 0 & 1 & -4 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4\\cdot4$",
    "solution": "$16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9.06(-9.0\\theta + i-1.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-3.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(6, -13)$ and $(-4, 10)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{629}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $44=$",
    "solution": "$6082.12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $12$ sided polygon with lengths of $27, 86, 79, 50, 76, 117, 76, 62, 29, 38, 10, 73$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$723$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^3 + 6*x^2 + 4*x + 8$",
    "solution": "${-2 - \\frac{2 \\sqrt{6}}{3}, -2 + \\frac{2 \\sqrt{6}}{3}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -997 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $36, 5, 23, 25, 33, 40, 9, 33, 13, 12, 24, 31, 28, 40, 50$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $26.8$, Standard Deviation is $152.96$, Variance is $12.367699866992245$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $43=$",
    "solution": "$5808.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 1m$ and radius $= 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$1319 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $44$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $7 , 34, 105 =$",
    "solution": "$214$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $2197 = $",
    "solution": "$895$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2004 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2004 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 4x + 4 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-2.0, -2.0)) = (\\frac{-4 + 0}{2*1}, \\frac{-4 - 0}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $34$ and exact value equals $32$.",
    "solution": "$6.25\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $545 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 5, 109, 545]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $26 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$36811.088 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -88 & 89 & 10 & 19 & 52 & -88 \\\\ -43 & -16 & -48 & -11 & -3 & 27 \\\\ 86 & 44 & 8 & 55 & -69 & -67 \\\\ 100 & 29 & -100 & 14 & 84 & -31 \\\\ 55 & -44 & 52 & 10 & -9 & -12 \\\\ -19 & 12 & 95 & 59 & 51 & 41 \\\\ -91 & 69 & -80 & -91 & 93 & -28 \\\\ -36 & -19 & -52 & -42 & -53 & -53 \\\\ -1 & 40 & -79 & -23 & -89 & 45 \\\\ -69 & -40 & 34 & -49 & 38 & 83 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -72 & -7 & -23 & -89 & 22 & 23 & -82 & -45 & -84 & 65 \\\\ -49 & 66 & 56 & 81 & 16 & -30 & 95 & -69 & 22 & 0 \\\\ -79 & 68 & 95 & 34 & 62 & -81 & -22 & -67 & -16 & -57 \\\\ -22 & 50 & 69 & 14 & -96 & 54 & -91 & -39 & -97 & 90 \\\\ 56 & -4 & 63 & -4 & -67 & -16 & 33 & -40 & 49 & 91 \\\\ 66 & 26 & -86 & -47 & 54 & -1 & -79 & 44 & 5 & 88 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -2129 & 5624 & 20113 & 19575 & -9952 & -5222 & 22390 & -9544 & 9455 & -7592 \\\\ 9528 & -3855 & -7737 & -512 & -1463 & 2806 & 1831 & 7992 & 5083 & 1054 \\\\ -18476 & 4130 & 6456 & 377 & -1183 & 4151 & -5037 & -9775 & -15435 & -2091 \\\\ 1629 & -6028 & -1252 & -8634 & -12182 & 8973 & 702 & -5071 & -3559 & 18376 \\\\ -7428 & 471 & 2366 & -5951 & 2725 & -931 & -10093 & -3481 & -7891 & -364 \\\\ -2461 & 11197 & 13892 & 4588 & -1203 & -6163 & -6317 & -8875 & -2679 & 6909 \\\\ 14853 & -5899 & 345 & 10638 & -4865 & -4057 & 29339 & 3291 & 23686 & -3546 \\\\ 2089 & -7804 & -6855 & 2012 & 401 & 2587 & 8551 & 7841 & 4650 & -12643 \\\\ 2845 & -2349 & -16306 & -1438 & 6321 & 5313 & 1221 & 9015 & 323 & -1771 \\\\ 12926 & -289 & -5548 & -682 & 6590 & -6478 & 266 & 7630 & 11402 & -71 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $692 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4, 173, 346, 692]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $2m, 20m, 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$960 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $8$ sided polygon with lengths of $62, 76, 105, 19, 20, 95, 75, 110$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$562$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[4, 48, 576, 6912, 82944, 995328]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 9th term value, sum upto 8th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $4$, common ratio is $12$ , 9th term is $1719926784$, sum upto 8th term is $156356980.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 48m$ and $r1 = 12m$ is and $r2 = 12m$ is ",
    "solution": "$23574.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11110100$",
    "solution": "$244$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $4 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{3}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$14^6 =$",
    "solution": "$7529536$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-6x-7)(5x-8)$",
    "solution": "$-30x^2+13x+56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $18^{2^{7}}$",
    "solution": "$18^{14}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 6x + 9 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-3.0, -3.0)) = (\\frac{-6 + 0}{2*1}, \\frac{-6 - 0}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $44, 31, 26, 26, 7, 5, 38, 34, 33, 43, 32, 33, 46, 40, 15$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $30.2$, Standard Deviation is $148.96$, Variance is $12.204917041913886$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{4} + 5x^{1} + 2x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$5x^{1} + 9x^{4}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $8$ terms of the AP series: $-61, -19, 23 ... $",
    "solution": "$688.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $5$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$21249$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=3*x^3 + 8*x^2 + 6*x + 9$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{8}{9} - \\frac{\\sqrt{10}}{9}, - \\frac{8}{9} + \\frac{\\sqrt{10}}{9}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[578.01, 293.97, 172.23, 982.91, 921.63, 535.92, 886.91, 153.15, 248.29, 25.26, 563.82, 976.38, 998.67, 101.9, 277.25, 594.26]$ and $[497.07, 832.92, 125.88, 821.39, 335.46, 363.3, 682.03, 726.03, 224.81, 994.48, 152.05, 4.16, 436.92, 297.43, 388.11, 67.38]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.86$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 21 =",
    "solution": 159
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $D8DD$ from base $15$ to base $2$.",
    "solution": "$1011001100111011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $ = $",
    "solution": "$$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 58th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$591286729879$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-65-59|=$",
    "solution": "$124$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $16$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$0.28$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 535$ and $SP = 157$ is: ",
    "solution": "$70.65$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[392.87, 889.54, 670.31, 174.08, 238.49, 515.33]$ and $[17.6, 742.31, 384.16, 7.0, 906.88, 705.3]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.64$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $68$",
    "solution": "$2, 2, 17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(2x+5)(-5x+9)$",
    "solution": "$-10x^2-7x+45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 12 m$, base width $= 16 m$ and height $= 44 m$ is",
    "solution": "$2816.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{1} + 5x^{8} + 10x^{5} + 9x^{9} + 1x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{7}{1}x^{2} + \\frac{5}{8}x^{9} + \\frac{10}{5}x^{6} + \\frac{9}{9}x^{10} + \\frac{1}{2}x^{3} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $267A$ from base $11$ to base $9$.",
    "solution": "$4681$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{2}{4}x^{5} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $9760$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$4782.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $12$ and $11 =$",
    "solution": "$132$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $97 = $",
    "solution": "$1100001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 28m$ and $r1 = 1m$ is and $r2 = 1m$ is ",
    "solution": "$1671.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$22 * \\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 2 \\\\ 2 & 4 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 22 & 44 \\\\ 44 & 88 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1000 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$00010$",
    "solution": "$0x2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $18$ and $8 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $750 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 10, 15, 25, 30, 50, 75, 125, 150, 250, 375, 750]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(14,7)$ and $(-7,-9)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$21y = 16x -77$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $52 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$294488.707 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $75$% of $33$?",
    "solution": "$24.75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-70--52|=$",
    "solution": "$18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^3 + 6*x^2 + 10*x + 8$",
    "solution": "${-2 - \\frac{\\sqrt{6}}{3}, -2 + \\frac{\\sqrt{6}}{3}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $18$ and $19$?",
    "solution": "$26.17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $13$ objects picked $5$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$1287$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 * \\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 8 \\\\ 2 & 5 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $91x^2+186x+90=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.79, -1.26}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$615.7521601035994 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $7477$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $6$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$10606.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[545.08, 669.19, 486.35, 389.9, 576.84]$ and $[790.31, 820.95, 130.84, 788.16, 289.56]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.49$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=3*x^3 + 9*x^2 + 2*x + 10$",
    "solution": "${-1 - \\frac{\\sqrt{7}}{3}, -1 + \\frac{\\sqrt{7}}{3}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 7m$ and radius $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$3392 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[9, 19, 24, 29, 36, 48, 52, 67, 83, 98]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $46.5$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $42.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MDLXXVI$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $6 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$452.389 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9204$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$12250.52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $9^{10}$ and $41^{10} = (9/41)^10 = 0.21951219512195122^{10}$",
    "solution": "$2.597685242865939e-07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $23 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$25482.505 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-15y = -90$ and $17x + 19y = -22$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -8$, $y = 6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{1}{6}\\div\\frac{2}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$77$ % $91 = $",
    "solution": "$77$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $60$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[16, 5, -11]\\cdot[-2, 17, -13]=$",
    "solution": "$196$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8^10 =$",
    "solution": "$1073741824$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 888$ and $SP = 146$ is: ",
    "solution": "$83.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$93$ % $20 = $",
    "solution": "$13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $92$% of $33$?",
    "solution": "$30.36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -593 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x + 4 = 7$",
    "solution": "$1/3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$30+15=$",
    "solution": "$45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $38$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $13$ objects picked $9$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$715$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(443989553,40002498)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$14-6=$",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $91 = $",
    "solution": "$1011011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(45) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-6x - 8y = 74$ and $-8x - 5y = 59$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -3$, $y = -7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{1}{4}\\div\\frac{9}{6}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{6}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-18, 19, 15] \\times [8, -19, -8] = $",
    "solution": "$[133, -24, 190]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[73, 1, 51, 44] = $",
    "solution": "$20.12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $3$ and $18 =$",
    "solution": "$18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$110000 = $",
    "solution": "$001111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$95\\div95=$",
    "solution": "$1.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $874 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 19, 23, 38, 46, 437, 874]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $13 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{21}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $19$ objects picked $2$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$342$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$27+46=$",
    "solution": "$73$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[238, 272, 286, 288, 256, 244, 225, 259, 215, 230, 268, 218, 281, 249, 208, 274, 251, 226, 265, 248, 270, 258, 283, 266, 209, 243, 278, 228, 204, 241, 202, 221, 211]$ with $95$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(254.7873877354595, 237.0307940827223)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[3, 23, 37, 48, 63, 77, 87, 93, 94, 95]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $62.0$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $70.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $6637$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1061.92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $62 = $",
    "solution": "$111110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[12, -1, -8] \\times [-19, -11, 9] = $",
    "solution": "$[-97, 44, -151]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $516 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 12, 43, 86, 129, 172, 258, 516]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $925$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$15$ hours and $25$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[239, 222, 295, 258, 203, 240, 236, 268, 283, 281, 204, 255, 201, 202, 230, 247, 220, 212, 289, 251, 219, 206, 260, 272, 248, 256, 294, 270, 291, 250, 276, 273, 215, 269, 278, 218, 286]$ with $99$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(261.6395295748082, 236.57668664140797)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 * \\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 4 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $45^{3}$ and $42^{3} = (45/42)^3 = 1.0714285714285714^{3}$",
    "solution": "$1.2299562682215743$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $33$",
    "solution": "$3, 11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[11, -2, 18]\\cdot[-17, -19, -15]=$",
    "solution": "$-419$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $1m$ is",
    "solution": "$1 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{5}{2}\\cdot\\frac{10}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{25}{4}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[118.87302957216994, 150.12573120288008, 682.8378381670402, 204.81361814757827, 446.77443693757635, 456.1885362232081, 460.563531187722, 213.64329679749306, 601.8552550908227]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1254.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2096 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2096 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $3x + 2y = 25$ and $9x - 6y = 15$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 5$, $y = 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$102\\div6=$",
    "solution": "$17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 4, 5, 8, 9}$, $b={8, 1, 9, 7}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 4, 5, 7, 8, 9}$. Intersection is ${8, 1, 9}$, a-b is ${4, 5}$, b-a is ${7}$. Symmetric difference is ${4, 5, 7}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $9758 = $",
    "solution": "$26114$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{5}{2}\\cdot\\frac{8}{3}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{20}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $1074 = $",
    "solution": "$432$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $60$ and $36 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 12]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $17^{7}$ and $17^{3} = $17^{7-3} = 17^{4}$",
    "solution": "$83521$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $14, 35, 60, 34 = $",
    "solution": "$232.75167785234902$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$176\\div16=$",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 43m$ and radius $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$10131 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $16$ and $12 = $",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $7$ and angle $169$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$72.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{5} + 7x^{8} + 6x^{5} + 5x^{1} + 7x^{7}$",
    "solution": "$40x^{4} + 56x^{7} + 30x^{4} + 5x^{0} + 49x^{6}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $10^{3^{5}}$",
    "solution": "$10^{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{2}{5}\\cdot\\frac{8}{1}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{16}{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[822.3320591162397, 265.94693783825994, 34.35592182151736, 473.2791916280202, 73.89298111154707, 71.40433694076798, 751.3816102841834, 269.6557127722051, 565.4288014347035, 269.974203701285, 885.3866525450925, 820.8694578507855, 298.17136757849016, 742.7385995036155, 476.0161056372504, 137.3446778612376, 149.84547814689986]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2092.55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(352615231,929015959)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 12 m$, base width $= 18 m$ and height $= 18 m$ is",
    "solution": "$1296.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 25m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$728 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{4} + 7x^{5} + 7x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$36x^{3} + 35x^{4} + 28x^{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $8m, 3m, 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$456 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(190725034,405578433)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 52m$, base width $= 12m$, and height $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1968 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $4 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 44 =",
    "solution": 46
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 764$ and $SP = 400$ is: ",
    "solution": "$47.64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-5x = 30$ and $8x + 3y = -78$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -6$, $y = -10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $153 , 16, 16 =$",
    "solution": "$175$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$100011$",
    "solution": "$35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $19x + -13y = 3$ and $14x + 6y = 158$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 7$, $y = 10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $7x + -13y = 59$ and $14x + 18y = 250$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 14$, $y = 3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4! =$",
    "solution": "$24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $95$ and $29 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $66 = $",
    "solution": "$414.69$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3544$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$7061.64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $20$ and $9 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 28m$ and $r1 = 20m$ is and $r2 = 20m$ is ",
    "solution": "$20525.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $87$ of the AP series: $98, 161, 224 ... $",
    "solution": "$5516$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $28 = $",
    "solution": "$11100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-17, 13, -9] \\times [-3, 14, -11] = $",
    "solution": "$[-17, -160, -199]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $12310122$ from base $4$ to base $16$.",
    "solution": "$6D1A$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $192$",
    "solution": "$2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 157 =",
    "solution": 23
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $19$ and $20 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.44\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=94.81$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=91.93\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$4.94$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{1}{3}$ and $\\frac{10}{3}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $47^{9}$ and $9^{9} = (47/9)^9 = 5.222222222222222^{9}$",
    "solution": "$2888671.365810927$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-6, 19, 4] \\times [-7, -6, 11] = $",
    "solution": "$[233, 38, 169]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{2}\\cdot\\frac{4}{10}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 15m$ and $r1 = 18m$ is and $r2 = 18m$ is ",
    "solution": "$8356.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $13$ sides",
    "solution": "$152.31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-5x+8)(5x+10)$",
    "solution": "$-25x^2-10x+80$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $19$ sides",
    "solution": "$161.05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{100}=$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $33$ and angle, $98$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 56.44395$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 16 & 4 & 1 \\\\ 25 & 6 & 2 \\\\ 12 & 3 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 1 & -2 \\\\ 1 & -4 & 7 \\\\ -3 & 0 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-7,7)$ and passing through $(-6.46, 7.84)$ is",
    "solution": "$3.14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $32^{1}$ and $35^{1} = (32/35)^1 = 0.9142857142857143^{1}$",
    "solution": "$0.9142857142857143$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-3,4)$ and passing through $(1.0, 4.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$50.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $11$ and $8 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 1m$ and radius $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$380 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $15x^2 + 96x + 9 = $",
    "solution": "$62.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$78\\div46=$",
    "solution": "$1.7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $673 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 673]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $6.22$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$356.38$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[24, 33, 17, 11] = $",
    "solution": "$19.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^3 + 7*x^2 + 3*x + 6$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{7}{3} - \\frac{2 \\sqrt{10}}{3}, - \\frac{7}{3} + \\frac{2 \\sqrt{10}}{3}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $3m, 1m, 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$36 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $57x^2 + 28x + 80 = $",
    "solution": "$113.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 47th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$2971215073$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -6x + 1$ and $y = -10/4x - 10$",
    "solution": "$(22/7, -125/7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $2.02 \\times 10^{22}$ and $9.71 \\times 10^{41} = $",
    "solution": "$1.96 \\times 10^{64}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $20m$ is",
    "solution": "$8000 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-48-65|=$",
    "solution": "$113$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $0.22$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$12.61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMDCCCVI$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(4, -10)$ and $(4, 0)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{100}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[5, 30, 180, 1080, 6480, 38880]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 8th term value, sum upto 7th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $5$, common ratio is $6$ , 8th term is $1399680$, sum upto 7th term is $279935.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$19-12=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $6x^2 + 7x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.5, -0.667)) = (\\frac{-7 + 1}{2*6}, \\frac{-7 - 1}{2*6})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $5166$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1859.76$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o1007$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $35 = $",
    "solution": "$219.91$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 23m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$678 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$80$ % $41 = $",
    "solution": "$39$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[7, 3, 19] \\times [-10, 3, -11] = $",
    "solution": "$[-90, -113, 51]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $13$ objects picked $1$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[11, -16, 14] \\times [9, -19, -17] = $",
    "solution": "$[538, 313, -65]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $26^{4}$ and $13^{4} = (26/13)^4 = 2.0^{4}$",
    "solution": "$16.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 52m$, base width $= 20m$, and height $= 24m$ is",
    "solution": "$2080 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $9.63 \\times 10^{36}$ and $8.11 \\times 10^{88} = $",
    "solution": "$7.81 \\times 10^{125}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(8x+4)(-7x-4)$",
    "solution": "$-56x^2-60x-16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $7$ sides",
    "solution": "$128.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 23m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$2435 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$15^6 =$",
    "solution": "$11390625$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2026 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2026 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $16$ and $20 =$",
    "solution": "$80$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $85 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$1286220.392 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$52$ % $94 = $",
    "solution": "$52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $2$ and $3 =$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[8, 72, 648, 5832, 52488, 472392]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 9th term value, sum upto 6th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $8$, common ratio is $9$ , 9th term is $344373768$, sum upto 6th term is $531440.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2^9 =$",
    "solution": "$512$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $32=$",
    "solution": "$3216.99$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(20, 2)$ and $(14, 7)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{61}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$108\\div18=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 41th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$165580141$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[4, -18, 0] \\times [0, 17, 7] = $",
    "solution": "$[-126, -28, 68]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$374\\div17=$",
    "solution": "$22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 24m$, base width $= 10m$, and height $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$480 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(15-13j) * (2-13j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-139-221j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.10\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=97.16$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=97.51\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$30.26$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $21$ of the AP series: $-69, 31, 131 ... $",
    "solution": "$1931$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $4$ sides?",
    "solution": "$360$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 31m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$519 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $64 = $",
    "solution": "$1000000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $20$ sides",
    "solution": "$162.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-15, 12)$ and $(-1, 6)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{232}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-2,17)$ and $(0,6)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$2y = -11x + 12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $47^{2^{3}}$",
    "solution": "$47^{6}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $39$ and $19 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10.63(-7.0\\theta + i-8.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $16$ and $9 =$",
    "solution": "$144$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{9}\\cdot\\frac{5}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{24}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$275\\div25=$",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{4} + 2x^{19} + 10x^{15} + 9x^{19} + 6x^{10} + 4x^{7} + 5x^{16} + 10x^{7} + 2x^{1} + 2x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$2x^{1} + 2x^{2} + 5x^{4} + 14x^{7} + 6x^{10} + 10x^{15} + 5x^{16} + 11x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.32\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=91.36$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=91.15\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$3.21$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{13} + 10x^{6} + 7x^{1} + 7x^{2} + 2x^{16} + 6x^{5}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{1} + 7x^{2} + 6x^{5} + 10x^{6} + 5x^{13} + 2x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $241$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$4.21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(30) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 6/4x - 5$ and $y = -7/6x + 8$",
    "solution": "$(39/8, 37/16)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$1350 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $2x^2+109x+73=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.68, -53.82}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$100$",
    "solution": "$0x4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x + 10 = 10$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $5m, 18m, 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$1054 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $4$ sides?",
    "solution": "$360$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{6} + 7x^{4} + 1x^{2} + 10x^{17} + 3x^{9} + 3x^{14} + 2x^{5} + 1x^{9} + 10x^{17}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{2} + 7x^{4} + 2x^{5} + 10x^{6} + 4x^{9} + 3x^{14} + 20x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -753 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $11$ objects picked $1$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[364.09, 286.95, 153.58, 29.33, 321.58, 69.6, 523.15, 869.16, 442.61, 755.76, 818.75, 313.67]$ and $[382.61, 13.57, 896.83, 72.77, 873.77, 418.84, 664.77, 185.38, 529.35, 414.15, 250.44, 285.55]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.85$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$20.4(-20.0\\theta + i4.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$2.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $49, 50, 25, 40, 35, 28, 39, 49, 16, 42, 35, 19, 21, 27, 30$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $33.666666666666664$, Standard Deviation is $115.42222222222223$, Variance is $10.743473471006583$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{661}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$8.71$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[294.68, 62.89, 796.68, 104.23, 918.67, 143.28, 107.38, 38.32, 923.45, 52.68, 252.21, 979.58, 876.02, 239.52, 397.17]$ and $[441.78, 819.87, 598.04, 644.43, 217.84, 407.68, 2.26, 723.97, 422.66, 255.24, 745.5, 989.56, 993.6, 463.49, 886.78]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.73$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $16x + -10y = -520$ and $20x + -8y = -560$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -20$, $y = 20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(68499691,700085630)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $3$ and angle, $44$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 2.30383$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 19 & -27 & 74 & 29 & 86 & 26 \\\\ 90 & 58 & -73 & 76 & 67 & -49 \\\\ -26 & -86 & 72 & -73 & -65 & -70 \\\\ 76 & -87 & -88 & 79 & -27 & -86 \\\\ -31 & 85 & -52 & 57 & -82 & 91 \\\\ 90 & -40 & 55 & -3 & 70 & 25 \\\\ -33 & 13 & 39 & 83 & -7 & -2 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -55 & -48 \\\\ -37 & 82 \\\\ -49 & 46 \\\\ 79 & -55 \\\\ 78 & 30 \\\\ -13 & -23 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4989 & 665 \\\\ 8348 & -3965 \\\\ -8843 & 1183 \\\\ 8604 & -18007 \\\\ -1968 & -1622 \\\\ -1267 & -3380 \\\\ 5460 & -285 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 368$ and $SP = 412$ is: ",
    "solution": "$11.96$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $49, 13, 47, 44, 41, 23, 21, 30, 20, 42, 47, 17, 22, 39, 9$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $30.933333333333334$, Standard Deviation is $177.3955555555555$, Variance is $13.318992287540206$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[5, 25, 31, 37, 46, 48, 66, 73, 80, 85]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $49.6$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $47.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$111101 = $",
    "solution": "$000010$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\tan)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$24.84(-19.0\\theta + i-16.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.44$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $39 = $",
    "solution": "$100111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $3 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $2$ and $12 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $16m, 8m, 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$768 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(16+16j) * (-1-9j) = $",
    "solution": "$(128-160j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{7}{5}$ and $\\frac{1}{4}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o4242$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 435$ and $SP = 202$ is: ",
    "solution": "$53.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=5*x^3 + 8*x^2 + 3*x + 2$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{8}{15} - \\frac{\\sqrt{19}}{15}, - \\frac{8}{15} + \\frac{\\sqrt{19}}{15}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $1$ and $87 = $",
    "solution": "$92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $8$ sides",
    "solution": "$135.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-19, 20, -4]\\cdot[-16, 3, -18]=$",
    "solution": "$436$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $38 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$114923.648 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $78408$ from base $9$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$52091$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $94x^2 + 90x + 49 = $",
    "solution": "$125.3333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $13m$ is",
    "solution": "$2197 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $12$ and height, $26$?",
    "solution": "$1960.35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{3}\\div\\frac{2}{10}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{40}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[255.8534508640171, 593.1714034878702, 406.5179468298192, 299.22513897272165, 746.7263589484735, 589.9077152925279, 516.4064933177591, 642.8658860753195, 626.1534651622821, 267.773786611579, 930.0147386593102, 628.0624696501617, 977.1498678003785, 132.6558750411222, 178.55243019643373, 773.7969738319687, 300.09264099853914, 664.7604496850356, 952.0942445130903, 643.1558064566262]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2726.9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $16^{5}$ and $16^{8} = $16^{5-8} = 16^{-3}$",
    "solution": "$0.000244140625$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $55 m = $",
    "solution": "$696909.9703213357 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $265 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 5, 53, 265]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $5$ and $20 = $",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $8$ sided polygon with lengths of $118, 66, 46, 2, 47, 113, 43, 94$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$529$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(9,-1)$ and passing through $(8.0, -1.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$3.14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $-6$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$21.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -6 & 74 & -72 \\\\ -75 & -60 & -36 \\\\ 71 & 73 & 95 \\\\ 1 & 27 & 16 \\\\ -52 & -79 & -79 \\\\ 71 & -44 & -54 \\\\ -60 & 79 & -96 \\\\ 3 & -32 & 65 \\\\ -10 & -18 & 21 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -40 & 51 & 69 & 86 & -13 & 60 & 18 & 86 & 82 & -88 \\\\ 15 & 2 & -55 & 53 & -61 & 6 & -11 & 40 & -59 & 22 \\\\ 66 & -92 & -59 & -16 & -84 & 71 & 27 & 40 & -42 & -34 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -3402 & 6466 & -236 & 4558 & 1612 & -5028 & -2866 & -436 & -1834 & 4604 \\\\ -276 & -633 & 249 & -9054 & 7659 & -7416 & -1662 & -10290 & -1098 & 6504 \\\\ 4525 & -4973 & -4721 & 8455 & -13356 & 11443 & 3040 & 12826 & -2475 & -7872 \\\\ 1421 & -1367 & -2360 & 1261 & -3004 & 1358 & 153 & 1806 & -2183 & -38 \\\\ -4319 & 4458 & 5418 & -7395 & 12131 & -9203 & -2200 & -10792 & 3715 & 5524 \\\\ -7064 & 8501 & 10505 & 4638 & 6297 & 162 & 304 & 2186 & 10686 & -5380 \\\\ -2751 & 5930 & -2821 & 563 & 4025 & -9942 & -4541 & -5840 & -5549 & 10282 \\\\ 3690 & -5891 & -1868 & -2478 & -3547 & 4603 & 2161 & 1578 & -596 & -3178 \\\\ 1516 & -2478 & -939 & -2150 & -536 & 783 & 585 & -740 & -640 & -230 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $3.4 \\times 10^{-60}$ and $4.23 \\times 10^{92} = $",
    "solution": "$1.44 \\times 10^{33}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $26^{4}$ and $26^{10} = $26^{4-10} = 26^{-6}$",
    "solution": "$3.2371282973906776e-09$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $790$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$13$ hours and $10$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $58$ terms of the AP series: $-83, -14, 55 ... $",
    "solution": "$109243.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $14$ and $29$?",
    "solution": "$69.77$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 19m$ and $r1 = 15m$ is and $r2 = 15m$ is ",
    "solution": "$4795.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-4x + 2y = -24$ and $4x + 9y = -20$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 4$, $y = -4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(5x+1)(3x-1)$",
    "solution": "$15x^2-2x-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $40^{3}$ and $10^{3} = (40/10)^3 = 4.0^{3}$",
    "solution": "$64.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{3}\\div\\frac{2}{5}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{35}{6}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $649 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 11, 59, 649]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $110001 = $",
    "solution": "$1111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$87$ % $29 = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $86$ and $17 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 453$ and $SP = 63$ is: ",
    "solution": "$86.09$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-18,7)$ and $(4,-15)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$y = -x -11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $14m, 12m, 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$960 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $5138$ from base $10$ to base $16$.",
    "solution": "$1412$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 8 & 4 \\\\ 0 & 3 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 2 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & -4 \\\\ 0 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 0 & -2 & 3 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 18m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$2230 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 38m$ and radius $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$3954 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o7054$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 9x + 6 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.814, -3.686)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{33}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{33}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$14^5 =$",
    "solution": "$537824$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9^2=$",
    "solution": "$81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $45x^2+135x+56=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.5, -2.5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 69th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$117669030460994$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 65 =",
    "solution": 25
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 6x - 2$ and $y = x + 1$",
    "solution": "$(3/5, 8/5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $18m$ is",
    "solution": "$5832 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $7, 48, 30, 98 = $",
    "solution": "$472.9093147312269$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-43$ and exact value equals $-16$.",
    "solution": "$168.75\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $82$ and $27 = $",
    "solution": "$71$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 647 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $126$ and $93$?",
    "solution": "$30.14$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $3$ sides",
    "solution": "$60.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0110$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-8,-13)$ and $(16,-9)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$6y = x -70$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$201.06192982974676 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $5$ and $190$?",
    "solution": "$189.74$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 7x - 3$ and $y = 5/3x + 2$",
    "solution": "$(15/16, 57/16)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9\\cdot9$",
    "solution": "$81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$162\\div18=$",
    "solution": "$9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 7x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.314, -3.186)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{33}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{33}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 502$ and $SP = 225$ is: ",
    "solution": "$55.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(x+5)(-5x+9)$",
    "solution": "$x^2-25x+45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 2 & 8 & 41 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 25 \\\\ 1 & 4 & 20 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -4 & 5 \\\\ -5 & 1 & 9 \\\\ 1 & 0 & -2 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{993}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.98$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 10 & 2 \\\\ 3 & 31 & 6 \\\\ 1 & 15 & 3 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 0 & -2 \\\\ -3 & 1 & 0 \\\\ 14 & -5 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $41$ and angle $221$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$3241.96$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$44+6=$",
    "solution": "$50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$24\\div4=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x + 1 = 10$",
    "solution": "$9/5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $3$ numbers $[67, 3, 47] = $",
    "solution": "$21.14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 2m$ and radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$502 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $17^{3}$ and $17^{2} = $17^{3-2} = 17^{1}$",
    "solution": "$17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 24m$, base width $= 8m$, and height $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$528 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 29m$ and radius $= 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$2459 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $19$ and angle, $162$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 53.72123$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $530 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 5, 10, 53, 106, 265, 530]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 2, 4, 6, 10}$, $b={8, 10, 4, 5}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${10, 4}$, a-b is ${1, 2, 6}$, b-a is ${8, 5}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 2, 5, 6, 8}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $79^{\\frac{1}{7}}$ _ $6^{\\frac{1}{1}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^3 + 4*x^2 + 5*x + 4$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{5}{3}, -1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $20$ objects picked $9$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$167960$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 41 & 11 & 12 & -91 & 86 \\\\ 14 & -2 & -4 & -96 & 29 \\\\ 47 & -69 & -74 & 79 & 50 \\\\ 99 & -57 & -73 & 55 & -62 \\\\ -78 & -29 & -11 & 92 & -31 \\\\ 88 & -42 & 78 & -56 & -9 \\\\ 63 & 30 & -56 & -38 & -20 \\\\ 22 & -35 & -23 & -30 & -80 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -27 & -100 & 10 & -72 & 24 & -36 & 43 & -20 & 20 & -19 \\\\ 39 & 99 & 12 & 66 & 65 & -69 & -25 & 20 & 36 & 75 \\\\ -20 & 39 & 45 & 18 & -81 & 64 & 27 & 54 & 90 & -53 \\\\ 29 & -78 & 4 & 75 & 34 & 92 & 0 & 89 & 5 & 100 \\\\ 6 & -46 & 29 & -84 & -17 & -67 & 1 & 50 & 99 & -81 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -3041 & 599 & 3212 & -16059 & -3829 & -15601 & 1898 & -3751 & 10355 & -16656 \\\\ -2986 & 4400 & 393 & -10848 & -3227 & -11397 & 573 & -7630 & 2239 & -12153 \\\\ 111 & -22879 & -1922 & -7545 & 4473 & 2251 & 1798 & 3215 & -2859 & 1704 \\\\ -2213 & -19828 & -4557 & -2871 & 7508 & 4911 & 3649 & -5267 & -12505 & 8235 \\\\ 3677 & -1250 & -2154 & 13008 & 789 & 14646 & -2957 & 7024 & -6203 & 11601 \\\\ -7252 & -5134 & 3401 & -11148 & -8687 & 173 & 6931 & -3822 & 6097 & -13827 \\\\ -633 & -1630 & -2262 & -4734 & 7046 & -10078 & 427 & -8066 & -4870 & 1841 \\\\ -2849 & -542 & -3675 & 162 & 456 & 2751 & 1120 & -9052 & -10960 & 1656 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-69$ and exact value equals $-66$.",
    "solution": "$4.55\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $16$ objects picked $9$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$4151347200$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{12} + 2x^{5} + 3x^{13} + 10x^{1} + 8x^{5} + 9x^{14} + 5x^{3} + 10x^{10} + 8x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$18x^{1} + 5x^{3} + 10x^{5} + 10x^{10} + 2x^{12} + 3x^{13} + 9x^{14}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $10^{1}$ and $10^{6} = $10^{1-6} = 10^{-5}$",
    "solution": "$1e-05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $20^{9^{9}}$",
    "solution": "$20^{81}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 34m$ and radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$226 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6! =$",
    "solution": "$720$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $3^{10^{8}}$",
    "solution": "$3^{80}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11010001$",
    "solution": "$0xd1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$92$ % $74 = $",
    "solution": "$18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 12 & 1 & 4 \\\\ 3 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 4 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -1 & 1 \\\\ 1 & -4 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 4 & -3 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $51=$",
    "solution": "$8171.28$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|97-7|=$",
    "solution": "$90$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{1}{4}$ and $\\frac{3}{1}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 84th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$160500643816367552$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $10$ objects picked $6$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$210$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(10,4)$ and passing through $(18.0, 4.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$201.06$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-10, -19)$ and $(-7, 8)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{738}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $2^{5}$ and $47^{5} = (2/47)^5 = 0.0425531914893617^{5}$",
    "solution": "$1.3952778139181375e-07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3868$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$4264.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $9$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$38020$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $10m, 11m, 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$220 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10101010 = $",
    "solution": "$01010101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{10}\\div\\frac{5}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{6}{25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o1753$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$59-49=$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-4, -11, 14]\\cdot[-13, -6, -8]=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-3x-8)(8x+9)$",
    "solution": "$-24x^2-91x-72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 838$ and $SP = 582$ is: ",
    "solution": "$30.55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(45) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $15, 18 25 = $",
    "solution": "$133.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-44--2|=$",
    "solution": "$42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$39\\div13=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-49-92|=$",
    "solution": "$141$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 40th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$102334155$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 4x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.586, -3.414)) = (\\frac{-4 + \\sqrt{8}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-4 - \\sqrt{8}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[431.71, 746.51, 784.75]$ and $[772.45, 74.12, 917.0]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.66$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 10m$ and $r1 = 4m$ is and $r2 = 4m$ is ",
    "solution": "$4743.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[246, 288, 232, 211, 264, 277, 225, 249, 216, 204, 298, 231, 213, 209, 254, 259, 222, 267, 294, 252, 251, 238, 282, 235, 274, 296, 272, 237, 208, 233, 260, 200]$ with $95$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(256.66007350573295, 236.90242649426705)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1964 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1964 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $82 m = $",
    "solution": "$2309564.8776326627 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x + 10 = 10$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=10*x^2 + x + 7$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{1}{20}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{637}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$8.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $4549$ from base $10$ to base $7$.",
    "solution": "$16156$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 22m$ and radius $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$5897 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $5$ sides",
    "solution": "$108.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(6,16)$ and $(-14,-14) = $",
    "solution": "$(-4.0,1.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $63$",
    "solution": "$3, 3, 7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $52$ and exact value equals $82$.",
    "solution": "$36.59\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $43 = $",
    "solution": "$270.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $5.08$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$291.06$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 5x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.219, -2.281)) = (\\frac{-5 + \\sqrt{17}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-5 - \\sqrt{17}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(8+1j) * (19+9j) = $",
    "solution": "$(143+91j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $10 = $",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $29$ terms of the AP series: $-87, -62, -37 ... $",
    "solution": "$7627.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{10} + 9x^{9} + 5x^{6} + 6x^{9} + 6x^{5}$",
    "solution": "$30x^{9} + 81x^{8} + 30x^{5} + 54x^{8} + 30x^{4}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[212, 233, 294, 248, 208, 281, 249, 296, 220, 282, 293, 232, 253, 265, 275, 213, 273, 297, 230, 246, 268, 226, 264, 215, 250, 287, 285]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(264.43386647504684, 246.3068742656939)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $4$ and height, $32$?",
    "solution": "$804.25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8^2=$",
    "solution": "$64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $17x + 14y = 224$ and $3x + 19y = 23$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 14$, $y = -1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 13 m$, base width $= 8 m$ and height $= 24 m$ is",
    "solution": "$832.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(348284801,561133837)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$69$ % $32 = $",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 12 & 1 \\\\ 15 & 61 & 5 \\\\ 4 & 16 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 19 & -4 & 1 \\\\ -5 & 1 & 0 \\\\ 4 & 0 & -3 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMDCCCXLII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{4} + 2x^{2} + 4x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$28x^{3} + 4x^{1} + 36x^{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $8$ of the AP series: $33, -64, -161 ... $",
    "solution": "$-646$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$294\\div14=$",
    "solution": "$21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $3m, 16m, 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$552 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x + 2 = 9$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 99 & -84 \\\\ 83 & -6 \\\\ -66 & 8 \\\\ -5 & -86 \\\\ 46 & 26 \\\\ 90 & 54 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -89 & 61 & 83 \\\\ -79 & -80 & -20 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -2175 & 12759 & 9897 \\\\ -6913 & 5543 & 7009 \\\\ 5242 & -4666 & -5638 \\\\ 7239 & 6575 & 1305 \\\\ -6148 & 726 & 3298 \\\\ -12276 & 1170 & 6390 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4^2=$",
    "solution": "$16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(2)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 55$ and $SP = 81$ is: ",
    "solution": "$47.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $17$ and $11 =$",
    "solution": "$187$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $26$ and $67 = $",
    "solution": "$87$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $7$ sided polygon with lengths of $78, 82, 50, 54, 37, 28, 23$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$352$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $39$ terms of the AP series: $-63, -31, 1 ... $",
    "solution": "$21255.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-7-7j) * (-3+10j) = $",
    "solution": "$(91-49j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[11, 19, 21, 22, 25, 41, 65, 71, 92, 97]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $46.4$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $33.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 14m$, base width $= 50m$, and height $= 24m$ is",
    "solution": "$1400 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $10 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{27}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $4$ sides?",
    "solution": "$360$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $91$ of the AP series: $-7, -17, -27 ... $",
    "solution": "$-907$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\tan)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $61$ and exact value equals $94$.",
    "solution": "$35.11\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={3, 5, 6}$, $b={8, 10, 3, 7}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${3, 5, 6, 7, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${3}$, a-b is ${5, 6}$, b-a is ${8, 10, 7}$. Symmetric difference is ${5, 6, 7, 8, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $5m, 6m, 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$412 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $18$ objects picked $1$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $35.67$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $15$ pistons will contain no more than $2$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$5.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[9, -4, 15]\\cdot[3, 2, -13]=$",
    "solution": "$-176$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|88--35|=$",
    "solution": "$123$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={8, 9, 2, 5}$, $b={1, 2, 5, 8, 10}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 5, 8, 9, 10}$. Intersection is ${8, 2, 5}$, a-b is ${9}$, b-a is ${1, 10}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{1} + 10x^{10} + 1x^{5}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{7}{1}x^{2} + \\frac{10}{10}x^{11} + \\frac{1}{5}x^{6} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $6.5 \\times 10^{49}$ and $6.96 \\times 10^{-75} = $",
    "solution": "$4.52 \\times 10^{-25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[251, 265, 292, 275, 225, 230, 229, 291, 208, 253, 247, 269, 289, 266, 240, 282, 235, 286, 202, 227, 216, 206, 258, 222, 252, 281, 288, 295, 284, 268, 242, 239, 226]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(260.66259063726113, 244.73134875667822)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $11$ and $16 =$",
    "solution": "$176$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $10101 = $",
    "solution": "$1011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 5x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.5, -2.0)) = (\\frac{-5 + 3}{2*2}, \\frac{-5 - 3}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6^7 =$",
    "solution": "$279936$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $5$ sides",
    "solution": "$108.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $64$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$147.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $16, 15, 39, 31, 24, 34, 11, 17, 31, 11, 17, 25, 33, 40, 12$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $23.733333333333334$, Standard Deviation is $98.99555555555555$, Variance is $9.949651026822778$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-1,6)$ and passing through $(3.8600000000000003, 13.57)$ is",
    "solution": "$254.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.23\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=91.55$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=98.22\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$10.6$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $18$% of $54$?",
    "solution": "$9.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[72.41, 801.88, 959.47, 35.27, 540.94, 232.9, 116.47, 468.18, 728.18]$ and $[618.01, 93.57, 842.88, 607.55, 887.42, 716.19, 97.46, 68.45, 884.57]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.74$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(391348417,713249318)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 31m$ and $r1 = 1m$ is and $r2 = 1m$ is ",
    "solution": "$97.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$37\\div1=$",
    "solution": "$37.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3 * \\begin{bmatrix} 8 & 8 \\\\ 4 & 9 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 24 & 24 \\\\ 12 & 27 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$40+0=$",
    "solution": "$40$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 2 & 4 \\\\ 1 & 1 & 2 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -1 & 2 & 0 \\\\ 1 & -1 & -2 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $5.96$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$341.48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(4)=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $336$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$5.86$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{1} + 5x^{8} + 5x^{1} + 7x^{13} + 4x^{16} + 4x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{1} + 4x^{3} + 5x^{8} + 7x^{13} + 4x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 1 & 1 \\\\ 6 & 2 & 1 \\\\ 7 & 2 & 2 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -2 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 5 & 1 & -3 \\\\ 2 & -1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 50 & 48 \\\\ 15 & 20 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$280$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{2}\\div\\frac{7}{5}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $103$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$1.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(7+14j) * (-4+8j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-140+0j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 58 =",
    "solution": 32
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 22m$ and radius $= 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$1753 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[11, -3, 0] \\times [3, -20, -13] = $",
    "solution": "$[39, 143, -211]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{2}\\div\\frac{5}{7}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{28}{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$010$",
    "solution": "$0x2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(10x+9)(6x+4)$",
    "solution": "$60x^2+94x+36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={3, 5, 7}$, $b={8, 1, 10, 3}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 3, 5, 7, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${3}$, a-b is ${5, 7}$, b-a is ${8, 1, 10}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 5, 7, 8, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $11AA6$ from base $14$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$43266$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 19m$ and radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$4536 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $649 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 11, 59, 649]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $10101000 = $",
    "solution": "$1011000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0001110 = $",
    "solution": "$1110001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $4$ sides",
    "solution": "$90.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{10} + 8x^{3} + 5x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{10}x^{11} + \\frac{8}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{5}{2}x^{3} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 2, 9, 7}$, $b={8, 10, 4, 6}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 4, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10}$. Intersection is $set()$, a-b is ${1, 2, 9, 7}$, b-a is ${8, 10, 4, 6}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 2, 4, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $4m$ is",
    "solution": "$64 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9j * (-16+12j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-108-144j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[239.54, 215.05, 191.82, 170.15, 555.52, 365.45, 551.27, 254.37, 169.1, 765.41, 590.74, 115.89, 45.86, 254.62, 80.39, 692.87, 478.43, 468.24, 712.97, 92.74]$ and $[573.68, 546.48, 438.38, 884.95, 880.49, 191.55, 666.29, 776.73, 978.48, 379.36, 831.56, 557.2, 146.99, 313.48, 144.05, 421.14, 942.75, 174.42, 250.45, 820.59]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.73$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cos)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\sin$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$100011$",
    "solution": "$35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{7}\\div\\frac{3}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4\\div2=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11 * \\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 4 \\\\ 7 & 2 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 11 & 44 \\\\ 77 & 22 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-5,-2)$ and $(18,-13) = $",
    "solution": "$(6.5,-7.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11110111$",
    "solution": "$0xf7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $89$ and $68 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $30$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $4 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $42^{4}$ and $42^{6} = $42^{4-6} = 42^{-2}$",
    "solution": "$0.0005668934240362812$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-5x-24$",
    "solution": "$(x+3)(x-8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $0.53$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$30.37$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[6, 19, 21, 43, 47, 58, 67, 77, 92, 98]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $52.8$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $52.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $3$ sided polygon with lengths of $120, 6, 114$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$240$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={9, 4, 7}$, $b={1, 10, 6}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10}$. Intersection is $set()$, a-b is ${9, 4, 7}$, b-a is ${1, 10, 6}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $34$% of $36$?",
    "solution": "$12.24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $48, 28, 17, 45, 36, 17, 43, 48, 40, 18, 44, 45, 35, 6, 34$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $33.6$, Standard Deviation is $167.17333333333335$, Variance is $12.929552712036614$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $11$ sided polygon with lengths of $48, 24, 42, 7, 22, 49, 36, 59, 36, 11, 57$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$391$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{10}\\div\\frac{6}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{8}{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|92--13|=$",
    "solution": "$105$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[14, 23, 43, 45, 46, 47, 59, 67, 85, 94]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $52.3$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $46.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 27m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$393 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $17=$",
    "solution": "$907.92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{100}=$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{6}\\cdot\\frac{3}{2}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{24}{12}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $26=$",
    "solution": "$2123.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5! =$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $5$ and $6 =$",
    "solution": "$30$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $36.48$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $14$ pistons will contain no more than $7$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$90.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $3x^2 + 7x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.333, -2.0)) = (\\frac{-7 + 5}{2*3}, \\frac{-7 - 5}{2*3})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[6, 11, 24, 25, 45, 49, 53, 55, 65, 81]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $41.4$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $47.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $2.44$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$139.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $16$ and height, $5$?",
    "solution": "$502.65$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=2*x^2 + 4*x + 9$",
    "solution": "${-1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[10, 30, 90, 270, 810, 2430]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 6th term value, sum upto 7th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $10$, common ratio is $3$ , 6th term is $2430$, sum upto 7th term is $10930.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $2417 = $",
    "solution": "$971$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $27 = $",
    "solution": "$11011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $37$ and angle $11$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$131.41$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[7, 28, 112, 448, 1792, 7168]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 9th term value, sum upto 7th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $7$, common ratio is $4$ , 9th term is $458752$, sum upto 7th term is $38227.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{7}\\cdot\\frac{10}{5}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{8}{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $3.8$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$217.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10^2=$",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $6$ sides",
    "solution": "$120.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $17, 38, 21, 23, 43, 5, 41, 43, 42, 40, 5, 40, 27, 14, 37$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $29.066666666666666$, Standard Deviation is $181.12888888888887$, Variance is $13.458413312455852$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $4239$ dollars, $2$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$4966.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $8.04 \\times 10^{70}$ and $7.63 \\times 10^{-10} = $",
    "solution": "$6.13 \\times 10^{61}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(18-20j) * (-20-14j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-640+148j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $38$ and $31 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12-6=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $9$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$0.16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 7}$, $b={8, 10, 6, 7}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 6, 7, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${7}$, a-b is ${1}$, b-a is ${8, 10, 6}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 6, 8, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $265 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 5, 53, 265]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cot)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1010001$",
    "solution": "$81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $3435$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$309.15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1^2=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 15m$ and radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$17011 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $2133 = $",
    "solution": "$855$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $154 , 39, 63 =$",
    "solution": "$104$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $11$ objects picked $9$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 50m$, base width $= 20m$, and height $= 24m$ is",
    "solution": "$1870 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $7565 = $",
    "solution": "$113813$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $44^{8}$ and $28^{8} = (44/28)^8 = 1.5714285714285714^{8}$",
    "solution": "$37.18409030944866$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(3,6)$ and passing through $(5.16, 9.370000000000001)$ is",
    "solution": "$50.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $51 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$277823.605 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 95 & 83 \\\\ 26 & 14 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-828$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11^3 =$",
    "solution": "$1331$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[136.6340152031813, 313.0724524990299, 656.75930987406, 11.639295214537771, 855.1690705795652, 731.8705262960987, 616.7389417464839, 845.905960456182, 134.44358158870617, 525.5186650827089, 314.4072483889365]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1817.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(729)=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^3 + 9*x^2 + 9*x + 6$",
    "solution": "${-3 - \\sqrt{6}, -3 + \\sqrt{6}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=3*x^3 + 10*x^2 + x + 4$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{10}{9} - \\frac{\\sqrt{91}}{9}, - \\frac{10}{9} + \\frac{\\sqrt{91}}{9}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $1$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$4966$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7^2=$",
    "solution": "$49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(90) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $12$ and $8 = $",
    "solution": "$160$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $33 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$75266.277 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $1.14 \\times 10^{-88}$ and $7.37 \\times 10^{37} = $",
    "solution": "$8.4 \\times 10^{-51}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $29$ and $92 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1101101011$",
    "solution": "$875$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-1x + 2y = 45$ and $11x + 14y = 153$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -9$, $y = 18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $16, 28, 36, 41, 39, 48, 26, 12, 32, 33, 5, 19, 31, 26, 42$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $28.933333333333334$, Standard Deviation is $133.66222222222223$, Variance is $11.561237919108066$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $9711$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$3107.52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $180 , 58, 86 =$",
    "solution": "$36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{495}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$7.91$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{776}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 17m$ and radius $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$376 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 41m$ and radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$171 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $18$ objects picked $0$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $4$ sided polygon with lengths of $97, 113, 58, 34$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$302$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 9 m$, base width $= 4 m$ and height $= 48 m$ is",
    "solution": "$576.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $39$ and $60$?",
    "solution": "$42.42$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $4.8 \\times 10^{80}$ and $4.7 \\times 10^{11} = $",
    "solution": "$2.26 \\times 10^{92}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(15,-5)$ and $(1,7)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$7y = -6x + 55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[15, 20, 32, 33, 65, 66, 74, 81, 84, 97]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $56.7$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $65.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(953807519,668759547)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^2 + 3*x + 3$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{3}{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-84$ and exact value equals $-57$.",
    "solution": "$47.37\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 11 & 54 \\\\ 98 & 44 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-4808$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|22-7|=$",
    "solution": "$15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 313 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$2400 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $43$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$0.75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 50m$, base width $= 32m$, and height $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$2734 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o6326$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 93 & 1 \\\\ 87 & 14 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$1215$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $10$ and angle $202$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$176.28$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5\\cdot0$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $2$ and $1 =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $91x^2 + 49x + 4 = $",
    "solution": "$58.8333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $19x + 14y = -393$ and $1x + -3y = -2$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -17$, $y = -5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $8235$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1976.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.52\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=90.46$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=93.94\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$18.73$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 43m$ and radius $= 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$1496 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $61=$",
    "solution": "$11689.87$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $706 = $",
    "solution": "$0x2c2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $98x^2+90x+17=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.27, -0.65}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $10x^2 + 67x + 54 = $",
    "solution": "$90.8333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[601.35, 321.67, 747.19, 117.08, 572.28]$ and $[486.03, 53.36, 22.41, 969.91, 125.32]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1.16$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$50.26548245743669 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 12 =",
    "solution": 78
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $3635 = $",
    "solution": "$1433$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 991$ and $SP = 328$ is: ",
    "solution": "$66.9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 12 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 4 & 0 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 5 & -4 \\\\ 0 & -1 & 1 \\\\ 1 & -3 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233, 377, 610$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 2 m$, base width $= 18 m$ and height $= 28 m$ is",
    "solution": "$336.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $94 = $",
    "solution": "$590.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$58-53=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $33$ and angle, $26$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 14.97492$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$50.26548245743669 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{1}{8}\\cdot\\frac{7}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{7}{64}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{16}=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[11, -8, 2] \\times [-2, -17, -1] = $",
    "solution": "$[42, 7, -203]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-17,-4)$ and $(-13,3)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$4y = 7x + 103$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $87 = $",
    "solution": "$1010111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6 * \\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 5 \\\\ 7 & 1 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 36 & 30 \\\\ 42 & 6 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $34.22$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $15$ pistons will contain no more than $8$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$96.35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[290.70973009620195, 560.7353699507539, 458.78665925492754, 672.0032694741037]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1030.05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(4x+6)(3x-10)$",
    "solution": "$12x^2-22x-60$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $8m, 20m, 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$2400 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 351 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $63, 28, 69, 68 = $",
    "solution": "$841.7306532663317$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$308\\div22=$",
    "solution": "$14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 126 =",
    "solution": 54
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $5^{8^{10}}$",
    "solution": "$5^{80}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $30 = $",
    "solution": "$188.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $47, 28, 18, 50, 38, 30, 29, 21, 6, 31, 15, 36, 17, 48, 16$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $28.666666666666668$, Standard Deviation is $165.55555555555554$, Variance is $12.866839377079188$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $683$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$11$ hours and $23$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMCCCVIII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $3x^2 + 9x + 5 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.736, -2.264)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{21}}{2*3}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{21}}{2*3})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{121}=$",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $47$ terms of the AP series: $-49, -130, -211 ... $",
    "solution": "$-89864.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $13$ objects picked $0$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $19m, 5m, 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$1235 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[11, 44, 176, 704, 2816, 11264]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 10th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $11$, common ratio is $4$ , 10th term is $2883584$, sum upto 10th term is $3844775.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$452.3893421169302 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 26m$ and radius $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$9883 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $85$ and $0$?",
    "solution": "$200.0$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $3$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0101$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $6 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{10}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $3 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $12m, 10m, 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$416 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $10$ and $8$?",
    "solution": "$12.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[4, 11, 20, 25, 39, 60, 72, 80, 92, 98]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $50.1$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $49.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $59x^2 + 47x + 70 = $",
    "solution": "$113.1667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $20m$ is",
    "solution": "$8000 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x + 3 = 5$",
    "solution": "$2/7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $34 = $",
    "solution": "$100010$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-6,8)$ and passing through $(1.0, 8.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$153.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $72$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[5, 15, 45, 135, 405, 1215]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 7th term value, sum upto 8th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $5$, common ratio is $3$ , 7th term is $3645$, sum upto 8th term is $16400.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $40$ terms of the AP series: $-77, -24, 29 ... $",
    "solution": "$38260.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $14$ and $66 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $70$ and $54 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$74\\div83=$",
    "solution": "$0.89$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{144}=$",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-13, 5, 18]\\cdot[-15, 7, 17]=$",
    "solution": "$536$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $99x^2+195x+73=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.5, -1.47}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $199$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$3$ hours and $19$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{8}\\div\\frac{9}{7}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{7}{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(3,-11)$ and $(3,-9) = $",
    "solution": "$(3.0,-10.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 23 =",
    "solution": 157
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $1110001100011101$ from base $2$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$58141$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $100 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$2094395.102 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $95$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-10,-4)$ and $(-3,-3) = $",
    "solution": "$(-6.5,-3.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $44^{3}$ and $18^{3} = (44/18)^3 = 2.4444444444444446^{3}$",
    "solution": "$14.606310013717424$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 663$ and $SP = 801$ is: ",
    "solution": "$20.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $89, 58, 72 = $",
    "solution": "$1699.467039248063$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(0,-5)$ and $(-7,8)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$7y = -13x -35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $9F18$ from base $16$ to base $6$.",
    "solution": "$512320$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $1011010010100011$ from base $2$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$46243$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9-0=$",
    "solution": "$9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$81\\div58=$",
    "solution": "$1.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[25, 68, 97, 61] = $",
    "solution": "$56.32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $8x + 1y = -38$ and $7x + -1y = -37$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -5$, $y = 2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $4.64$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$265.85$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 18m$, base width $= 30m$, and height $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1080 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $82$ and $20 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-9,-12)$ and $(2,8)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$11y = 20x + 48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$25-4=$",
    "solution": "$21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $6$ sides",
    "solution": "$120.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 21 =",
    "solution": 69
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-98--69|=$",
    "solution": "$29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-20,-14)$ and $(17,-14)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$y = -14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{746}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $4372$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$4829.41$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $82x^2 + 88x + 88 = $",
    "solution": "$159.3333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $9$ and $2 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{16} + 3x^{6} + 5x^{18} + 2x^{2} + 10x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$2x^{2} + 3x^{6} + 10x^{10} + 2x^{16} + 5x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[18, 4, 20] \\times [-10, -4, 7] = $",
    "solution": "$[108, -326, -32]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $40x^2 + 60x + 74 = $",
    "solution": "$117.3333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $51, 66 = $",
    "solution": "$1898.7692307692307$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $131 , 99, 95 =$",
    "solution": "$35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7\\cdot1$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $36.43$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $20$ pistons will contain no more than $2$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$0.87$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 26m$ and radius $= 1m$ is",
    "solution": "$84 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 19 m$, base width $= 16 m$ and height $= 35 m$ is",
    "solution": "$3546.6666666666665 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(3, -15)$ and $(8, 21)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{1321}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=5*x^2 + 5*x + 4$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{1}{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $94=$",
    "solution": "$27759.11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $8m$ is",
    "solution": "$512 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $18^{5}$ and $28^{5} = (18/28)^5 = 0.6428571428571429^{5}$",
    "solution": "$0.10979242280002384$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $23$ and $24 = $",
    "solution": "$[1]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $7, 37, 46, 13, 39, 26, 42, 31, 21, 31, 6, 32, 21, 14, 33$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $26.6$, Standard Deviation is $146.64000000000001$, Variance is $12.109500402576483$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-17, -10, -11]\\cdot[1, -8, -14]=$",
    "solution": "$217$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(1,-14)$ and $(-11,-2) = $",
    "solution": "$(-5.0,-8.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $43, 6, 41, 21, 15, 8, 11, 19, 30, 38, 49, 33, 48, 10, 44$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $27.733333333333334$, Standard Deviation is $227.66222222222223$, Variance is $15.088479784995645$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $20m$ is",
    "solution": "$8000 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{1}{9}$ and $\\frac{7}{4}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $322$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$5$ hours and $22$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o5621$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $83$ and $91$?",
    "solution": "$9.2$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[3, 49, 52, 69, 71, 75, 77, 92, 94, 98]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $68.0$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $73.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $273 = $",
    "solution": "$0x111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -69 & 96 & 11 \\\\ 75 & 22 & 84 \\\\ 92 & 64 & -91 \\\\ 35 & -73 & -34 \\\\ 30 & 70 & 45 \\\\ -46 & -97 & 30 \\\\ 60 & 66 & 49 \\\\ 10 & -50 & 47 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -98 & -49 & 90 \\\\ -18 & -20 & 73 \\\\ -75 & 63 & -96 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4209 & 2154 & -258 \\\\ -14046 & 1177 & 292 \\\\ -3343 & -11521 & 21688 \\\\ 434 & -2397 & 1085 \\\\ -7575 & -35 & 3490 \\\\ 4004 & 6084 & -14101 \\\\ -10743 & -1173 & 5514 \\\\ -3605 & 3471 & -7262 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 8/6x - 1$ and $y = 9/5x + 9$",
    "solution": "$(-150/7, -207/7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-12+13j) * (-8-10j) = $",
    "solution": "$(226+16j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $37$ and $64 = $",
    "solution": "$79$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $3 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{2}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 430$ and $SP = 5$ is: ",
    "solution": "$98.84$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9^7 =$",
    "solution": "$4782969$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 448 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $12$ of the AP series: $39, 91, 143 ... $",
    "solution": "$611$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.39\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=94.92$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=96.20\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$8.91$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+x-56$",
    "solution": "$(x-7)(x+8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{4} + 5x^{4} + 7x^{5} + 2x^{2} + 6x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$36x^{3} + 20x^{3} + 35x^{4} + 4x^{1} + 12x^{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $19$ and angle, $153$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 50.73672$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $12$ sides",
    "solution": "$150.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o4072$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $113$ composite?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $245 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 5, 7, 35, 49, 245]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 46 & 97 & -7 & 66 & -74 \\\\ 13 & 82 & 1 & 47 & 12 \\\\ -58 & 14 & -5 & -89 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -90 & -27 & 52 & 0 & -67 & -100 & 54 & -43 \\\\ 66 & 90 & -77 & 22 & 40 & 56 & 18 & 97 \\\\ 44 & 61 & -76 & 47 & -42 & -39 & -97 & -70 \\\\ 27 & -32 & 83 & 52 & -55 & -44 & -96 & -77 \\\\ -33 & -71 & -37 & 59 & 78 & 57 & 35 & -83 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6178 & 10203 & 3671 & 871 & -8310 & -6017 & -4017 & 8981 \\\\ 5159 & 4734 & -2257 & 5003 & 718 & 1869 & -2011 & 2710 \\\\ 3389 & 5085 & -11249 & -4319 & 9863 & 10923 & 6289 & 10723 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $7210$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$15659.35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $42$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$107.60000000000001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $10$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{9}=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-4x+3$",
    "solution": "$(x-3)(x-1)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 3m$ and radius $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$28 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $4.13$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$236.63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{527}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$8.08$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sec)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec \\cdot \\tan$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-16, -2, -20]\\cdot[-10, -12, -2]=$",
    "solution": "$224$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $18$ and $6 = $",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5821$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$8752.63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.49\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=99.80$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=94.35\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$8.0$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $8$ and $16$?",
    "solution": "$17.89$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{1}{2}$ and $\\frac{7}{8}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(109426641,484246189)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-18,-15)$ and $(-14,-9) = $",
    "solution": "$(-16.0,-12.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$192\\div24=$",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$294 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $16m, 3m, 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$384 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=10*x^3 + 10*x^2 + 3*x + 6$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{1}{3} - \\frac{\\sqrt{10}}{30}, - \\frac{1}{3} + \\frac{\\sqrt{10}}{30}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{7} + 3x^{6} + 9x^{7} + 2x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{7}x^{8} + \\frac{3}{6}x^{7} + \\frac{9}{7}x^{8} + \\frac{2}{8}x^{9} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $97 = $",
    "solution": "$1100001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$16^2=$",
    "solution": "$256$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{1}\\div\\frac{10}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{6}{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $94x^2 + 70x + 58 = $",
    "solution": "$124.3333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $100111 = $",
    "solution": "$11001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 536$ and $SP = 31$ is: ",
    "solution": "$94.22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 6m$ and radius $= 18m$ is",
    "solution": "$2035 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 11 m$, base width $= 8 m$ and height $= 21 m$ is",
    "solution": "$616.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=2*x^3 + 8*x^2 + 5$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{8}{3}, 0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $6056 = $",
    "solution": "$17108$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 320 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $14$ and $11 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=6*x^3 + 9*x^2 + x + 10$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{1}{2} - \\frac{\\sqrt{7}}{6}, - \\frac{1}{2} + \\frac{\\sqrt{7}}{6}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $7$ and $14 =$",
    "solution": "$14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 40m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$4188 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $14$ and $8 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[8, 5, 32, 70] = $",
    "solution": "$17.3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-17, 9, 4]\\cdot[-16, -8, -2]=$",
    "solution": "$192$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-20-8j) * (1+6j) = $",
    "solution": "$(28-128j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1 * \\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 8 \\\\ 5 & 2 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 8 \\\\ 5 & 2 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12\\cdot6$",
    "solution": "$72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6.32(-6.0\\theta + i2.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$2.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $9m, 8m, 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$576 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 2/3x + 5$ and $y = -5x - 8$",
    "solution": "$(-39/17, 59/17)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[3, 5, 17, 19, 25, 39, 41, 52, 89, 98]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $38.8$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $32.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-69-32|=$",
    "solution": "$101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $79$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$174.20000000000002$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(8,8)$ and $(13,-7) = $",
    "solution": "$(10.5,0.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 11 & 5 & 5 \\\\ 2 & 1 & 1 \\\\ 4 & 2 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & -5 & 0 \\\\ -2 & 9 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 2 & -1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $49^{\\frac{1}{8}}$ _ $33^{\\frac{1}{2}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $18$ objects picked $4$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$73440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$300\\div12=$",
    "solution": "$25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.22\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=90.17$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=99.95\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$95.7$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $98=$",
    "solution": "$30171.86$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $13m, 11m, 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$286 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 10 m$, base width $= 3 m$ and height $= 14 m$ is",
    "solution": "$140.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $20m, 20m, 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$960 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 49m$ and radius $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$1696 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $14$ objects picked $9$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$2002$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-13,-11)$ and $(6,4) = $",
    "solution": "$(-3.5,-3.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $3.71$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$212.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|61--38|=$",
    "solution": "$99$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $14$ objects picked $0$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $6x^2 + 8x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.14, -1.194)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{40}}{2*6}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{40}}{2*6})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $23^{\\frac{1}{3}}$ _ $92^{\\frac{1}{7}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12^2 =$",
    "solution": "$144$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 95 & 52 \\\\ 71 & 37 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-177$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MDLXIV$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=3*x^3 + 10*x^2 + x + 10$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{10}{9} - \\frac{\\sqrt{91}}{9}, - \\frac{10}{9} + \\frac{\\sqrt{91}}{9}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1993 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1993 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[241, 213, 266, 262, 276, 231, 204, 249, 227, 274, 216, 248, 244, 207, 291, 252, 287, 292, 217, 265, 234, 245, 282, 256, 208, 240, 228, 203, 233]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(252.65893208035033, 236.37555067827037)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $27^{6^{3}}$",
    "solution": "$27^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[9, 36, 144, 576, 2304, 9216]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 10th term value, sum upto 8th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $9$, common ratio is $4$ , 10th term is $2359296$, sum upto 8th term is $196605.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$51\\div70=$",
    "solution": "$0.73$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+2x-35$",
    "solution": "$(x+7)(x-5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[8, -14, 15] \\times [-18, -16, -9] = $",
    "solution": "$[366, -198, -380]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $9.96 \\times 10^{61}$ and $8.71 \\times 10^{-3} = $",
    "solution": "$8.68 \\times 10^{59}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-86$ and exact value equals $-100$.",
    "solution": "$14.0\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11$",
    "solution": "$0x3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{6}\\cdot\\frac{3}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{7}{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$56$ % $18 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $36, 14$ and $21$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 1m$ and radius $= 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$615 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3943$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$5825.61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 10 =",
    "solution": 80
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $4, 19 19 = $",
    "solution": "$37.79$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $2$ and $10$?",
    "solution": "$10.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2096 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2096 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $31$ and exact value equals $32$.",
    "solution": "$3.12\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $2410$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$3121.02$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 51 & 20 \\\\ 85 & 48 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$748$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $13$ of the AP series: $62, 159, 256 ... $",
    "solution": "$1226$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $-26$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$-14.800000000000004$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$18^2=$",
    "solution": "$324$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $51$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$123.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-9,19)$ and $(-13,-17)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$y = 9x + 100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $200$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$3.49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $35^{6}$ and $35^{9} = $35^{6-9} = 35^{-3}$",
    "solution": "$2.3323615160349855e-05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $11$ sided polygon with lengths of $46, 46, 117, 2, 52, 103, 59, 39, 6, 66, 110$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$646$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $85$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$185.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[563.2, 992.22, 517.2, 293.18, 987.69, 953.66, 973.93, 469.69, 338.01, 610.87, 273.48, 30.8, 682.08, 541.58, 251.4, 456.41, 901.16, 562.79, 119.01, 569.53]$ and $[132.9, 85.16, 949.38, 330.11, 380.76, 140.79, 292.03, 764.88, 605.5, 940.81, 907.71, 571.13, 122.58, 545.05, 648.92, 57.11, 641.73, 38.14, 801.53, 54.64]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.91$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $36, 44$ and $21$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-8x-6)(7x+7)$",
    "solution": "$-56x^2-98x-42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$81\\div63=$",
    "solution": "$1.29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$30\\div5=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 6 & 3 \\\\ 1 & 8 & 4 \\\\ 0 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 4 & -3 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ -1 & 1 & -2 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 29m$ and radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$1943 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{10}{2}\\cdot\\frac{4}{6}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{10}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 20m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$6283 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$101$",
    "solution": "$0x5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -x - 3$ and $y = 5x - 2$",
    "solution": "$(-1/6, -17/6)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $61 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$475387.895 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $8252$ from base $16$ to base $7$.",
    "solution": "$166160$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\tan)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 28 & 9 \\\\ 19 & 79 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$2041$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$23.35(-17.0\\theta + i16.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$2.39$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 98th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$135301852344707186688$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$18.79(-8.0\\theta + i17.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$2.01$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-18, -3, 8]\\cdot[-19, 4, -15]=$",
    "solution": "$210$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{1}{4}$ and $\\frac{8}{4}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $25$ and $7 = $",
    "solution": "$148$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=6*x^3 + 7*x^2 + 2*x + 3$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{7}{18} - \\frac{\\sqrt{13}}{18}, - \\frac{7}{18} + \\frac{\\sqrt{13}}{18}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $6.56 \\times 10^{-3}$ and $3.9 \\times 10^{73} = $",
    "solution": "$2.56 \\times 10^{71}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 24m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$7263 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $29$ and exact value equals $39$.",
    "solution": "$25.64\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 8 & 58 \\\\ 93 & 6 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-5346$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$36\\div2=$",
    "solution": "$18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(2)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $27 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$41223.979 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $83=$",
    "solution": "$21642.43$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(16,6)$ and $(-12,-6) = $",
    "solution": "$(2.0,0.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[8, 49, 49, 52] = $",
    "solution": "$31.61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $78$ of the AP series: $98, 115, 132 ... $",
    "solution": "$1407$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$011011$",
    "solution": "$0x1b$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$76-33=$",
    "solution": "$43$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 35m$ and $r1 = 5m$ is and $r2 = 5m$ is ",
    "solution": "$9492.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $3m$ is",
    "solution": "$27 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{6}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{2}{6}x^{7} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-6, -4)$ and $(9, 6)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{325}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9^2 =$",
    "solution": "$81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$100$",
    "solution": "$0x4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$1734 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $10$ objects picked $2$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$90$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{3}{6}$ and $\\frac{8}{9}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $3.66 \\times 10^{-65}$ and $4.28 \\times 10^{49} = $",
    "solution": "$1.57 \\times 10^{-15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.86\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=92.60$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=92.09\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$9.22$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$726 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 45m$ and $r1 = 18m$ is and $r2 = 18m$ is ",
    "solution": "$30300.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $83 = $",
    "solution": "$521.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233, 377, 610, 987, 1597, 2584$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMDCXCII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $19 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$14365.456 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $14=$",
    "solution": "$615.75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(243)=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $23 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$25482.505 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[1, 5, 13, 16, 28, 45, 60, 66, 68, 80]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $38.2$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $36.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$54-19=$",
    "solution": "$35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{7}\\div\\frac{10}{7}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{2}{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 14m$ and radius $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$596 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o3255$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $2, 9 10 = $",
    "solution": "$8.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{4}{1}$ and $\\frac{5}{10}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $8$ and $19 =$",
    "solution": "$152$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 48m$, base width $= 50m$, and height $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$4800 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4\\div33=$",
    "solution": "$0.12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[224, 204, 215, 209, 220, 269, 227, 278, 237, 235, 259, 208, 231, 261, 297, 239, 200, 289, 275, 266, 236, 273, 292, 260, 287, 202, 225, 274, 253, 286, 256, 247, 268, 250, 293, 248, 206, 294]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(257.6899187104644, 241.94166023690403)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $19^{9^{4}}$",
    "solution": "$19^{36}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[3, 13, 14, 23, 27, 35, 62, 73, 80, 83]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $41.3$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $31.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $59, 28 = $",
    "solution": "$531.6781609195402$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-9,-7)$ and passing through $(-7.92, -5.32)$ is",
    "solution": "$12.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -27 & 3 & -47 \\\\ 90 & -51 & 48 \\\\ -64 & 72 & -19 \\\\ -42 & -4 & -7 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -98 & 23 \\\\ 1 & -55 \\\\ -35 & 57 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4294 & -3465 \\\\ -10551 & 7611 \\\\ 7009 & -6515 \\\\ 4357 & -1145 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 340$ and $SP = 190$ is: ",
    "solution": "$44.12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $26^{5}$ and $26^{8} = $26^{5-8} = 26^{-3}$",
    "solution": "$5.689576695493855e-05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $14$ sides",
    "solution": "$154.29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $12$ sides",
    "solution": "$150.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{9} + 2x^{10} + 7x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{9}x^{10} + \\frac{2}{10}x^{11} + \\frac{7}{1}x^{2} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 34m$ and $r1 = 20m$ is and $r2 = 20m$ is ",
    "solution": "$19796.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{6} + 8x^{6}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{6}x^{7} + \\frac{8}{6}x^{7} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $27, 55, 76 = $",
    "solution": "$1111.4889205649865$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $139$",
    "solution": "$139$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $12$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1800$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $3$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $163$",
    "solution": "$163$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $17$ and $3 =$",
    "solution": "$51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $13, 50, 15, 7, 15, 15, 25, 48, 8, 6, 12, 44, 40, 32, 39$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $24.6$, Standard Deviation is $237.97333333333336$, Variance is $15.426384324699464$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 20m$ and radius $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$3619 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{3}{6}$ and $\\frac{3}{6}$?",
    "solution": "="
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $59$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$138.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $111 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $9m, 4m, 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$252 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[6.47, 884.23, 471.96, 819.14, 490.4, 677.34, 507.2, 266.02, 874.77, 260.27, 15.38]$ and $[557.3, 702.47, 865.77, 208.23, 252.7, 343.36, 436.18, 35.09, 772.14, 252.35, 368.41]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.62$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $19m$ is",
    "solution": "$6859 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $6m, 5m, 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$434 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $25$ and angle, $125$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 54.54154$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $5.48 \\times 10^{35}$ and $1.72 \\times 10^{43} = $",
    "solution": "$9.43 \\times 10^{78}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(10,9)$ and passing through $(8.0, 9.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$12.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $89$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$1$ hours and $29$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $93$ of the AP series: $33, 5, -23 ... $",
    "solution": "$-2543$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -7/4x - 9$ and $y = -9/6x - 3$",
    "solution": "$(-24, 33)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$67$ % $25 = $",
    "solution": "$17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $9 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{4}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(8x-2)(6x+7)$",
    "solution": "$48x^2+44x-14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $53710$ from base $10$ to base $13$.",
    "solution": "$1B5A7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2-2=$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{5}{3}\\cdot\\frac{5}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{25}{24}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 * \\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 8 \\\\ 7 & 5 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 20m$ and radius $= 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$874 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 56th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$225851433717$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $2$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$272\\div16=$",
    "solution": "$17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 4/5x - 10$ and $y = 6x + 6$",
    "solution": "$(-40/13, -162/13)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 9x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.347, -8.653)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{69}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{69}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $97$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$206.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1996 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1996 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 6m$, base width $= 26m$, and height $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$492 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $78x^2+200x+92=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.6, -1.96}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $11$ objects picked $3$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$990$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 50m$, base width $= 24m$, and height $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$2416 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 6 m$, base width $= 2 m$ and height $= 1 m$ is",
    "solution": "$4.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $8248$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$9093.42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$16.49(4.0\\theta + i16.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$1.33$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cot)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $14$ and angle, $21$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 5.13127$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 2m$ and radius $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$301 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $12$ sides",
    "solution": "$150.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{79}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$4.29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $6$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$26679$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $20$ objects picked $8$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$5079110400$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMDXIII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=3*x^2 + 6*x + 10$",
    "solution": "${-1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{5} + 7x^{5} + 5x^{10} + 1x^{2} + 2x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$35x^{4} + 35x^{4} + 50x^{9} + 2x^{1} + 8x^{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $15$ and $19 =$",
    "solution": "$285$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{3} + 5x^{2} + 6x^{1} + 2x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{5}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{6}{1}x^{2} + \\frac{2}{2}x^{3} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$15\\div5=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{6}\\cdot\\frac{2}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $2.21$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$126.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$39-3=$",
    "solution": "$36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x + 10 = 10$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $45=$",
    "solution": "$6361.73$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$2400 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $37 = $",
    "solution": "$232.48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $4, 13 15 = $",
    "solution": "$24.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $40$ and angle $82$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$1144.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 73 & 41 \\\\ 85 & 89 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$3012$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-10x+6)(-7x-6)$",
    "solution": "$70x^2+18x-36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $4$ and $4 =$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 8m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$2670 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{2}{1}\\cdot\\frac{10}{6}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{10}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$14^2=$",
    "solution": "$196$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-8+12j) * (20+18j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-376+96j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{761}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $48$ and height, $31$?",
    "solution": "$9349.38$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(3,10)$ and passing through $(8.0, 10.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$78.54$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 18m$ is",
    "solution": "$4071.5040790523717 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 13m$ and radius $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$565 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 68 & 68 \\\\ 8 & 21 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$884$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[762.7207130906187, 298.3771961301145, 700.606923142578, 462.95846994060264, 123.70633593303049, 357.2982497106919, 380.7386984995238, 10.844405819969815, 517.8864797619888, 81.45780298024907, 618.8939291916097, 665.1350377512508, 828.274069247086, 429.4818206347124, 733.6918200837532, 334.77731695681115, 728.2396844896714, 379.01584375313627]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2226.91$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(27)=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{8} + 7x^{1} + 8x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$56x^{7} + 7x^{0} + 8x^{0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$1536 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-8, -4, 7]\\cdot[5, -4, 19]=$",
    "solution": "$109$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$101000100 = $",
    "solution": "$010111011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $31x^2 + 93x + 1 = $",
    "solution": "$57.8333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $82$ of the AP series: $33, -52, -137 ... $",
    "solution": "$-6852$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$91\\div62=$",
    "solution": "$1.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $14$ and $15 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{1}{8}\\div\\frac{1}{3}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 50m$ and radius $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$22619 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $6, 15$ and $26$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11^8 =$",
    "solution": "$214358881$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sec)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec \\cdot \\tan$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $16$ objects picked $5$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$4368$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $10$ of the AP series: $-66, -141, -216 ... $",
    "solution": "$-741$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $19$ sides",
    "solution": "$161.05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $80DF$ from base $16$ to base $2$.",
    "solution": "$1000000011011111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $40$ and angle $75$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$1047.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 62 =",
    "solution": 28
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 62 & 47 \\\\ 39 & 99 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$4305$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $15$ objects picked $5$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$3003$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $17$ and $1$?",
    "solution": "$17.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9237$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$11962.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3 * \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 9 \\\\ 6 & 9 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 21 & 27 \\\\ 18 & 27 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$452.3893421169302 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o256$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 11m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$552 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-2,-9)$ and $(-3,-20) = $",
    "solution": "$(-2.5,-14.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 13 m$, base width $= 11 m$ and height $= 46 m$ is",
    "solution": "$2192.6666666666665 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $11011 = $",
    "solution": "$101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $19m, 14m, 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$1060 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 11m$ and radius $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$1780 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1100000 = $",
    "solution": "$0011111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $97, 54, 5, 2 = $",
    "solution": "$2.7441324392288347$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $51$ terms of the AP series: $63, 80, 97 ... $",
    "solution": "$24888.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|63-36|=$",
    "solution": "$27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(17,0)$ and $(-13,14) = $",
    "solution": "$(2.0,7.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{7}\\cdot\\frac{1}{2}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{14}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $8, 4 10 = $",
    "solution": "$15.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $22^{9}$ and $22^{6} = $22^{9-6} = 22^{3}$",
    "solution": "$10648$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{7} + 6x^{17} + 8x^{1} + 3x^{16} + 7x^{13} + 4x^{4} + 3x^{17} + 3x^{12}$",
    "solution": "$8x^{1} + 4x^{4} + 9x^{7} + 3x^{12} + 7x^{13} + 3x^{16} + 9x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 67 =",
    "solution": 113
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(9,1)$ and passing through $(14.0, 1.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$78.54$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[792.7564279881934, 880.5344113952808, 173.93700679987057, 21.98587915761463]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1197.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$78-67=$",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $154 , 47, 24 =$",
    "solution": "$135$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $46 = $",
    "solution": "$289.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $44x^2+185x+37=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.21, -3.99}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $76$ terms of the AP series: $26, -13, -52 ... $",
    "solution": "$-109174.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-17, -11, 16]\\cdot[-18, -3, 2]=$",
    "solution": "$371$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $34.2$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $20$ pistons will contain no more than $9$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$89.33$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{238}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$6.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$456\\div19=$",
    "solution": "$24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $15m$ is",
    "solution": "$3375 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $ = $",
    "solution": "$$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 13 & 62 \\\\ 94 & 89 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-4671$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $46x^2+165x+41=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.27, -3.32}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-18--12|=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $7$ and $12 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $10$ and $15 = $",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $15m, 17m, 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$1406 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[0, -15, 18] \\times [14, 11, 10] = $",
    "solution": "$[-348, 252, 210]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[498.36, 704.18, 697.62, 478.43]$ and $[222.17, 34.04, 266.35, 235.82]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.55$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $200$",
    "solution": "$2, 2, 2, 5, 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{4}\\cdot\\frac{6}{9}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-20, 15, -16] \\times [19, 12, -6] = $",
    "solution": "$[102, -424, -525]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $4$ and $7 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $3196$ from base $10$ to base $14$.",
    "solution": "$1244$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 * \\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 9 \\\\ 4 & 4 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{1}{2}\\cdot\\frac{8}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{8}{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $35.48$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $17$ pistons will contain no more than $8$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$89.29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(30) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $10001011 = $",
    "solution": "$1110101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $3$% of $17$?",
    "solution": "$0.51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[239, 218, 276, 240, 254, 220, 251, 271, 288, 270, 275, 221, 241, 290, 280, 248, 278, 204, 274, 228, 299, 259, 283, 246, 256, 217, 289, 298, 210]$ with $99$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(269.2121394812531, 242.7188950015055)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $828 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 9, 12, 18, 23, 36, 46, 69, 92, 138, 207, 276, 414, 828]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $189$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $11$ sides",
    "solution": "$147.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[203, 243, 257, 241, 278, 280, 250, 204, 255, 226, 236, 205, 263, 239, 212, 216, 247, 253, 242, 291, 275, 232, 298, 231, 282, 286, 259, 233, 206, 284, 224, 273, 268]$ with $99$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(260.4573653900472, 236.0274830948013)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(2, 14)$ and $(13, 7)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{170}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $32^{1^{5}}$",
    "solution": "$32^{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.31\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=92.05$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=97.56\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$33.37$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(4x-7)(7x+7)$",
    "solution": "$28x^2-21x-49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3920$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $6$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$6574.23$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{9}\\cdot\\frac{5}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{35}{36}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x + 8 = 10$",
    "solution": "$1/3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $10$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MXXIX$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $854$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$14$ hours and $14$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -62 & -67 & -60 & -2 & -55 & -3 \\\\ 71 & 69 & -53 & 40 & 43 & -79 \\\\ 48 & -38 & 84 & -41 & -77 & -86 \\\\ 52 & -69 & 25 & 56 & 10 & 79 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -34 & 39 & -69 & 89 & -87 & 3 & -33 & -1 \\\\ -27 & -86 & -95 & -12 & -9 & 75 & 32 & -54 \\\\ -61 & -98 & -55 & 50 & 48 & -36 & -34 & 73 \\\\ 73 & 22 & 36 & 87 & 91 & 47 & -91 & 86 \\\\ 83 & -29 & 4 & 97 & 82 & -85 & 56 & 50 \\\\ 45 & -54 & 19 & -96 & -15 & 39 & 45 & 73 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 2731 & 10937 & 13594 & -12935 & -1530 & 1413 & -1091 & -3841 \\\\ 1890 & 5928 & -8428 & 18076 & -991 & 2440 & -3120 & -7843 \\\\ -18984 & 2883 & -7740 & 6148 & -8557 & -4466 & -10107 & -5518 \\\\ 7043 & 2188 & 5149 & 4964 & 2028 & -1056 & -5755 & 16582 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{100}=$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $4x + 3y = 27$ and $-2x +  = -18$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 9$, $y = -3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & 0 \\\\ 1 & 2 & 1 \\\\ 4 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & 0 \\\\ -4 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 7 & 1 & -2 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $15m, 11m, 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$538 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[6, 30, 150, 750, 3750, 18750]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 10th term value, sum upto 8th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $6$, common ratio is $5$ , 10th term is $11718750$, sum upto 8th term is $585936.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1919 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1919 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 72 =",
    "solution": 108
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 8x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.419, -3.581)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{40}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{40}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{979}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $4, 16 16 = $",
    "solution": "$31.75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(8x)(9x+6)$",
    "solution": "$72x^2+48x$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-8, 16, -8]\\cdot[14, -11, -3]=$",
    "solution": "$-264$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 7m$ and radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$3103 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-9,13)$ and $(15,-13) = $",
    "solution": "$(3.0,0.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $8$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$33538$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 45m$ and radius $= 11m$ is",
    "solution": "$5701 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-10,-9)$ and $(-11,10) = $",
    "solution": "$(-10.5,0.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $82$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$179.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 77 =",
    "solution": 103
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|83--33|=$",
    "solution": "$116$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$95\\div81=$",
    "solution": "$1.17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 26m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$7868 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{3}\\div\\frac{9}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{16}{27}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $72$ and $20 = $",
    "solution": "$88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & 4 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 3 \\\\ 2 & 1 & 6 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -3 & 4 & 0 \\\\ 0 & -2 & 1 \\\\ 1 & -1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $63 m = $",
    "solution": "$1047394.4243362226 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $19$ objects picked $6$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$27132$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $28$ and angle, $170$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 83.07767$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $2116$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1058.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 24m$ and radius $= 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$1837 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $6$ and $5 =$",
    "solution": "$30$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 8 & 84 \\\\ 65 & 66 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-4932$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-4x-4)(x+1)$",
    "solution": "$-4x^2-8x-4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $1$ and angle $273$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$2.38$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$46-12=$",
    "solution": "$34$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $52$ and exact value equals $83$.",
    "solution": "$37.35\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $103$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$1$ hours and $43$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$1536 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $12$ objects picked $7$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$3991680$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $8$ and angle, $145$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 20.24582$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1000 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 1m$ is",
    "solution": "$6 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10^2=$",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$48+40=$",
    "solution": "$88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $12$ objects picked $2$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{6}{2}\\cdot\\frac{10}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{15}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $53x^2+146x+32=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.24, -2.51}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $95 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$1795682.001 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $3$ and $3 =$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2 * \\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 10 \\\\ 3 & 5 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 20 \\\\ 6 & 10 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $10m, 11m, 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$220 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $27, 39, 14, 35, 45, 35, 19, 15, 30, 27, 48, 22, 8, 11, 40$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $27.666666666666668$, Standard Deviation is $148.48888888888888$, Variance is $12.18560170401482$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $81$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(6x-7)(3x-2)$",
    "solution": "$18x^2-33x+14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(664386766,840913518)=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$18.44(12.0\\theta + i-14.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-0.86$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o4647$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-5,3)$ and $(14,-4)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$19y = -7x + 22$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{10} + 6x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{8}{10}x^{11} + \\frac{6}{4}x^{5} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $13$ and angle, $248$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 56.26942$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7^2=$",
    "solution": "$49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $15$ and $7$?",
    "solution": "$16.55$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $5.96$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$341.48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $6$ sides?",
    "solution": "$720$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4! =$",
    "solution": "$24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{8}\\cdot\\frac{1}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{3}{32}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1 = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 11m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1151 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $4$% of $63$?",
    "solution": "$2.52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $9174 = $",
    "solution": "$23136$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $89=$",
    "solution": "$24884.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1001110$",
    "solution": "$78$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $9$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1260$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\tan)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 12 m$, base width $= 2 m$ and height $= 14 m$ is",
    "solution": "$112.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{515}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$8.02$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 98th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$135301852344707186688$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1111101 = $",
    "solution": "$11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $4$ sided polygon with lengths of $54, 114, 22, 19$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$209$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-1,9)$ and passing through $(-1.0, 9.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$0.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(11,0)$ and $(-20,-18)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$31y = 18x -198$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $12$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1800$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{3} + 1x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{1}{4}x^{5} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $8x + y = 81$ and $-2x - 8y = -90$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 9$, $y = 9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={9, 2, 6}$, $b={10, 3, 4, 7}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${2, 3, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10}$. Intersection is $set()$, a-b is ${9, 2, 6}$, b-a is ${10, 3, 4, 7}$. Symmetric difference is ${2, 3, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10$",
    "solution": "$0x2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[9, 17, 26, 28, 40, 60, 65, 68, 80, 94]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $48.7$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $50.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 52 =",
    "solution": 38
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $4$ numbers $[25, 83, 50, 25] = $",
    "solution": "$40.13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $2x - 9y = 52$ and $-3x - y = 38$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -10$, $y = -8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $11$ and $84 = $",
    "solution": "$85$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 79 & 93 \\\\ 59 & 99 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$2334$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $18$ objects picked $5$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1028160$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$14-2=$",
    "solution": "$12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $6m, 8m, 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$292 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $7 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$718.378 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $87 = $",
    "solution": "$546.64$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$25\\div1=$",
    "solution": "$25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$24\\div3=$",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 28 =",
    "solution": 152
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{36}=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 10m$, base width $= 10m$, and height $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$180 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.32\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=93.38$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=93.27\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$15.65$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(2x-9)(8x-3)$",
    "solution": "$16x^2-78x+27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $32$ and $30 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $4m, 18m, 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$288 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $71 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$749607.045 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$010 = $",
    "solution": "$101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144, 233, 377, 610$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $9$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1260$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $9122$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $1$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$729.76$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{13} + 10x^{13} + 9x^{5} + 7x^{13} + 7x^{14} + 8x^{9} + 9x^{15} + 10x^{19}$",
    "solution": "$9x^{5} + 8x^{9} + 24x^{13} + 7x^{14} + 9x^{15} + 10x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$231\\div11=$",
    "solution": "$21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$312\\div24=$",
    "solution": "$13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $2342$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$3147.45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 39 =",
    "solution": 141
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6^2=$",
    "solution": "$36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -3/6x + 1$ and $y = 9/5x + 9$",
    "solution": "$(-80/23, 63/23)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{1}{4}$ and $\\frac{5}{2}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $57$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 27m$ and radius $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$2381 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 43m$ and radius $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$2199 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-12, -4)$ and $(-8, -4)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $27, 7$ and $5$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{1} + 5x^{17} + 6x^{18} + 7x^{17} + 6x^{6} + 9x^{14} + 2x^{9} + 8x^{12}$",
    "solution": "$9x^{1} + 6x^{6} + 2x^{9} + 8x^{12} + 9x^{14} + 12x^{17} + 6x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $6$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $80x^2 + 78x + 0 = $",
    "solution": "$65.6667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $238$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$4.15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $9x + y = 18$ and $-4x + 6y = -66$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 3$, $y = -9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{4} + 6x^{4} + 4x^{3} + 10x^{1} + 7x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{4}x^{5} + \\frac{6}{4}x^{5} + \\frac{4}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{10}{1}x^{2} + \\frac{7}{3}x^{4} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(3,12)$ and $(-13,-12)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$2y = 3x + 15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $6851$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$8289.71$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $227$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$3$ hours and $47$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[9, 63, 441, 3087, 21609, 151263]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 8th term value, sum upto 9th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $9$, common ratio is $7$ , 8th term is $7411887$, sum upto 9th term is $60530409.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$18^6 =$",
    "solution": "$34012224$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $7$ sided polygon with lengths of $39, 85, 23, 46, 96, 92, 114$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$495$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $224$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $45$ and angle $20$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$353.43$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-4x-21$",
    "solution": "$(x+3)(x-7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(45) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5\\div9=$",
    "solution": "$0.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$96-70=$",
    "solution": "$26$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$39$ % $58 = $",
    "solution": "$39$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -15 & -18 & 11 & -45 & -27 & 90 & -76 \\\\ 57 & -30 & 28 & 11 & 94 & -12 & -65 \\\\ 97 & 32 & 4 & 2 & 35 & -84 & -39 \\\\ -95 & 0 & 50 & 75 & -23 & 75 & 39 \\\\ -35 & 1 & 91 & -44 & 83 & -31 & -99 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 67 & 46 & -75 & 92 & -91 & 94 & -100 \\\\ -83 & -84 & -49 & 2 & 97 & -85 & 86 \\\\ -42 & 2 & 78 & 91 & -81 & -97 & 59 \\\\ 35 & 9 & 58 & -79 & -18 & -71 & -5 \\\\ 59 & -12 & 19 & -34 & -16 & 97 & 25 \\\\ 99 & 34 & -22 & 59 & 30 & -60 & 57 \\\\ 21 & -93 & 61 & 47 & 75 & -45 & 61 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4173 & 10891 & -6874 & 5796 & -3030 & -2351 & 645 \\\\ 8511 & 9806 & -1898 & -96 & -17302 & 17174 & -8982 \\\\ -3325 & 2151 & -8281 & 1215 & -12088 & 16058 & -13014 \\\\ 1047 & -4396 & 15667 & -3075 & 8788 & -27591 & 18154 \\\\ -8041 & 5249 & 3342 & -765 & -12980 & 5288 & 3444 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $66$ and $32 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\tan(60) = $",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(152905340,270222530)=$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(705452195,304703910)=$",
    "solution": "$35$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $388 = $",
    "solution": "$0x184$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $12$ and $18 = $",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$5026.548245743669 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(0) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 602 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1912 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1912 is a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $40, 50$ and $30$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(2,16)$ and $(1,1)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$y = 15x -14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 14m$ and radius $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1960 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 19m$ and $r1 = 10m$ is and $r2 = 10m$ is ",
    "solution": "$7938.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Profit percent when $CP = 585$ and $SP = 944$ is: ",
    "solution": "$61.37$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $4m, 16m, 18m$ is",
    "solution": "$848 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $916 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4, 229, 458, 916]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=10*x^3 + 8*x^2 + 4$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{8}{15}, 0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$22+23=$",
    "solution": "$45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $98$ and $4 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $7 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{15}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $3 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{2}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $41 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$144347.805 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 22 & 51 & -65 & 95 & -5 & -97 & -60 & -49 & 36 & -4 \\\\ -83 & -67 & -58 & -52 & 71 & 77 & 88 & -16 & 25 & 2 \\\\ 78 & -14 & -74 & -85 & -92 & 46 & -6 & 4 & 90 & -78 \\\\ 80 & 83 & -38 & 63 & -80 & -75 & -83 & 32 & -31 & -57 \\\\ 6 & -68 & -67 & -52 & 61 & 39 & 52 & 80 & -29 & -63 \\\\ 50 & 73 & 19 & -81 & 0 & -23 & 72 & -53 & -2 & 74 \\\\ 48 & 1 & -17 & 1 & -11 & 30 & -85 & 46 & 99 & 84 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 35 & -53 & 77 & -66 & -91 & -97 & -53 \\\\ 4 & 71 & 32 & -13 & -28 & 55 & -70 \\\\ 13 & 30 & -95 & -21 & 96 & -44 & 90 \\\\ -61 & 38 & 94 & 66 & 93 & -69 & 45 \\\\ 47 & -4 & -84 & -18 & 55 & 49 & -74 \\\\ 29 & -72 & -100 & -51 & 77 & 63 & -39 \\\\ 10 & -51 & -78 & 30 & -47 & -77 & -46 \\\\ 64 & -73 & -25 & -44 & -34 & -51 & 43 \\\\ -2 & 25 & -35 & -13 & -83 & -98 & 98 \\\\ -86 & -2 & 83 & 49 & -69 & -5 & -71 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -12178 & 18664 & 32864 & 10249 & -6805 & -5769 & 2307 \\\\ 4449 & -12601 & -28750 & 2047 & 3054 & 10416 & -9156 \\\\ 10631 & -11102 & -1530 & -15060 & -25175 & -8997 & 6181 \\\\ -958 & 9863 & 34596 & -2426 & -8249 & -6433 & 4413 \\\\ 17353 & -21275 & -19531 & -9294 & -1962 & 2733 & -7284 \\\\ -2469 & 1680 & 988 & -677 & -20596 & -546 & -19839 \\\\ -3573 & -1777 & 12348 & -5835 & -15812 & -8494 & 5171 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $18^{2}$ and $45^{2} = (18/45)^2 = 0.4^{2}$",
    "solution": "$0.16000000000000003$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $13$ and $39 = $",
    "solution": "$128$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $40$ and $46 = $",
    "solution": "$94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $39, 24, 45, 40, 47, 14, 50, 27, 31, 23, 12, 40, 18, 44, 42$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $33.06666666666667$, Standard Deviation is $147.5288888888889$, Variance is $12.146147079995734$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $15$ and angle, $86$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 22.51475$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$21.95(-11.0\\theta + i19.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$2.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$2166 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $776 = $",
    "solution": "$0x308$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 12 & 3 \\\\ 1 & 16 & 4 \\\\ 0 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 4 & -3 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ -1 & 1 & -4 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $19x + -3y = -88$ and $-8x + -17y = -36$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -4$, $y = 4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $40x^2 + 12x + 73 = $",
    "solution": "$92.3333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[14, 21, 29, 46, 56, 67, 76, 78, 79, 83]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $54.9$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $61.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $52 = $",
    "solution": "$326.73$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $94 = $",
    "solution": "$590.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $74$ of the AP series: $-42, 55, 152 ... $",
    "solution": "$7039$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $70, 48, 53, 67 = $",
    "solution": "$972.2495980384765$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$77\\div92=$",
    "solution": "$0.84$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $60$ terms of the AP series: $17, -37, -91 ... $",
    "solution": "$-94560.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $23$ composite?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1101001 = $",
    "solution": "$10111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[213.37, 147.96, 710.61, 714.42, 275.09, 336.15, 619.55, 285.42]$ and $[742.38, 780.63, 43.35, 756.97, 107.51, 426.61, 514.57, 201.08]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.78$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 76 =",
    "solution": 14
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8 * \\begin{bmatrix} 2 & 5 \\\\ 5 & 9 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 16 & 40 \\\\ 40 & 72 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[23, 34, 43, 53, 59, 60, 61, 70, 71, 91]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $56.5$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $59.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-10, -4, -14] \\times [-8, -4, 13] = $",
    "solution": "$[-108, 242, 8]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(10,-20)$ and $(12,-2)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$y = 9x -110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-2x+4)(7x-8)$",
    "solution": "$-14x^2+44x-32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$17^4 =$",
    "solution": "$83521$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $14$ sides",
    "solution": "$154.29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7^2=$",
    "solution": "$49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{10} + 4x^{2} + 8x^{7}$",
    "solution": "$90x^{9} + 8x^{1} + 56x^{6}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$1176 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $9^{\\frac{1}{8}}$ _ $92^{\\frac{1}{6}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $15$ objects picked $0$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 691 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-5x+10)(-4x-5)$",
    "solution": "$20x^2-15x-50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $582 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 3, 6, 97, 194, 291, 582]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $7x + 5y = -35$ and $-7x - 3y = 49$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -10$, $y = 7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 12m$ and radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$2475 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $86, 28 = $",
    "solution": "$591.438596491228$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$21.47(19.0\\theta + i-10.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-0.48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 96 & 34 & -18 & -1 & -64 & 94 & -40 \\\\ -78 & -96 & -91 & 86 & 18 & -59 & 37 \\\\ -12 & 52 & 6 & 51 & 9 & 74 & -75 \\\\ 43 & 84 & 35 & -50 & 45 & -73 & 15 \\\\ -71 & -31 & 7 & 43 & 22 & -22 & 23 \\\\ -73 & -43 & -23 & -60 & -34 & 29 & -96 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 44 & 83 & -38 & 16 & 47 & -75 \\\\ -59 & -61 & -8 & 41 & 19 & -29 \\\\ -25 & 61 & 98 & -33 & 74 & -79 \\\\ -56 & -1 & -26 & 41 & -32 & -95 \\\\ 45 & 61 & -1 & -61 & 45 & -90 \\\\ 60 & -29 & -74 & 59 & -20 & 11 \\\\ -96 & 47 & 15 & 80 & -83 & -98 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 9324 & -3713 & -13150 & 9733 & 2418 & 4045 \\\\ -6591 & -1707 & -2519 & -274 & -16057 & 1758 \\\\ 5443 & -8975 & -7308 & 1650 & 4386 & 1427 \\\\ -4934 & 6197 & 8006 & -4925 & 10047 & -9999 \\\\ -6416 & -557 & 4465 & -1675 & -5263 & -2890 \\\\ 12686 & -12206 & -1128 & -8527 & 1828 & 27026 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $14$ and $10 = $",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 89th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$1779979416004719360$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$21.4(13.0\\theta + i-17.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-0.92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $3$ numbers $16, 96, 81 = $",
    "solution": "$950.0090497737556$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7\\cdot6$",
    "solution": "$42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $12, 7 11 = $",
    "solution": "$37.95$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $6.04 \\times 10^{-20}$ and $4.13 \\times 10^{-92} = $",
    "solution": "$2.49 \\times 10^{-111}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & 0 \\\\ 25 & 5 & 1 \\\\ 20 & 4 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & 0 \\\\ -5 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 0 & -4 & 5 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $11$ and height, $21$?",
    "solution": "$1451.42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cos)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\sin$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{5} + 5x^{14} + 2x^{6} + 8x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$2x^{5} + 2x^{6} + 8x^{10} + 5x^{14}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $10$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $5$ composite?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $23232231$ from base $4$ to base $5$.",
    "solution": "$3014140$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $48x^2+146x+66=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.55, -2.49}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-8x - 7y = 14$ and $-8x - 8y = 16$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 0$, $y = -2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(8,-9)$ and $(4,10) = $",
    "solution": "$(6.0,0.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $44, 36, 36, 43, 40, 8, 33, 35, 12, 39, 41, 6, 28, 49, 45$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $33.0$, Standard Deviation is $174.13333333333333$, Variance is $13.195958977404155$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[22, 28, 41, 52, 59, 66, 79, 80, 84, 95]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $60.6$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $62.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-5,10)$ and $(6,8)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$11y = -2x + 100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $9312 = $",
    "solution": "$2460$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-3,-4)$ and passing through $(-5.609999999999999, -7.029999999999999)$ is",
    "solution": "$50.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $3$ and $2 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$16^9 =$",
    "solution": "$68719476736$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $24, 34$ and $45$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9\\cdot9$",
    "solution": "$81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 31 & 86 \\\\ 77 & 56 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-4886$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $31.55$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $20$ pistons will contain no more than $5$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$35.87$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1947 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1947 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $10m, 4m, 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$240 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $15$ objects picked $7$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$32432400$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 49m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$15393 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $14$ objects picked $0$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $52 m = $",
    "solution": "$588977.4131146048 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $289 = $",
    "solution": "$0x121$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $9$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$37669$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[6, 26, 34, 41, 52, 58, 65, 69, 71, 97]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $51.9$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $55.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $6973$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$15054.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $36^{\\frac{1}{7}}$ _ $41^{\\frac{1}{5}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $5x + 3y = -18$ and $x - 7y = 4$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -3$, $y = -1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMLXXIII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $12$ and $7 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -757 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$21.26(-14.0\\theta + i-16.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-2.29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55, 89, 144$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(4)=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $9 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{25}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $49 = $",
    "solution": "$110001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $3.9 \\times 10^{56}$ and $3.77 \\times 10^{-84} = $",
    "solution": "$1.47 \\times 10^{-27}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$56-29=$",
    "solution": "$27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$54 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $49 = $",
    "solution": "$307.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -966 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $8, 18$ and $21$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o5071$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{6}{5}$ and $\\frac{3}{6}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -52 & -69 & -67 & 87 & -9 & -35 & 81 & 36 \\\\ 26 & 88 & -96 & -85 & -80 & -37 & -27 & -91 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 73 & 55 & 20 & 5 & 66 & -97 & 6 \\\\ -16 & 59 & 78 & -52 & 38 & 100 & -68 \\\\ -81 & 52 & -17 & -40 & -41 & 59 & -21 \\\\ 53 & -88 & 99 & 5 & -31 & -21 & 24 \\\\ 29 & 11 & -43 & -89 & -56 & -43 & -97 \\\\ -51 & -79 & -39 & 47 & 56 & 24 & 29 \\\\ -36 & 0 & 47 & -42 & 93 & 92 & 70 \\\\ 87 & -9 & -49 & -90 & 75 & -18 & -85 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 9086 & -15729 & 7125 & -1043 & 2773 & -1285 & 10343 \\\\ -3617 & 11972 & 8674 & 13674 & 4703 & 4105 & 6680 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6^8 =$",
    "solution": "$1679616$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$98\\div52=$",
    "solution": "$1.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MCVI$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 14m$, base width $= 50m$, and height $= 24m$ is",
    "solution": "$1400 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{633}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$8.59$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $13$ and $4 =$",
    "solution": "$52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(128)=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[3, 12, 48, 192, 768, 3072]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 6th term value, sum upto 11th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $3$, common ratio is $4$ , 6th term is $3072$, sum upto 11th term is $4194303.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1110000 = $",
    "solution": "$10000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$CDXXVI$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $16$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$0$ hours and $16$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 * \\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 3 \\\\ 3 & 10 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(17, 10)$ and $(9, -5)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{289}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o6606$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$54 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 4 m$, base width $= 15 m$ and height $= 6 m$ is",
    "solution": "$120.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.39\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=99.73$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=99.89\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$92.74$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{6} + 8x^{11} + 1x^{4} + 7x^{11} + 7x^{12} + 2x^{5} + 10x^{18} + 10x^{8} + 5x^{19} + 5x^{7}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{4} + 2x^{5} + 2x^{6} + 5x^{7} + 10x^{8} + 15x^{11} + 7x^{12} + 10x^{18} + 5x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $8$",
    "solution": "$2, 2, 2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 4 \\\\ 2 & 1 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -4 & 1 & 0 \\\\ 7 & -2 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 27m$ and radius $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$2162 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $42$ of the AP series: $10, 9, 8 ... $",
    "solution": "$-31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-8x-1)(-1x-5)$",
    "solution": "$8x^2+41x+5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $107 , 67, 25 =$",
    "solution": "$161$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $39 = $",
    "solution": "$100111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $9 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{25}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $55 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$348454.985 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $17$ and angle, $81$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 24.03318$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $15720$ from base $11$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$22165$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $15$ and $13 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1$",
    "solution": "$0x1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[274, 249, 271, 288, 243, 280, 248, 270, 266, 212, 237, 294, 201, 218, 206, 281, 252, 295, 216, 246, 242, 225, 231, 217, 276]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(258.8144078022002, 240.2255921977998)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{12} + 5x^{3} + 10x^{12} + 1x^{17}$",
    "solution": "$5x^{3} + 20x^{12} + 1x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $1010010100110001$ from base $2$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$42289$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $87$",
    "solution": "$3, 29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -597 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $11^{5^{7}}$",
    "solution": "$11^{35}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$58-57=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $18$ and $5 =$",
    "solution": "$90$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{655}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$8.68$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $14^{1^{1}}$",
    "solution": "$14^{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $18$ sides",
    "solution": "$160.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $30, 19, 31, 42, 26, 45, 35, 50, 38, 43, 29, 31, 47, 11, 20$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $33.13333333333333$, Standard Deviation is $117.9822222222222$, Variance is $10.861962171827988$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1268$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$101.44$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(128)=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $83x^2+168x+66=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.53, -1.49}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $3$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $15 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{10}{216}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-7x-8)(x-6)$",
    "solution": "$-7x^2+34x+48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$75-10=$",
    "solution": "$65$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 6x + 6 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.268, -4.732)) = (\\frac{-6 + \\sqrt{12}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-6 - \\sqrt{12}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $6$ sides",
    "solution": "$120.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $202$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 16 =",
    "solution": 74
  },
  {
    "problem": "$34$ % $33 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $114$ and $197$?",
    "solution": "$53.38$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $18$% of $63$?",
    "solution": "$11.34$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3^2=$",
    "solution": "$9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(-3,-16)$ and $(7,-11)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$2y = x -29$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$280\\div20=$",
    "solution": "$14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $22 = $",
    "solution": "$10110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $16$ and $8 =$",
    "solution": "$16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $157 , 42, 128 =$",
    "solution": "$33$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[92.28, 262.63, 905.86, 106.11, 543.52, 25.23, 115.6, 149.83, 899.43, 1.21, 813.11, 61.2]$ and $[786.49, 213.83, 347.68, 784.68, 825.61, 125.32, 598.46, 911.5, 424.78, 378.25, 784.65, 105.79]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.86$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $919 = $",
    "solution": "$0x397$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1777$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$159.93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $17$ and $17 = $",
    "solution": "$17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $35 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$89797.19 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $9 m = $",
    "solution": "$3053.6280592892786 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$001110100 = $",
    "solution": "$110001011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $4$ and $4$?",
    "solution": "$5.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $66$ of the AP series: $12, 8, 4 ... $",
    "solution": "$-248$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$600 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 2098 a leap year?",
    "solution": "2098 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$54 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 8m$ and radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$100 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$1809.5573684677208 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $49$% of $16$?",
    "solution": "$7.84$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -70 & -24 & -93 & -12 & -31 & -6 & 13 & -15 & 7 & 41 \\\\ -32 & 75 & -9 & -50 & 78 & -75 & -1 & -37 & 31 & -11 \\\\ -45 & 36 & -46 & -7 & -74 & -54 & 43 & -88 & -34 & 79 \\\\ -4 & 21 & -5 & -66 & -79 & 30 & -63 & 11 & 44 & -78 \\\\ 47 & 59 & -15 & -80 & 55 & -69 & -45 & -43 & 4 & -42 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -2 & 86 & -50 \\\\ 92 & 56 & 66 \\\\ -42 & 77 & -61 \\\\ 61 & 65 & -59 \\\\ 66 & 49 & -33 \\\\ -100 & -98 & 27 \\\\ -87 & 55 & 7 \\\\ -31 & 20 & -52 \\\\ -60 & -100 & 78 \\\\ -68 & -98 & 82 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -4214 & -20539 & 13937 \\\\ 17062 & 5860 & 8883 \\\\ 1078 & -7922 & 17532 \\\\ -2286 & -10655 & 5225 \\\\ 19478 & 10829 & 2290 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $19x + 6y = 6$ and $13x + 3y = 24$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 6$, $y = -18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 768 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3302$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$6434.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $237$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$3$ hours and $57$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $21, 42$ and $22$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $68 m = $",
    "solution": "$1317089.6816713943 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{16}=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$60\\div20=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $21 = $",
    "solution": "$10101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1^4 =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 41m$ and radius $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$28981 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 52m$, base width $= 48m$, and height $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$4992 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $4x + 11y = -212$ and $20x + -16y = -208$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -20$, $y = -12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $7$ sides?",
    "solution": "$900$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $11$ and $9$?",
    "solution": "$14.21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $12$ and angle $232$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$291.54$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-10,3)$ and passing through $(-16.0, 3.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$113.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[11, 121, 1331, 14641, 161051, 1771561]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 8th term value, sum upto 8th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $11$, common ratio is $11$ , 8th term is $214358881$, sum upto 8th term is $235794768.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $81$ and $95$?",
    "solution": "$15.91$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $6$ and $7 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1998 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1998 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8.54(-3.0\\theta + i-8.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$-1.93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-1,8)$ and passing through $(-3.0, 8.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$12.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(64)=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $9=$",
    "solution": "$254.47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[242.3994588887418, 479.5339907340535, 715.4367057069795, 576.9955964843915, 75.43303968195237, 502.1800209334787, 754.9034475636518, 917.414764177831, 329.3062557275943, 324.40634540902823, 319.3736773679433, 883.417840452695, 139.25810551416095, 211.70791076667385, 462.4835121257789]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2043.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $37x^2+76x+36=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.74, -1.31}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{933}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.77$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 975$ and $SP = 688$ is: ",
    "solution": "$29.44$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $26$ and angle, $255$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 115.71533$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{8}{3}$ and $\\frac{8}{7}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 4m$ and radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$804 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $7 , 167, 48 =$",
    "solution": "$138$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $86$ and $24 = $",
    "solution": "$70$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $2^{6}$ and $27^{6} = (2/27)^6 = 0.07407407407407407^{6}$",
    "solution": "$1.6519518666964456e-07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $7x^2 + 9x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.123, -1.163)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{53}}{2*7}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{53}}{2*7})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\csc)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc \\cdot \\cot$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[3, 27, 243, 2187, 19683, 177147]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 11th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $3$, common ratio is $9$ , 11th term is $10460353203$, sum upto 10th term is $1307544150.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{7}{3}$ and $\\frac{5}{8}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 20m$ and radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$742 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $275$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$4.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $18m, 20m, 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$1800 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$1734 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $124 , 14, 83 =$",
    "solution": "$139$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-18, -8, -3] \\times [-4, 7, -2] = $",
    "solution": "$[37, -24, -158]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $131$ and $21$?",
    "solution": "$144.74$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $166$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 8x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.268, -3.732)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{48}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{48}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$114\\div19=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $19^{7}$ and $29^{7} = (19/29)^7 = 0.6551724137931034^{7}$",
    "solution": "$0.05181902310416154$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\cot)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $4^{10}$ and $40^{10} = (4/40)^10 = 0.1^{10}$",
    "solution": "$1.0000000000000006e-10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 77th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$5527939700884771$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $8x^2 + 61x + 75 = $",
    "solution": "$108.1667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 40th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$102334155$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(30) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $115 , 123, 73 =$",
    "solution": "$49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 5, 6, 7}$, $b={8, 1, 10, 5}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 5, 6, 7, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${1, 5}$, a-b is ${6, 7}$, b-a is ${8, 10}$. Symmetric difference is ${6, 7, 8, 10}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-2x-8$",
    "solution": "$(x-4)(x+2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2.0(0.0\\theta + i2.0\\theta)$",
    "solution": "$1.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 13 m$, base width $= 10 m$ and height $= 42 m$ is",
    "solution": "$1820.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $16$ objects picked $5$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$524160$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(90) = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $2$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $2 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{36}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $27, 43, 12, 13, 28, 26, 16, 9, 30, 26, 31, 28, 9, 47, 32$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $25.133333333333333$, Standard Deviation is $123.18222222222221$, Variance is $11.098748678216937$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $559 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 13, 43, 559]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 14 m$, base width $= 3 m$ and height $= 42 m$ is",
    "solution": "$588.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[1, 3, 11, 18, 22, 45, 60, 71, 93, 97]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $42.1$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $33.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x + 7 = 9$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(3)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $19^{5^{5}}$",
    "solution": "$19^{25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $12$ objects picked $2$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -95 & -71 & -71 & 14 & -94 & -95 & -96 \\\\ 25 & -99 & 85 & 23 & -3 & 57 & 62 \\\\ 54 & 80 & 65 & -68 & -40 & -22 & 51 \\\\ 55 & -22 & -64 & -33 & -92 & 30 & 73 \\\\ 1 & 83 & -94 & 42 & 33 & -44 & -99 \\\\ -16 & 40 & -39 & 68 & 75 & -50 & 7 \\\\ 5 & -20 & -95 & -83 & 59 & 56 & -52 \\\\ 23 & 15 & 13 & 18 & -38 & -65 & 73 \\\\ 63 & -91 & -55 & 59 & -15 & 39 & 47 \\\\ 42 & 90 & 70 & 20 & 41 & 25 & 60 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -36 & -35 & 76 \\\\ 45 & 75 & 53 \\\\ -16 & -82 & 24 \\\\ -4 & -74 & -30 \\\\ -76 & 59 & 74 \\\\ 7 & -56 & -78 \\\\ -53 & 34 & -68 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 12872 & -704 & -6125 \\\\ -9466 & -18233 & -10881 \\\\ 1071 & 4418 & 7232 \\\\ 1519 & -511 & -11644 \\\\ 7466 & 11835 & 13565 \\\\ -3693 & 9189 & 6902 \\\\ -564 & 10834 & 3064 \\\\ -1869 & 1802 & -391 \\\\ -6797 & -10357 & -10473 \\\\ -4783 & 1119 & 6046 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-17x+70$",
    "solution": "$(x-10)(x-7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0101111 = $",
    "solution": "$1010000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[156.19365424101582, 79.45065164990639, 975.8156015920383, 481.7378031062325]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1102.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $32^{\\frac{1}{2}}$ _ $86^{\\frac{1}{7}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4^7 =$",
    "solution": "$16384$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $12$ objects picked $0$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $18$ objects picked $5$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$1028160$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[912.0206416110498, 720.0098195908641, 347.83654428337127, 767.0164045793899, 529.1657258134956, 204.49812008748114, 484.78127942340234]$ is:",
    "solution": "$1617.51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(729)=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $101$ composite?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$CCXXII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $35$ and $45 = $",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $6 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={8, 10, 2, 5}$, $b={1, 2, 7, 8, 10}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 5, 7, 8, 10}$. Intersection is ${8, 10, 2}$, a-b is ${5}$, b-a is ${1, 7}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 5, 7}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $560 = $",
    "solution": "$0x230$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $24$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 64 & 93 & 61 & 25 & -9 \\\\ -45 & 62 & 2 & -82 & -62 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 29 & 74 & -7 & 37 & 93 & 53 \\\\ 56 & 51 & 75 & -44 & 76 & -22 \\\\ 72 & -95 & 55 & -48 & 59 & -8 \\\\ -99 & -89 & -23 & -18 & 51 & -14 \\\\ -93 & -60 & -76 & 5 & 8 & 81 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 9818 & 1999 & 9991 & -5147 & 17822 & -221 \\\\ 16195 & 10660 & 11673 & -3323 & -4033 & -7639 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(9,10)$ and passing through $(9.0, 10.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$0.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4\\cdot2$",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-9+14j) * (-8-20j) = $",
    "solution": "$(352+68j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $30$ and angle $16$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$125.66$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$272\\div16=$",
    "solution": "$17$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[578.0, 404.75, 4.05, 645.48, 276.49, 853.72, 314.29, 397.27, 520.33, 106.92, 2.69, 82.6, 681.24, 777.22, 178.52, 665.9, 438.04, 133.94]$ and $[367.67, 950.54, 268.64, 353.87, 598.28, 679.34, 493.34, 242.73, 311.15, 708.15, 833.58, 9.43, 25.63, 491.4, 938.23, 478.69, 886.33, 733.43]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.82$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $5x^2 + 8x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.6, -1.0)) = (\\frac{-8 + 2}{2*5}, \\frac{-8 - 2}{2*5})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $251$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$4.38$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $66$% of $45$?",
    "solution": "$29.70$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $14$ objects picked $3$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$364$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $48880$ from base $10$ to base $4$.",
    "solution": "$23323300$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1643$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1150.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $919$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$15$ hours and $19$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $11$ of the AP series: $-2, 70, 142 ... $",
    "solution": "$718$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -845 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $93, 21, 48, 6 = $",
    "solution": "$24.40296759078485$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $17$ and $71$?",
    "solution": "$122.73$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $5.97 \\times 10^{22}$ and $3.3 \\times 10^{-50} = $",
    "solution": "$1.97 \\times 10^{-27}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $11100 = $",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[5, 24, 25, 33, 41, 60, 72, 79, 88, 92]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $51.9$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $50.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $117$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $17$ objects picked $4$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$57120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10011000 = $",
    "solution": "$01100111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $7$ and $19 =$",
    "solution": "$133$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[10, 80, 640, 5120, 40960, 327680]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 6th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $10$, common ratio is $8$ , 6th term is $327680$, sum upto 10th term is $1533916890.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{81}=$",
    "solution": "$9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $60$ and $37 = $",
    "solution": "$83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[3, 9, 27, 81, 243, 729]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 9th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $3$, common ratio is $3$ , 9th term is $19683$, sum upto 10th term is $88572.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 16m$ and $r1 = 17m$ is and $r2 = 17m$ is ",
    "solution": "$10673.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=10*x^3 + 2*x^2 + 9$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{2}{15}, 0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-1x-3)(3x-9)$",
    "solution": "$-3x^2x+27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the series of numbers $[2, 14, 24, 33, 35, 44, 82, 88, 92, 96]$. Find the arithmatic mean and mdian of the series",
    "solution": "Arithmetic mean of the series is $51.0$ and Arithmetic median of this series is $39.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $247$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[6, 14, 14]\\cdot[7, 4, -17]=$",
    "solution": "$-140$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $39 = $",
    "solution": "$245.04$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{40}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$3.42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$384 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $25$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMCCXXXIV$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $46^{2}$ and $45^{2} = (46/45)^2 = 1.0222222222222221^{2}$",
    "solution": "$1.044938271604938$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $47x^2 + 94x + 95 = $",
    "solution": "$157.6667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $47^{9^{8}}$",
    "solution": "$47^{72}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$1014 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1001101011 = $",
    "solution": "$110010101$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $62 = $",
    "solution": "$389.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $45$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $16x^2 + 27x + 0 = $",
    "solution": "$18.8333$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $33$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{62}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$3.96$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o6674$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1934 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1934 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x + 7 = 9$",
    "solution": "$2/9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $59^{\\frac{1}{8}}$ _ $89^{\\frac{1}{7}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{17} + 4x^{11} + 4x^{18} + 10x^{14} + 8x^{18} + 9x^{16}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{11} + 10x^{14} + 9x^{16} + 8x^{17} + 12x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(279463109,597460156)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 35m$ and radius $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$782 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$19^8 =$",
    "solution": "$16983563041$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $49, 91 = $",
    "solution": "$2898.3500000000004$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{3} + 9x^{8} + 4x^{2} + 2x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{9}{8}x^{9} + \\frac{4}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{2}{4}x^{5} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $3$ numbers $[64, 100, 2] = $",
    "solution": "$23.39$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 16m$, base width $= 16m$, and height $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$448 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[598.94, 497.67, 9.93, 222.78, 10.64, 784.84, 96.89, 482.35]$ and $[302.45, 673.03, 300.51, 323.56, 54.81, 886.21, 565.36, 24.72]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.63$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-1x-42$",
    "solution": "$(x+6)(x-7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o5526$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-4,-10)$ and passing through $(-4.0, -10.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$0.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $55$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$0$ hours and $55$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\tan(60) = $",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+3x-40$",
    "solution": "$(x-5)(x+8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 2 m$, base width $= 17 m$ and height $= 49 m$ is",
    "solution": "$555.3333333333334 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$19^2=$",
    "solution": "$361$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $17$ and height, $13$?",
    "solution": "$1388.58$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 85 & 9 & 4 & -28 \\\\ -55 & 91 & -72 & -45 \\\\ 4 & 44 & -8 & -31 \\\\ -85 & 45 & 13 & 0 \\\\ -96 & -3 & -37 & -41 \\\\ -35 & 2 & -7 & 95 \\\\ -74 & 61 & 38 & 75 \\\\ 21 & 42 & -20 & -57 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -50 & 86 & -90 & 99 & 55 & -59 \\\\ 58 & 30 & 54 & -87 & -71 & -4 \\\\ 9 & -73 & -92 & 19 & -16 & 100 \\\\ 47 & 9 & 64 & 53 & 4 & -85 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -5008 & 7036 & -9324 & 6224 & 3860 & -2271 \\\\ 5265 & 2851 & 13608 & -17115 & -8514 & -494 \\\\ 823 & 1969 & 768 & -5227 & -2900 & 1423 \\\\ 6977 & -6909 & 8884 & -12083 & -8078 & 6135 \\\\ 2366 & -6014 & 9258 & -12119 & -4639 & 5461 \\\\ 6268 & -1584 & 9982 & 1263 & -1575 & -6718 \\\\ 11105 & -6633 & 11258 & -7936 & -8709 & 1547 \\\\ -1473 & 4013 & -1430 & -4976 & -1735 & 1438 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $13$ terms of the AP series: $25, 12, -1 ... $",
    "solution": "$-689.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$21+2=$",
    "solution": "$23$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 24m$, base width $= 24m$, and height $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$816 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $846 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 3, 6, 9, 18, 47, 94, 141, 282, 423, 846]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{11} + 3x^{5} + 7x^{3} + 1x^{14} + 4x^{16} + 9x^{8} + 9x^{6} + 7x^{5}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{3} + 10x^{5} + 9x^{6} + 9x^{8} + 4x^{11} + 1x^{14} + 4x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $3435$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$137.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$20$ % $81 = $",
    "solution": "$20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$110$",
    "solution": "$0x6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $61$",
    "solution": "$61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $15$ and angle, $216$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 56.54867$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -845 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -10/2x + 7$ and $y = 4/5x - 9$",
    "solution": "$(80/29, -197/29)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $13$ objects picked $0$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $9, 13 13 = $",
    "solution": "$54.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $13m, 20m, 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$780 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sqrt{16}=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x + 10 = 10$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{6}{9}$ and $\\frac{8}{9}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $28x^2+173x+84=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.53, -5.65}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $5$ sided polygon with lengths of $13, 39, 39, 43, 67$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$201$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $44$ and angle, $271$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 208.11306$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[216, 240, 272, 276, 297, 271, 201, 286, 215, 203, 228, 229, 262, 231, 212, 205, 218, 275, 202, 244, 299, 242, 234, 251, 290]$ with $95$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(256.2302787799463, 231.68972122005374)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.40\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=92.41$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=97.44\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$12.66$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-4x - 3y = 41$ and $-7x + 6y = 38$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -8$, $y = -3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $5.07 \\times 10^{-28}$ and $1.61 \\times 10^{32} = $",
    "solution": "$8.16 \\times 10^{4}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $4 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $9$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{6}{2}\\cdot\\frac{3}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{9}{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(27)=$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -7/4x - 6$ and $y = -10/5x - 8$",
    "solution": "$(-8, 8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -72 & 42 & 71 & 17 & -56 & 80 \\\\ 8 & 51 & -15 & -76 & 66 & -95 \\\\ -60 & 45 & 91 & -69 & -33 & 95 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -60 & 89 & 91 & -13 & -14 & 59 \\\\ 11 & -78 & 30 & -25 & 73 & 20 \\\\ 56 & 29 & -79 & 90 & -49 & -22 \\\\ 63 & -51 & 69 & 8 & -89 & -4 \\\\ -47 & -59 & -89 & -64 & -14 & 89 \\\\ -66 & 10 & 62 & -20 & -56 & 38 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 7181 & -4388 & 216 & 8396 & -4614 & -6982 \\\\ -2379 & -4669 & -13565 & -5661 & 15506 & 4390 \\\\ 125 & 205 & -7233 & 7505 & 949 & -3693 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $2$ numbers $[37, 99] = $",
    "solution": "$60.52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $4$ and $5 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 464 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $13 m = $",
    "solution": "$9202.7720799157 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $55$ and $35 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 5]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 827$ and $SP = 801$ is: ",
    "solution": "$3.14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $652 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4, 163, 326, 652]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[11, 99, 891, 8019, 72171, 649539]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 11th term value, sum upto 10th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $11$, common ratio is $9$ , 11th term is $38354628411$, sum upto 10th term is $4794328550.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $137$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$2$ hours and $17$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 21 & -43 & -45 \\\\ -40 & -16 & 45 \\\\ 100 & 9 & -78 \\\\ 85 & 8 & -38 \\\\ 13 & 42 & -18 \\\\ -40 & -8 & -68 \\\\ -48 & -49 & -48 \\\\ 6 & 98 & 35 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -58 & -75 & -100 & -65 & 49 \\\\ 13 & 28 & 78 & 10 & -18 \\\\ -3 & 27 & -59 & 98 & -30 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -1642 & -3994 & -2799 & -6205 & 3153 \\\\ 1977 & 3767 & 97 & 6850 & -3022 \\\\ -5449 & -9354 & -4696 & -14054 & 7078 \\\\ -4712 & -7177 & -5634 & -9169 & 5161 \\\\ -154 & -285 & 3038 & -2189 & 421 \\\\ 2420 & 940 & 7388 & -4144 & 224 \\\\ 2291 & 932 & 3810 & -2074 & -30 \\\\ 821 & 3239 & 4979 & 4020 & -2520 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $59=$",
    "solution": "$10935.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $21 = $",
    "solution": "$0x15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $43 m = $",
    "solution": "$333038.1428119516 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $42, 9, 26, 41, 44, 35, 46, 41, 8, 5, 15, 30, 6, 43, 18$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $27.266666666666666$, Standard Deviation is $228.72888888888886$, Variance is $15.123785534345853$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 46m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$3527 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $60 = $",
    "solution": "$111100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|49--91|=$",
    "solution": "$140$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $18$ objects picked $6$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$18564$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $6m, 5m, 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$150 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.42\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=97.98$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=98.83\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$26.1$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{3}\\cdot\\frac{7}{2}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{14}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$43+41=$",
    "solution": "$84$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $3.02$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$173.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $93x^2 + 48x + 68 = $",
    "solution": "$123.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $16, 13$ and $9$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $31$ of the AP series: $88, -12, -112 ... $",
    "solution": "$-2912$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 22m$ and radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$276 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$CDLI$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $1$ and angle $157$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$1.37$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the area of a sector with radius $27$ and angle $260$ degrees?",
    "solution": "$1654.05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$110000101$",
    "solution": "$389$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $122$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={4, 5}$, $b={1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 9}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 9}$. Intersection is ${5}$, a-b is ${4}$, b-a is ${1, 2, 3, 6, 9}$. Symmetric difference is ${1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 9}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $44$ and height, $60$?",
    "solution": "$16587.61$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$31+13=$",
    "solution": "$44$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $65 , 144, 104 =$",
    "solution": "$47$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Third angle of triangle with angles $76$ and $13 = $",
    "solution": "$91$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 954$ and $SP = 797$ is: ",
    "solution": "$16.46$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of frustum with height $= 10m$ and $r1 = 11m$ is and $r2 = 11m$ is ",
    "solution": "$5791.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $49$ and angle, $136$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 116.30874$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 36m$ and radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$40828 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 39m$ and radius $= 19m$ is",
    "solution": "$44230 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $50$% of $63$?",
    "solution": "$31.50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-1x-4)(-5x+10)$",
    "solution": "$5x^2+10x-40$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $8$ prime?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $178 , 45, 7 =$",
    "solution": "$130$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $-23$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$-9.399999999999999$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $16$ sides",
    "solution": "$157.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $20$ and $1 =$",
    "solution": "$20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-11x + 18y = 446$ and $-8x + -3y = 83$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -16$, $y = 15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[628.7004616268383, 390.48938744290786, 704.4633258640598, 264.7621535621271, 492.01657796194354, 772.4270387243312, 513.8015572531727, 660.8884888139976, 596.8898981251216, 268.8450072726872, 638.0798580269981, 681.2904673822243, 331.3762882483369, 502.2313620625356, 267.07850602800556, 808.8271458464011, 832.9710463806491, 578.2174156325017]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2463.58$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $3$ sides?",
    "solution": "$180$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\csc)=$",
    "solution": "$-\\csc \\cdot \\cot$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $891 = $",
    "solution": "$0x37b$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-7,-19)$ and $(11,9) = $",
    "solution": "$(2.0,-5.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{366}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$7.15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 8x + 7 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.293, -2.707)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{8}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{8}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $153$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $10$ objects picked $6$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$210$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{7}{1}\\div\\frac{9}{2}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{14}{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $1$ and $11$?",
    "solution": "$11.05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $514 = $",
    "solution": "$0x202$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 24m$ and radius $= 14m$ is",
    "solution": "$14778 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $50$ and $100$?",
    "solution": "$66.67$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $94 = $",
    "solution": "$590.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[0.9, 992.36, 67.84, 915.04, 44.82, 955.1, 262.69, 896.67, 395.95, 788.35, 528.17, 77.99, 745.09, 631.43, 353.94, 973.39]$ and $[700.37, 613.88, 124.58, 470.73, 667.6, 836.97, 181.26, 525.32, 769.56, 314.02, 28.83, 882.75, 507.22, 123.23, 342.56, 682.38]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.73$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $42, 33$ and $23$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 222 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given radius, $14$ and angle, $202$. Find the arc length of the angle.",
    "solution": "Arc length of the angle $= 49.35791$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $99$ and exact value equals $34$.",
    "solution": "$191.18\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the curved surface area of a cylinder of radius, $45$ and height, $3$?",
    "solution": "$848.23$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $326 = $",
    "solution": "$0x146$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-9x-10)(4x-3)$",
    "solution": "$-36x^2-13x+30$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $350$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$6.11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $105$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$1.83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $3$ and $2 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{3}{9}\\div\\frac{3}{5}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of 947 is =",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $23x^2 + 10x + 88 = $",
    "solution": "$100.6667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{10}{1}\\cdot\\frac{4}{9}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{40}{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $900$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$15$ hours and $0$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$50-37=$",
    "solution": "$13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1979 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1979 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3! =$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $8.28 \\times 10^{80}$ and $9.05 \\times 10^{-22} = $",
    "solution": "$7.49 \\times 10^{59}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $183$ and $102$?",
    "solution": "$56.84$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{343}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$7.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $152 , 86, 10 =$",
    "solution": "$112$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$f(x)=x^2 + x + 2$",
    "solution": "${- \\frac{1}{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The complementary angle of 69 =",
    "solution": 21
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1$",
    "solution": "$0x1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $186$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $48$ and $4 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the mean,standard deviation and variance for the data $40, 32, 47, 12, 47, 12, 40, 17, 5, 14, 39, 48, 22, 48, 37$",
    "solution": "The Mean is $30.666666666666668$, Standard Deviation is $221.02222222222224$, Variance is $14.866816142746309$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 15 m$, base width $= 2 m$ and height $= 50 m$ is",
    "solution": "$500.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $99x^2+148x+49=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.49, -1.0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $28=$",
    "solution": "$2463.01$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $80$ terms of the AP series: $43, -50, -143 ... $",
    "solution": "$-290440.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(14, 16)$ and $(-9, -18)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{1685}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $7, 19 20 = $",
    "solution": "$66.45$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $3x^2 + 9x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.242, -2.758)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{57}}{2*3}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{57}}{2*3})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $33^{7}$ and $1^{7} = (33/1)^7 = 33.0^{7}$",
    "solution": "$42618442977.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $870 = $",
    "solution": "$0x366$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $77 = $",
    "solution": "$483.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $10$ and $1 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $15m, 12m, 1m$ is",
    "solution": "$180 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $232$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $8129 = $",
    "solution": "$115121$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $0.49$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$28.07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{2}{2}x^{3} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $73x^2+125x+41=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.44, -1.27}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10^4 =$",
    "solution": "$10000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6^2=$",
    "solution": "$36$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{1}{4}\\div\\frac{10}{1}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{40}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $3914 = $",
    "solution": "$15410$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $7 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$718.378 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$38\\div66=$",
    "solution": "$0.58$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $7$ sides",
    "solution": "$128.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[11, 66, 396, 2376, 14256, 85536]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 8th term value, sum upto 6th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $11$, common ratio is $6$ , 8th term is $3079296$, sum upto 6th term is $102641.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 9 m$, base width $= 12 m$ and height $= 29 m$ is",
    "solution": "$1044.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cuboid with sides = $3m, 18m, 18m$ is",
    "solution": "$972 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$93$ % $52 = $",
    "solution": "$41$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{4}{1}\\cdot\\frac{8}{1}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{32}{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-24-8|=$",
    "solution": "$32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $195$ and $127$?",
    "solution": "$42.24$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-8--3|=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[10, 110, 1210, 13310, 146410, 1610510]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 10th term value, sum upto 7th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $10$, common ratio is $11$ , 10th term is $23579476910$, sum upto 7th term is $19487170.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10^2=$",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $3$ and $17 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$93\\div50=$",
    "solution": "$1.86$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0111100000$",
    "solution": "$480$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $247$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$4.31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{9} + 2x^{5} + 1x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$90x^{8} + 10x^{4} + 3x^{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $20$ and $11 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $35441$ from base $10$ to base $14$.",
    "solution": "$CCB7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $17 m = $",
    "solution": "$20579.526276115535 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $43^{9}$ and $43^{3} = $43^{9-3} = 43^{6}$",
    "solution": "$6321363049$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{10}{7}\\div\\frac{4}{10}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{25}{7}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1! =$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1 * \\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 7 \\\\ 5 & 8 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 7 \\\\ 5 & 8 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $1, 6 6 = $",
    "solution": "$2.99$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-16x+63$",
    "solution": "$(x-7)(x-9)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-98-53|=$",
    "solution": "$151$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 50m$ and radius $= 8m$ is",
    "solution": "$10053 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-9+4j) * -1j = $",
    "solution": "$(4+9j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "For the given GP $[2, 14, 98, 686, 4802, 33614]$. Find the value of a common ratio, 8th term value, sum upto 8th term",
    "solution": "The value of a is $2$, common ratio is $7$ , 8th term is $1647086$, sum upto 8th term is $1921600.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "angle between the vectors $[744.22, 174.84, 717.47, 231.45, 794.85, 502.22, 226.46, 557.79, 649.96, 657.14, 157.09, 57.05, 672.03, 670.08, 460.93, 767.52, 763.09]$ and $[213.09, 164.21, 378.06, 273.92, 209.21, 591.34, 771.89, 882.08, 638.04, 626.11, 622.93, 978.04, 432.08, 761.02, 863.06, 728.25, 207.59]$ is:",
    "solution": "$0.69$ radians"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Fibonacci Series of the first ${n}$ numbers is ?",
    "solution": "$0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$DCLII$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $18, 17 22 = $",
    "solution": "$149.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 17th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$1597$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is 1951 a leap year?",
    "solution": "1951 is not a leap year"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $19$ objects picked $9$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$92378$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{7} + 5x^{1} + 6x^{1} + 6x^{15} + 4x^{6} + 7x^{18} + 3x^{13} + 8x^{1} + 6x^{16}$",
    "solution": "$19x^{1} + 4x^{6} + 4x^{7} + 3x^{13} + 6x^{15} + 6x^{16} + 7x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12+39=$",
    "solution": "$51$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $30, 29$ and $4$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[19, 8, 15]\\cdot[9, -18, 18]=$",
    "solution": "$297$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $2$ numbers $28, 67 = $",
    "solution": "$1323.0736842105264$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $51$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $80$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$1.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 6m$ and radius $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$452 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $87^{\\frac{1}{1}}$ _ $84^{\\frac{1}{4}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-20,14)$ and $(-8,-18) = $",
    "solution": "$(-14.0,-2.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$000$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$99-36=$",
    "solution": "$63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $5$ sided polygon with lengths of $27, 67, 3, 91, 42$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$230$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $174 = $",
    "solution": "$0xae$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $20$ and $7 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Number of Permutations from $11$ objects picked $6$ at a time is: ",
    "solution": "$332640$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cuboid with sides of lengths: $18m, 11m, 20m$ is",
    "solution": "$1556 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o4400$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-2$ and exact value equals $-17$.",
    "solution": "$88.24\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 96 & 33 \\\\ 100 & 59 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$2364$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $13 = $",
    "solution": "$81.68$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "GCD of $19$ and $15 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{847}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.46$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $9771$ from base $13$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$21048$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x + 1 = 8$",
    "solution": "$7/5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Loss percent when $CP = 463$ and $SP = 174$ is: ",
    "solution": "$62.42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{987}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$9.96$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the other two sides have lengths $9$ and $15$?",
    "solution": "$17.49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $7928$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$18693.81$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{1} + 6x^{3} + 10x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$5x^{0} + 18x^{2} + 20x^{1}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 7x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.314, -3.186)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{33}}{2*2}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{33}}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-2,-2)$ and passing through $(5.0, -2.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$153.94$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$50+13=$",
    "solution": "$63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$000$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(30) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $135$ and $68$?",
    "solution": "$66.01$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{8}{4}\\div\\frac{6}{10}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{10}{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Harmonic mean of $4$ numbers $2, 68, 65, 39 = $",
    "solution": "$70.17777174650564$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMCCCXV$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$19^2=$",
    "solution": "$361$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $41243$ from base $6$ to base $16$.",
    "solution": "$157B$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7 * \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 10 \\\\ 4 & 10 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 49 & 70 \\\\ 28 & 70 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$000111110 = $",
    "solution": "$111000001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The supplementary angle of 99 =",
    "solution": 81
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $59$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$1.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Circumference of circle with radius $10 = $",
    "solution": "$62.83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{7} + 6x^{19} + 3x^{19}$",
    "solution": "$8x^{7} + 9x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 6 & 24 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 20 \\\\ 2 & 10 & 41 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -5 & 6 & 0 \\\\ 1 & 7 & -4 \\\\ 0 & -2 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0011110001 = $",
    "solution": "$1100001110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $5$ composite?",
    "solution": "No"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $48 = $",
    "solution": "$110000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-2--56|=$",
    "solution": "$54$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5! =$",
    "solution": "$120$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 49m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$15393 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $16$ and $9 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 50m$ and radius $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$2111 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 17m$ and radius $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$1055 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $3920$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1411.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-16, -12, 15] \\times [-20, -3, 7] = $",
    "solution": "$[-39, -188, -192]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The perimeter of a $5$ sided polygon with lengths of $51, 44, 40, 109, 25$cm is: ",
    "solution": "$269$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $22$ terms of the AP series: $100, 171, 242 ... $",
    "solution": "$18601.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x + 10 = 10$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Product of scientific notations $5.2 \\times 10^{92}$ and $4.34 \\times 10^{-61} = $",
    "solution": "$2.26 \\times 10^{32}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-20,-8)$ and $(-1,-9) = $",
    "solution": "$(-10.5,-8.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -3/5x + 3$ and $y = 5$",
    "solution": "$(-10/3, 5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(17, -19)$ and $(15, -9)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{104}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $39^{\\frac{1}{2}}$ _ $66^{\\frac{1}{3}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $4343$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$5836.63$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{261}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$6.39$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 21m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$1044 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $11^{10^{7}}$",
    "solution": "$11^{70}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If $1$ dice are rolled at the same time, the probability of getting a sum of $6 =$",
    "solution": "\\frac{1}{6}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $5$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$22374$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the 20th Fibonacci number?",
    "solution": "$6765$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $10$ and $11 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(315363031,381542403)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The confidence interval for sample $[264, 253, 238, 288, 231, 229, 207, 272, 294, 226, 280, 252, 298, 225, 223, 224, 290, 209, 201, 206, 268, 263, 228, 212, 220, 215, 227, 217, 295]$ with $90$% confidence is",
    "solution": "$(252.62653866340463, 233.92518547452642)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{5}{1}\\cdot\\frac{4}{8}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{5}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $146A5$ from base $12$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$28637$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of triangle with side lengths: $7, 5 3 = $",
    "solution": "$6.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $0.8$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$45.84$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 10m$ and radius $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$94 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$113.09733552923255 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $1000010101000111$ from base $2$ to base $16$.",
    "solution": "$8547$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|13-78|=$",
    "solution": "$65$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{5} + 3x^{5} + 1x^{3} + 1x^{1} + 10x^{14} + 9x^{11} + 10x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{1} + 1x^{3} + 12x^{5} + 10x^{9} + 9x^{11} + 10x^{14}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $7342 = $",
    "solution": "$1121014$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{7} + 4x^{10} + 5x^{2} + 6x^{6} + 4x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{6} + 40x^{9} + 10x^{1} + 36x^{5} + 16x^{3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$22+34=$",
    "solution": "$56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $172$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$3.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of sphere with radius $47 m = $",
    "solution": "$434892.7654315374 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$000 = $",
    "solution": "$111$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $1m$ is",
    "solution": "$1 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 13m$ is",
    "solution": "$1014 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{378}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$7.23$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{4} + 10x^{2} + 1x^{1} + 3x^{6} + 9x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{4}{4}x^{5} + \\frac{10}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{1}{1}x^{2} + \\frac{3}{6}x^{7} + \\frac{9}{2}x^{3} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $0.34\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=96.16$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=90.23\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$3.25$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$DCLXIX$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 25m$ and radius $= 2m$ is",
    "solution": "$104 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$69\\div96=$",
    "solution": "$0.72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 25m$ and radius $= 17m$ is",
    "solution": "$4486 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the two sets $a={1, 3, 4, 5, 8}$, $b={1, 4, 6, 8, 9}. Find the Union, intersection, a-b, b-a, and symmetric difference",
    "solution": "Union is ${1, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 9}$. Intersection is ${8, 1, 4}$, a-b is ${3, 5}$, b-a is ${9, 6}$. Symmetric difference is ${3, 5, 6, 9}$."
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $11100 = $",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $37.55$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $11$ pistons will contain no more than $2$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$15.49$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $10$ and $10 =$",
    "solution": "$10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $50$ and $2 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Integer of Binary Coded Decimal $3$ is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$14745$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $43, 45$ and $21$ exist?",
    "solution": "$Yes$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{8}{3}$ and $\\frac{5}{1}$?",
    "solution": "<"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x + 10 = 10$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $8$ and $5 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $773 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 773]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[3, -2, 4] \\times [16, 3, -4] = $",
    "solution": "$[-4, 76, 41]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $3^{6}$ and $3^{5} = $3^{6-5} = 3^{1}$",
    "solution": "$3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 8x + 6 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.0, -3.0)) = (\\frac{-8 + 4}{2*2}, \\frac{-8 - 4}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6! =$",
    "solution": "$720$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMCMLXXXI$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $10010 = $",
    "solution": "$1110$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-1, -6)$ and $(-17, -3)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{265}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4! =$",
    "solution": "$24$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $10$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o526$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9109$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$12466.3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{2} + 10x^{10} + 9x^{9} + 1x^{2} + 1x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{6}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{10}{10}x^{11} + \\frac{9}{9}x^{10} + \\frac{1}{2}x^{3} + \\frac{1}{1}x^{2} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $271$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$4.73$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(x-6)(9x+10)$",
    "solution": "$x^2-54x-60$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $81 = $",
    "solution": "$1010001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4^2=$",
    "solution": "$16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $82^{\\frac{1}{5}}$ _ $83^{\\frac{1}{3}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $15$ sides",
    "solution": "$156.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $42^{9}$ and $42^{7} = $42^{9-7} = 42^{2}$",
    "solution": "$1764$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $69$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$156.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cube with a side length of $17m$ is",
    "solution": "$4913 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -532 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2! =$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $10$ and $3 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$17^2=$",
    "solution": "$289$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 10m$, base width $= 8m$, and height $= 3m$ is",
    "solution": "$160 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 15m$ is",
    "solution": "$1350 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $75$ of the AP series: $-70, -47, -24 ... $",
    "solution": "$1632$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the cube root of: $\\sqrt[3]{553}=$ to 2 decimal places?",
    "solution": "$8.21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Someone tested positive for a nasty disease which only $1.49\\%$ of the population have. Test sensitivity (true positive) is equal to $SN=92.09$% whereas test specificity (true negative) $SP=97.13\\%$. What is the probability that this guy really has that disease?",
    "solution": "$32.67$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $26^{7}$ and $32^{7} = (26/32)^7 = 0.8125^{7}$",
    "solution": "$0.2337564416229725$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $39 , 175, 13 =$",
    "solution": "$133$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$81-24=$",
    "solution": "$57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$350\\div25=$",
    "solution": "$14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $38$ terms of the AP series: $99, 161, 223 ... $",
    "solution": "$47348.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$MMMCCCXXIX$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sin)=$",
    "solution": "$\\cos$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $26 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 13, 26]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $20^{4}$ and $3^{4} = (20/3)^4 = 6.666666666666667^{4}$",
    "solution": "$1975.308641975309$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 5 & 15 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 16 \\\\ 1 & 6 & 18 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 0 & -5 \\\\ 2 & -3 & 1 \\\\ -1 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(232484581,88291502)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find term number $70$ of the AP series: $100, 31, -38 ... $",
    "solution": "$-4661$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $45 , 7, 145 =$",
    "solution": "$163$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{9}{8}\\div\\frac{7}{9}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{81}{56}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with radius $89=$",
    "solution": "$24884.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "HCF of $3$ and $20 = $",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $50^{5}$ and $50^{4} = $50^{5-4} = 50^{1}$",
    "solution": "$50$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$30x^{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $43691$ from base $10$ to base $12$.",
    "solution": "$2134B$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "BCD of Decimal Number $9796 = $",
    "solution": "$2644$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $35 = $",
    "solution": "$100011$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-28$ and exact value equals $-20$.",
    "solution": "$40.0\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The decimal number ${x}$ in Octal is: ",
    "solution": "$0o7703$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "signum of -583 is =",
    "solution": "$-1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $1$ and $4 =$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[345.76789209543637, 276.975446571887]$ is:",
    "solution": "$443.02$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+7x$",
    "solution": "$(x+7)(x)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-18, 20, -7] \\times [-1, -17, -1] = $",
    "solution": "$[-139, -11, 326]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $695$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$11$ hours and $35$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the sum of interior angles of a polygon with $9$ sides?",
    "solution": "$1260$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Geometric mean of $3$ numbers $[2, 31, 22] = $",
    "solution": "$11.09$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 16m$, base width $= 12m$, and height $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$384 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 20 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 6 & 0 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -5 & 6 \\\\ 0 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 1 & 0 & -4 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$50\\div68=$",
    "solution": "$0.74$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\tan)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec^{{2}}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $1.69$ radians in degrees is: ",
    "solution": "$96.83$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$55\\div88=$",
    "solution": "$0.62$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6\\div98=$",
    "solution": "$0.06$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $30^{7}$ and $7^{7} = (30/7)^7 = 4.285714285714286^{7}$",
    "solution": "$26555.990397587007$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\tan(0) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(6x+6)(6x-3)$",
    "solution": "$36x^2+18x-18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{d}{dx}(\\sec)=$",
    "solution": "$\\sec \\cdot \\tan$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $88 = $",
    "solution": "$1011000$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|-9--53|=$",
    "solution": "$44$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Does triangle with sides $13, 22$ and $35$ exist?",
    "solution": "$No$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $84$ degrees Celsius to degrees Fahrenheit",
    "solution": "$183.20000000000002$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{9}{6}\\div\\frac{5}{4}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{6}{5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\sin(0) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{2}{5}\\cdot\\frac{6}{5}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{12}{25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Common Factors of $36$ and $16 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $7814$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$9306.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $2x^2+178x+84=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.47, -88.53}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(60) = $",
    "solution": "$\\frac{1}{2}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $6748$ dollars, $2$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1079.68$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The Quotient of $35^{7}$ and $12^{7} = (35/12)^7 = 2.9166666666666665^{7}$",
    "solution": "$1795.5916953730043$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $158$",
    "solution": "$2, 79$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-9x - 10y = -153$ and $-8x + 8y = 16$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 7$, $y = 9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -x - 8$ and $y = 8$",
    "solution": "$(-16, 8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$864 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $294$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$4$ hours and $54$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cube with side $= 16m$ is",
    "solution": "$1536 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $20$ objects picked $3$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$1140$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{2} + 1x^{8} + 8x^{16} + 1x^{1} + 9x^{17} + 10x^{19} + 7x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{1} + 7x^{2} + 1x^{8} + 7x^{9} + 8x^{16} + 9x^{17} + 10x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 48m$, base width $= 48m$, and height $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$4800 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$73-73=$",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(17, 16)$ and $(17, 9)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{49}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "A manufacturer of metal pistons finds that, on average, $32.56$% of the pistons they manufacture are rejected because they are incorrectly sized. What is the probability that a batch of $12$ pistons will contain no more than $6$ rejected pistons?",
    "solution": "$94.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6! =$",
    "solution": "$720$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $11B6$ from base $16$ to base $11$.",
    "solution": "$3452$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1588$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$142.92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $5$ prime?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0$ % $81 = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $8$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$0.14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Angle $73$ degrees in radians is: ",
    "solution": "$1.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$|76--54|=$",
    "solution": "$130$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4+26=$",
    "solution": "$30$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 16 & 55 \\\\ 63 & 90 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-2025$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-3x+3)(x-7)$",
    "solution": "$-3x^2+24x-21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "2's complement of $1001010111 = $",
    "solution": "$110101001$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$14^3 =$",
    "solution": "$2744$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-5,-3)$ and passing through $(-8.0, -3.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$28.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the number of combinations from $16$ objects picked $9$ at a time.",
    "solution": "$11440$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the sum of first $64$ terms of the AP series: $-48, -28, -8 ... $",
    "solution": "$37248.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 49m$ and radius $= 4m$ is",
    "solution": "$668 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $720$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$12$ hours and $0$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $9x - 2y = 87$ and $-3x - y = -24$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 9$, $y = -3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The number $0$ in Roman Numerals is: ",
    "solution": "$DLXI$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the equation of the line between points $(7,-5)$ and $(-5,-16)$ in slope-intercept form?",
    "solution": "$12y = 11x -137$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\frac{1}{5}\\cdot\\frac{6}{7}=$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{6}{35}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1011001$",
    "solution": "$89$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of hemisphere with radius $23 m =$ ",
    "solution": "$25482.505 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10^2 =$",
    "solution": "$100$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-20, -19, 13] \\times [-14, -14, -14] = $",
    "solution": "$[448, -462, 14]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $10^{7^{6}}$",
    "solution": "$10^{42}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of Sphere with radius $= 7m$ is",
    "solution": "$615.7521601035994 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cylinder with height $= 39m$ and radius $= 12m$ is",
    "solution": "$17643 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$GCD(772434178,670180020)=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $34^{\\frac{1}{4}}$ _ $95^{\\frac{1}{2}}$",
    "solution": "$<$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of pyramid with base length $= 9 m$, base width $= 19 m$ and height $= 28 m$ is",
    "solution": "$1596.0 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Euclidian norm or L2 norm of the vector $[378.37536546112017, 974.2822780754054, 72.15944056865209, 915.7471585836192, 724.109289427761, 410.94201601019984, 512.2423563100298, 162.96743056665886, 815.5113359872709, 657.518053001641, 284.14250023987444, 540.4771044078807, 142.71727421987478, 128.57818324127757, 58.74150745684892, 897.135166509579, 181.36397300662276, 792.099210162486, 923.3638015418095, 237.8550579389054]$ is:",
    "solution": "$2608.31$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Is $99$ composite?",
    "solution": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Which symbol represents the comparison between $\\frac{8}{5}$ and $\\frac{5}{10}$?",
    "solution": ">"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cylinder with height $= 42m$ and radius $= 10m$ is",
    "solution": "$3267 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of cone with height $= 8m$ and radius $= 9m$ is",
    "solution": "$594 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fill in the blanks $47^{\\frac{1}{1}}$ _ $35^{\\frac{1}{2}}$",
    "solution": "$>$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(2)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0101 = $",
    "solution": "$1010$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the angle of a regular polygon with $10$ sides",
    "solution": "$144.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $88 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 4, 8, 11, 22, 44, 88]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Factors of $358 = $",
    "solution": "$[1, 2, 179, 358]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $969$ minutes to hours & minutes",
    "solution": "$16$ hours and $9$ minutes"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find prime factors of $18$",
    "solution": "$2, 3, 3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Binary of $639 = $",
    "solution": "$0x27f$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $-22$ and exact value equals $-1$.",
    "solution": "$2100.0\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-6, -16, -18]\\cdot[9, -18, 4]=$",
    "solution": "$162$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -7/3x + 4$ and $y = 7/2x - 1$",
    "solution": "$(6/7, 2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Volume of cone with height $= 7m$ and radius $= 6m$ is",
    "solution": "$263 m^3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Fourth angle of quadrilateral with angles $85 , 45, 16 =$",
    "solution": "$214$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Area of circle with center $(-1,-7)$ and passing through $(-4.0, -7.0)$ is",
    "solution": "$28.27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\cos(90) = $",
    "solution": "$0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is $1$% of $78$?",
    "solution": "$0.78$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Convert $34F4$ from base $16$ to base $10$.",
    "solution": "$13556$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Surface area of pyramid with base length $= 24m$, base width $= 26m$, and height $= 5m$ is",
    "solution": "$1248 m^2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$33+26=$",
    "solution": "$59$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-18, 10)$ and $(13, 21)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{1082}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$28\\div4=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+10x+9$",
    "solution": "$(x+9)(x+1)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the percentage error when observed value equals $88$ and exact value equals $71$.",
    "solution": "$23.94\\%$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 86 & 16 & -6 & 59 & -94 \\\\ -29 & 78 & -18 & 10 & -26 \\\\ -50 & 78 & -42 & -96 & -19 \\\\ 44 & 60 & 73 & 44 & -22 \\\\ 24 & -95 & -1 & -2 & -85 \\\\ 14 & 99 & -7 & -39 & 91 \\\\ 65 & 44 & 12 & 100 & 7 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -33 & -44 & -44 & -82 & -38 & 29 & 23 \\\\ 70 & 100 & 80 & -9 & -17 & 57 & -60 \\\\ -52 & 54 & -87 & 92 & 13 & 93 & -49 \\\\ -16 & 96 & -57 & -99 & 94 & 22 & 18 \\\\ 92 & 48 & 21 & 78 & -47 & 0 & -63 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -10998 & -1356 & -7319 & -20921 & 6346 & 4146 & 8296 \\\\ 4801 & 7816 & 7966 & -2998 & 1704 & 2151 & -2647 \\\\ 9082 & -2396 & 17167 & 7556 & -8103 & -3022 & -4303 \\\\ -3776 & 11174 & -6457 & -3504 & 3427 & 12453 & -3987 \\\\ -15178 & -14882 & -10240 & -7637 & 4497 & -4856 & 11620 \\\\ 15828 & 9530 & 12047 & 8276 & -10249 & 4540 & -11710 \\\\ -645 & 12124 & -5937 & -13976 & 6009 & 7709 & -374 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13+39=$",
    "solution": "$52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8\\cdot11$",
    "solution": "$88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simplify $33^{10^{4}}$",
    "solution": "$33^{40}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The definite integral within limits $0$ to $1$ of the equation $68x^2 + 49x + 68 = $",
    "solution": "$115.1667$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{3} + 8x^{7} + 3x^{6} + 7x^{6}$",
    "solution": "$\\frac{2}{3}x^{4} + \\frac{8}{7}x^{8} + \\frac{3}{6}x^{7} + \\frac{7}{6}x^{7} + C$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-12, 12)$ and $(-11, 15)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{10}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3999$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$4369.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What is the percentage difference between $170$ and $76$?",
    "solution": "$76.42$%"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 91 & 73 & 25 & -53 & 7 \\\\ 20 & 24 & 85 & -70 & 97 \\\\ 92 & -92 & -90 & 23 & -82 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -37 & 14 & -62 & -21 & -19 & -15 & -35 & 98 & -50 \\\\ 14 & -41 & -31 & -62 & -94 & -28 & -31 & 5 & -97 \\\\ -91 & -31 & 41 & -88 & 29 & 58 & -14 & 17 & 83 \\\\ 84 & -57 & -49 & -19 & 78 & -80 & -13 & -73 & -62 \\\\ -74 & 100 & -69 & 53 & 3 & 74 & 70 & -8 & -1 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -9590 & 1227 & -4766 & -7259 & -11979 & 2799 & -4619 & 13521 & -6277 \\\\ -21197 & 10351 & -1762 & -2917 & -5340 & 16736 & 5066 & 7859 & 7970 \\\\ 11498 & -1661 & -2011 & 6909 & 5838 & -11932 & -5147 & 6003 & -4490 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "LCM of $15$ and $12 =$",
    "solution": "$60$"
  }
]